<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <!--
      This is HTML template for atom.xml RSS feed. It needs to be saved as HTML due to create-react-app limitation what
      is treating XML files as media, and .ejs files too
    -->
    <title>RuneLite</title>
    <subtitle>
    RuneLite is a free, open-source and super fast client for Old School
    RuneScape. You can download the RuneLite launcher for various platforms below
    or contribute to the project on GitHub.
  </subtitle>
    <link href="https://runelite.net"/>
    <link href="https://runelite.net/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
    <id>https://runelite.net/</id>
    <updated>2018-10-11T12:07:01.192Z</updated>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-10-11-1.4.21-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-10-11-1.4.21-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.21 Release</title>
        <summary>Bank tag tabs, master clue 3-step cryptic solutions, partial grand exchange name searching, and various plugin visual improvements</summary>
        <updated>2018-10-11T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <h2 id="bank-tag-tabs">Bank tag tabs</h2>
<p>Thanks to the tireless work of <a href="https://github.com/raiyni">@raiyni</a>, and supporting work from
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> and <a href="https://github.com/Abextm">@Abextm</a>, we are proud
to offer a new bank tag experience in bank tag tabs!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/bank-tag-tabs-intro.gif" alt="Bank tag tabs: adding and selecting tabs"/></p>
<p>As indicated above, tabs can be created for any number of tags by clicking the &quot;+&quot; button in the
upper-left-hand corner of the bank interface, and selecting these tabs will display items tagged
with that tab&#39;s tag. More information regarding its features and functionalities can be found <a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite/wiki/Bank-Tags#using-tag-tabs">by
browsing the Bank Tags wiki
page</a>.</p>
<h2 id="master-clue-3-step-cryptic-solutions">Master clue 3-step cryptic solutions</h2>
<p>The Clue Scroll plugin now displays solutions for master-level three step cryptic clues, removing
steps from the overlay as they are completed. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/eadgars-ruse">@Eadgars-ruse</a> for submitting
<a href="https://streamable.com/ujaar">(and demonstrating in video form)</a> this feature!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/master-three-step-cryptic-clue-full.png" alt="Master-level three step cryptic clue solution"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/master-three-step-cryptic-clue-partial.png" alt="Partial solution for master-level three step cryptic clue"/></p>
<h2 id="grand-exchange-partial-name-searching">Grand Exchange partial name searching</h2>
<p>The Grand Exchange search panel and ingame <code>!price</code> command now allow for partial name searching,
yielding better results than before. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Adam-">@Adam-</a> for implementing
this enhancement.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/grand-exchange-search-before-after.gif" alt="Grand exchange search results: before and after"/></p>
<h2 id="visual-improvements">Visual improvements</h2>
<p>Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Adam-">@Adam-</a>, <a href="https://github.com/Monsterxsync">@Monsterxsync</a>,
<a href="https://github.com/psikoi">@psikoi</a>, and
<a href="https://github.com/SebastiaanVanspauwen">@SebastiaanVanspauwen</a> respectively, a number of plugins
have had their visuals updated, which can be seen below:</p>
<ul>
<li>The &quot;To:&quot; and &quot;From:&quot; in split private chat can now be recolored</li>
<li>A toggle has been added to use default skill coloring for XP globe progress arcs</li>
<li>XP globes&#39; progress bar has been changed into an overlay directly on the globe to save space</li>
<li>A chatbox background image has been added to the 2005 interface style</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/recolored-split-private-chat-to-from.png" alt="Recolored &quot;To:&quot; and &quot;From:&quot; in split private chat"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/xp-globes-default-skill-color.png" alt="XP globes default skill colors"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/xp-globes-progress-overlay.png" alt="Updated XP globes progress overlay"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.21-Release/2005-chat-background.gif" alt="2005 interface chat background"/></p>
<p>The Camera Zoom plugin has been disabled until we can fix it for the update today.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The percentage completion component of the XP tracker is now accurate to two decimal places</li>
<li>The 2010 interface style has had some tab icon offsets updated to be more accurate to the style</li>
<li>Cavaliers will now display their buy limit in the grand exchange plugin</li>
<li>Mouse tooltips should now properly be hidden whenever a RuneScape tooltip is displayed</li>
<li>Chat notification highlight words now ignore leading and trailing space for highlight terms</li>
<li>Regen meters should now be more accurate for the beginning and end of a regen cycle</li>
<li>Overlays snapped above chatbox will now be rendered when text input or chat dialogs are open</li>
<li>An option has been added to the boosts overlay to display in yellow when below the boost threshold</li>
<li>Notifications have been added for highlighted ground items</li>
<li>The Fairy ring plugin now remembers scroll position when re-opening the fairy ring menu</li>
<li>The Slayer plugin will now update when assigned a task through partner slayer</li>
<li>The NPC HP overlay has been updated to use a more accurate HP formula</li>
<li>The Loot tracker no longer tries to add empty slots from Chambers of Xeric or Theatre of Blood</li>
<li>The newly-added Al Kharid palace shortcuts have been added to the agility obstacle highlighter</li>
<li>An idle alert should no longer trigger after casting most Lunar spells</li>
<li>A toggle to send a notification upon the Ulitmate Force powerup spawning in Nightmare Zone has
been added</li>
<li>The Kingdom of Miscellania completion state check has been corrected</li>
<li>Several bank tag editing edge cases have been fixed</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Jordan</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 23 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (7):
      feed controller: move feed result fetch to spring scheduler
      http service: return item names in price lookup
      http-api: modify ItemPrice to contain id/name instead of Item
      mixins: fix runelite message not being cleared on reused messages nodes
      chat message manager: add support for coloring to/from
      runelite-client: update for search api changes
      ge search: cap max results at 100

Bailey Townsend (1):
      Add buy limit for cavalier hats to GE plugin (#5855)

Eadgars-Ruse (2):
      Fix and improve cryptic clues
      Add solutions for 3 step cryptic master clues

Eric White (1):
      Increase XP tracker accuracy to 2 decimal places (#5845)

GravitySalad (2):
      Add additional search tags for interface styles and pve plugins
      Change plugin search to include the plugin description

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      2010 styles: Fix emotes and music tab offsets (#5884)

Jordan Atwood (1):
      mouse tooltips: Don&#39;t add a tooltip if another is present

Kamiel (3):
      Fix chat notification highlight words split regex (#5798)
      Change regen meter stroke end-cap style to CAP_BUTT
      Fix snapped overlays above chatbox not being rendered

Magic fTail (3):
      Add support for making the boost colour yellow if below boost threshold
      Update osrs wiki link
      Stop CoX party size from showing before varb is loaded

Marshall (1):
      Add highlighted ground item notifications (#3647)

Max Weber (7):
      Add thread assertions to Widget
      WidgetInspector: run on client thread
      runelite-client: Make Widget::isHidden only run on client thread
      Add thread assertion to getVar(Varbits)
      runelite-client: Make getVar(Varbits) only run on the client thread
      fairyring: Don&#39;t loose scroll position
      timetracking: Show overview completion by tab, not implementation

Monsterxsync (1):
      Add default skill coloring to XP globe arcs

Nathen Sample (4):
      Improve readability of stackformatter tests
      Add support for partner assignment to slayer plugin (#5782)
      Improve attack style plugin encapsulation (#5806)
      Improve BA plugin encapsulation (#5807)

Ron Young (9):
      Add bank-related widget ids, scripts and varbits
      Add script for managing current bank tab
      Add method for getting keys based on prefix from ConfigManager
      Add tag tabs to bank tags plugin
      More accurate NPC hp overlay when max hp is known (#5528)
      widget: expose setchildren (#5309)
      Don&#39;t update tags if interface is force closed
      Don&#39;t change the active tab if tags are being edited
      Don&#39;t assume bank title is the same as search str because it truncate...

Ruben Amendoeira (1):
      XP Globes - Move progress bar display from tooltip to globe (#5856)

Sebastiaan Vanspauwen (1):
      Interface plugin: Added 2005 chatbox

Tomas Slusny (15):
      Fix Raids plugin varbit access not happening on client thread
      Move map clue checking to MenuOptionClicked
      Skip empty spots in Loot Tracker when getting items
      Fix NPE in Miscellania plugin on DC
      Use NpcSpawned/Despawned events for checking clue NPCs
      Move clue inventory/equipment assignment to ItemContainerChanged
      Inverse findClueScroll conditions
      Do not set hint arrows for object clue scroll
      Correctly highlight ObjectClueScroll for single location
      Remove clue scroll timeout
      Add executor service logger that logs exceptions
      Remove unnecessary calls to RunnableExceptionLogger
      Add method for standardizing text input to Text
      Use TAG_SEARCH const instead of hardcoding &quot;tag:&quot; in Bank Tags
      Properly reset search when deleting active tag tab

Tyler Nichols (2):
      Remove unused variable &quot;rank&quot; in HiscorePanel (#5843)
      Do not show quantity value for items with no GE/HA value (#5850)

forsco (4):
      Add new Al-Kharid palace agility shortcuts (#5800)
      Remove idle alerts from Lunar Spells shared animation (#5863)
      Fix spelling of Burthorpe Games Room in Discord Rich Presence (#5886)
      Correct Burthorpe spelling for Discord rich presence

mikek2 (1):
      Add ultimate force notification trigger to NMZ plugin (#5790)

robinwithes (1):
      Fix NPE in Grand Exchange search caused by null entry (#5911)

trimbe (1):
      Kingdom Plugin: fix throne completion state check (#5874)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-10-04-1.4.20-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-10-04-1.4.20-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.20 Release</title>
        <summary>Currently-hovered tile highlight, Control-locked zoom, and removed Runecrafting pouch counter</summary>
        <updated>2018-10-04T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The Tile Indicators plugin can now show your currently hovered tile. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@Deathbeam</a> for this feature.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.20-Release/tile-indicator-highlighted-tile.gif" alt="Currently-hovered tile indicator"/></p>
<p>The Camera Zoom plugin can now require the Control key be held down to enable zooming via the scroll
wheel. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/MagicfTail">@MagicfTail</a> for this feature.</p>
<p>The world map overlay has had its fairy ring icon changed to be easier on the eyes.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.20-Release/fairy-ring-icon-change.png" alt="Cleaner fairy ring icon"/></p>
<p>The Runecrafting plugin has had its pouch counter removed as the data we relied on to display that
information was removed in last week&#39;s Runecrafting pouch emptying and filling update.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>An option has been added to hide XP globes and/or XP trackers for skills which have reached level
99</li>
<li>A stamina timer will be started when you are the recipient of a dose via the Boost Potion Share
spell</li>
<li>Various clues have had their item requirements fixed</li>
<li>The idle notifier will notify you when you&#39;ve stopped collecting sand</li>
<li>The friends list counter now correctly displays the maximum friends list capacity for members</li>
<li>Obstacle highlighting has been added for the Meiyerditch entrance, the Weiss entrance, and
the McGrubor&#39;s Woods railing</li>
<li>The raids scouting overlay is now hidden when on Olm&#39;s floor</li>
<li>The raids ending message default color has been improved</li>
<li>Items examined within the clue scroll reward panel or smithing interface-as well as item
placeholders within the bank-will now display their price information</li>
<li>Tars, leather shields, and super antifire potions have been added to the skill calculator</li>
<li>The cannon spot for ice trolls has been improved via a slight adjustment</li>
<li>Timers which no longer apply will now clear themselves upon death</li>
<li>Map clues will now indicate in the clue overlay if you are missing a spade in your inventory</li>
<li>A Karamja diary requirement has been corrected</li>
<li>The screenshot plugin can now take screenshots upon player death</li>
<li>The Salty Peter clue scroll now gives you a hint on his general direction (he may still wander
outside of view of that spot, so be sure to look out for him!)</li>
<li>The slayer plugin now displays icons for all missing wilderness task monsters</li>
<li>Wilderness slayer updates from the slayer gem no longer interfere with the plugin highlighting
monsters</li>
<li>The 2010 interface style has had some icon locations adjusted to be better aligned</li>
<li>Chat commands now have more descriptive tooltips within the settings menu, indicating the exact
text needed to use the command</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Jordan</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 17 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Andre (2):
      Truncate NPC name instead of subtitle in Loot Tracker (#5740)
      Add option to hide both globes and xp tracker after 99 (#5741)

Chris Hranj (1):
      Update stamina potion timer to include shared stamina potions (#5750)

Christopher O&#39;Hara (2):
      Fix amulet of glory item requirement for elite clue scroll
      Add sand collection to idle notifier

Forsco (1):
      Update membership days VarPlayer id

Jordan Atwood (6):
      player indicators plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      wasd camera plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      corp plugin: Fix settings description typo
      world map plugin: Update fairy ring icon
      agility plugin: Highlight Meiyerditch entrance obstacles
      Revert &quot;Truncate NPC name instead of subtitle in Loot Tracker (#5740)&quot;

Kamiel (2):
      Add default cc info chatcolor and change cc info highlight to red
      Make raids scout overlay not show at Olm (#5734)

Magic fTail (3):
      Add option to require control to be held for zooming
      Add support for examine price to clue scroll reward
      Rename zoom handling script

Max Weber (2):
      runelite-client: Don&#39;t duplicate chatbox input when widget ids are wrong
      cluescrolls: add bullroarer to items list for bullroarer clue

Robbie McLeod (1):
      Add Tar to the Herblore Skill calculator

Ron Young (1):
      widget: expose drag methods (#5735)

Tomas Slusny (15):
      Properly name Perspective methods, remove unused
      Add mappings for checkClick, mouseCanvasHoverX/Y
      Add currently hovered tile to TileIndicators
      Remove pouch counter from Runecraft plugin
      Remove dupe strings from AnagramClue
      Remove dupe strings from CipherClue
      Make sprite and widget sprite overrides more flexible
      Make interface styles not replace entire override map
      Cleanup GE plugin code
      Make examine plugin work with placeholders
      Make examine work for smithing interface
      Export widget onLoadListener
      Fix BlastFurnace access levels and subscriber names
      Fix screenshot plugin access levels
      Fix special counter access levels and subscriber names

bowlcutmullet (1):
      Use more optimal location for Jatizso Ice Trolls cannon spot (#5715)

johnhamilto (1):
      Remove timers on local player death

raiyni (1):
      Require spade on map dig clues

rbbi (1):
      Add leather shields to the crafting calculator (#4331)

robinwithes (9):
      Add mcgrubor woods railing to agility plugin (#5705)
      Add super antifire to skill calculator (#5708)
      Fix achievement diary Brimhaven Dungeon requirement (#5706)
      Add option to take screenshot on local player death (#5711)
      Add location for Salty Peter clue scroll (#5730)
      Add chaos druids, bandits and magic axes to slayer plugin (#5759)
      Added ALL remaining missing wilderness tasks (#5760)
      Add support for parsing Wilderness assignment updates to slayer plugin (#5757)
      Add missing Weiss agility obstacles (#5785)

trimbe (3):
      Update location for terrorchick cage hot/cold
      Adjust tab icon offsets for 2010 interface style
      Chat Commands: Add hints to config description (#5747)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-27-1.4.19-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-27-1.4.19-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.19 Release</title>
        <summary>Grand Exchange buy limits, Barbarian Assault game/wave duration timers</summary>
        <updated>2018-09-27T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Grand Exchange buy limits were added to the Grand Exchange plugin, which will show <code>Buy limit: x</code>
in GE window for items with known buy limits. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Asymons">@Asymons</a> for this contribution.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.19-Release/buylimits.png" alt="gebuylimits"/></p>
<p>A timer for Barbarian Assault waves and full game was added to the Barbarian Assault plugin that will
announce the times in your chat thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Jacoblairm">@Jacoblairm</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.19-Release/bawave.png" alt="bawave"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.19-Release/bagame.png" alt="bagame"/></p>
<p>There are also numerous smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Duplicated display of actively traded price in GE interface has been fixed</li>
<li>Teleblock timers are now removed when entering safe zone/leaving wilderness</li>
<li>Search bar was added to the skill calculator plugin</li>
<li>Little boulder in Weiss was added to the agility plugin obstacle highlighting</li>
<li>Notes plugin now supports undo and redo (with ctrl-z and ctrl-u)</li>
<li>Instance map now has a close button in top-right corner</li>
<li>NPC indicators now has support for highlighting the south-west tile for large NPCs</li>
<li>Idle notifier now also supports idle notifications for low oxygen on Fossil Island</li>
<li>Charged versions of the new wilderness weapons will now display their prices correctly</li>
<li>World map clipping in fixed mode has been fixed</li>
<li>Multiple world points for hot/cold clues has been centered and should not show the wrong destination anymore</li>
<li>The opponent info plugin now has a configuration option to always show opponent health in percent</li>
<li>The Discord plugin now has a configuration option to hide the &quot;time elapsed&quot;</li>
<li>You can now configure the prayer flick helper to show even when prayers are off</li>
<li>Fix loot tracker not grouping Barrows loots</li>
</ul>
<p>In regards to the <a href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-18-Worldhopper-disabled">world hopper being disabled</a>:
After speaking with Jagex and other client developers, we think the chat message hop-to option is what is causing the issues. Jagex is allowing us to readd the world hopper without this feature in this release, and will let us know if it causes any further problems.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 24 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (2):
      opponent info: add config opt to show health as percent
      xp tracker: limit to one update per 5 minutes

Alessio (1):
      Add GE limits to Grand Exchange Plugin Search

ArthurTsvettsih (1):
      Add Undo Redo support for the Note plugin (#5606)

Ben Moyer (1):
      Reduce tab size in notes panel to 2 (#5599)

Jacob McElroy (2):
      Add barbarian assault game duration timer (#4590)
      Fix Fremennik Hot/Cold clue scroll dig location.

Jordan Atwood (6):
      Add IN_WILDERNESS Varbit
      Add PVP and Deadman widget info
      worldtype: Add PVP_WORLD_TYPES and isPvpWorld
      timers plugin: Reset Teleblock on entering safe zone
      slayer plugin: Add parsing for boss task assignments
      slayer plugin: Use boss pets as slayer icons

Justin Barnyak (1):
      Change Prayerbar Color Scheme to be Colorblind Friendly

MSAskew (1):
      Updated co-ordinates to match location suggested by user and cross-referenced with osrs wiki to confirm as there were two possibilities.

Max Weber (1):
      devtools: Add Interacting arrow devtool

Michael Goodwin (1):
      Fix HotColdLocation WorldPoint

Mike (1):
      Add option to disable time elapsed on discord activity (#5590)

Robin Withes Linux (1):
      Lady of the lake clue scroll rename

Runelite auto updater (1):
      [maven-release-plugin] prepare for next development iteration

Shaun Dreclin (1):
      Add option to always show prayer flick helper

Tomas Slusny (4):
      Simplify checkbox checks in skill calc
      Fix GE OSB actively traded price races
      Cleanup skill calculator
      Move IconTextField common icons to IconTextField.Icon class

Unknown (1):
      instancemap: add &#39;X&#39; button on the interface to close map

davidyip50 (1):
      Correct location of Kharazi Jungle Hot/Cold clue (#5610)

johnhamilto (1):
      Add south-western tile indicator to NPC indicators (#5551)

ltvill (2):
      Hot/Cold clue West of Brimhaven location fix
      Hot/Cold clue near Fishing tutor location fix

psikoi (1):
      Fix loot tracker box subtitle

rbbi (1):
      Add searchbar suppor to Skill Calculator

robinwithes (2):
      Add little boulder from weiss into agility obstacles (#5636)
      Add oxygen alert to idle notifier (#5630)

rune3132 (1):
      Add wilderness weapons item mappings

steffenhauge (1):
      Add Justiciar armor set prayer bonuses to the prayer plugin (#5651)

trimbe (1):
      Fix clipping in fixed mode for edge snapping map points
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-20-1.4.18-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-20-1.4.18-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.18 Release</title>
        <summary>Wintertodt plugin and virtual levels plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-09-20T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A Wintertodt plugin was added which shows your current activity and can be
configured to notify you when you become idle. It also tracks points in your
inventory from logs or kindling and displays it. Thanks to work from
<a href="https://github.com/jbfleischman">@jbfleischman</a> for initially getting this
started.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.18-Release/wintertodt1.png" alt="wintertodt1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.18-Release/wintertodt2.png" alt="wintertodt2"/></p>
<p>A virtual levels plugin was added which shows virtual levels and virtual skill
total on the skills tab. It is off by default. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Joshua-F">@Joshua
Filby</a> and
<a href="https://github.com/Nightfirecat">@Nightfirecat</a> for their work on this.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.18-Release/virtuallevels.png" alt="virtuallevels"/></p>
<p>There are also numerous smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Add Fairy Ring AIQ to Mudskipper Point Clue</li>
<li>Colorize &quot;Lookup&quot; player menu entry if applicable</li>
<li>Fix Dwarf Cannon quest start location on the world map</li>
<li>Add notification for low fishing trawler activity</li>
<li>Add sand to Daily Notifications plugin</li>
<li>Add daily runes to Daily Notifications plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>Regarding the <a href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-18-Worldhopper-disabled">world hopper being
disabled</a>, we
have fairly thoroughly reviewed other hopping implementations and can not find
anything with the World Hopper action forcing that would differentiable on
Jagex&#39;s side. Based on the
<a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite/commits/master/runelite-client/src/main/java/net/runelite/client/plugins/worldhopper/WorldHopperPlugin.java">plugin history</a>
the newest addition is the Hop-To chat option from pull
<a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite/pull/5125">#5125</a> which went into RuneLite
release 1.4.15 on Aug 30. Because other clients do not have this feature, this
is my first guess as to what the problem is.</p>
<p>I have asked Jagex to review if there were any issues with the world hopper
prior to Aug 30. If not, we should be able to remove the chatbox Hop-to feature and
reenable the plugin.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (3):
      world hopper: disable world hopper plugin
      Add Wintertodt Plugin
      runelite-api: add queueChangedSkill for queueing a skill change event

Gary (1):
      Add Fairy Ring AIQ to Mudskipper Point Clue

Jordan Atwood (8):
      hiscore plugin: Colorize &quot;Lookup&quot; player menu entry
      Add world map surface selector and overview map widgets
      world map overlay: Render on ABOVE_WIDGETS layer
      world map overlay: Clip around widgets above map
      Centralize item (de)spawn log messages
      opponent info plugin: Fix possible onGameTick NPE
      clue scroll overlay: Show visible emote widget area
      Add Virtual Levels plugin

Lotto (1):
      entityhider: make hidden entities not occupy the tile they&#39;re on

Max Weber (5):
      runescape-api: Update setWorldMapPositionTarget&#39;s name
      Worldmap: Fix Dwarf Cannon start location
      idlenotifier: Correctly warn about AFK kicking
      banktags: Don&#39;t use cs2 to add menu options
      Revert &quot;Add camera setters to Client.java and RSClient.java.&quot;

Runelite auto updater (1):
      [maven-release-plugin] prepare for next development iteration

Sebastiaan Vanspauwen (2):
      MTA: Fixed alchemy
      BA plugin: widget overlay fix

Shaun Dreclin (1):
      Refactor daily task indicator plugin

ShaunDreclin (2):
      Add notification for low fishing trawler activity
      Add sand to daily task indicator

Tomas Slusny (5):
      Make HiscoreClient call the OSRS hiscore API directly
      Fix WorldMapPlugin
      Add option for displaying only last fished fish
      Add fishing spot display configuration
      Return null instead of IllegalArgumentException from hiscore

astaninger (1):
      Add daily runes to Daily Notifications plugin (#5219)

rbbi (1):
      Change skill calc checkboxes to radio buttons (#4373)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-18-Worldhopper-disabled</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-18-Worldhopper-disabled"/>
        <title>World Hopper plugin disabled</title>
        <summary>World Hopper plugin disabled</summary>
        <updated>2018-09-18T21:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Jagex has requested we remove the world hopper plugin because it is getting
flagged by their bot detection. It has been removed until we can sort out how to
fix it with them. I do not know why our world hopper is being flagged and the
world hopper on other clients is not.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-13-1.4.17-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-13-1.4.17-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.17 Release</title>
        <summary>Loot tracker grouping, home and minigame cooldown timers, minigame and quest world map icons, and various bug fixes and enhancements</summary>
        <updated>2018-09-13T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The Loot tracker plugin now has a setting to group loot by NPC/event. In addition, a right-click
menu has been added to view details of a specific NPC&#39;s loots. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/psikoi">@psikoi</a> for this feature!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.17-Release/grouped-loot-tracker.gif" alt="grouped-loot-tracker"/></p>
<p>Home and minigame teleports will now add a timer for their cooldowns.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.17-Release/home-minigame-teleport-timers.png" alt="home-minigame-teleport-timers"/></p>
<p>The World Map plugin now displays tooltips for quest and minigame names, thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/johnhamilto">@johnhamilto</a> and <a href="https://github.com/MagicfTail">@MagicfTail</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.17-Release/quest-tooltips.png" alt="quest-tooltips"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.17-Release/minigame-tooltips.png" alt="minigame-tooltips"/></p>
<p>There are also numerous smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The Achievement Diary plugin has been fixed</li>
<li>The idle notifier now considers mouse clicks, not mouse movement, to determine when players are
no longer idle for the Idle Notifier plugin</li>
<li>Fixed Fishing plugin inventory and equipment check</li>
<li>The Player-owned House plugin now displays the new Troll stronghold teleport portal</li>
<li>The farming tracker now tracks the Weiss herb patch</li>
<li>The bottom-right snap corner no longer moves when the collapsible chatbox is opened</li>
<li>Cutting sacred eels will no longer incorrectly trigger the Idle Notifier plugin</li>
<li>Time tracking tabs have been better ordered by priority</li>
<li>The vanilla Tithe farm overlay has been made layoutable and now replaces the previous custom
overlay</li>
<li>Wizard&#39;s tower clue solutions now indicate the nearby fairy ring for convenience</li>
<li>The stairway to the task-only Kurask room and Godwars crossbow climbing rocks are now highlighted</li>
<li>Weiss and Troll stronghold basalt teleports and Kharedst&#39;s Memoirs teleports have been added to
the World Map plugin</li>
<li>The Ape Atoll Arceuus teleport location has been fixed in the World Map plugin</li>
<li>Dark crabs have been added to the Fishing plugin</li>
<li>Quest screenshots now use a standardized naming format</li>
<li>The Chambers of Xeric party size overlay indicator is now hidden when raiding solo</li>
<li>Ogre bellows now display the number of charges they contain</li>
<li>NPCs highlighted with the slayer plugin are now immediately un-highlighted upon task completion</li>
<li>Fixed 2005 interface swapper sprites for quest and spellbook icons</li>
<li>The clue scroll plugin now checks for sets across the user&#39;s inventory and equipped items</li>
<li>Upon killing Grotesque Guardians, a timer is created showing the time until the instance closes</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Jordan</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 14 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (2):
      http-service: add caching for hiscore lookups
      http-api: use https for hiscore urls

Damen (1):
      Add Grotesque Guardians instance close timer (#4338)

Jordan Atwood (8):
      interface styles plugin: Add more error handling
      Fix SpriteIDs from 2018/08/30 update
      clue scroll plugin: Check for sets across inventory and equipment
      timers plugin: Reset fields on shutdown
      Add home teleport animation and graphic definitions
      Add minigame teleport button widget info
      Add home teleport widget info
      timers plguin: Add teleport cooldown timers

Mack Bryan (3):
      Add ogre bellows to item charges plugin (#5323)
      Moved hot-cold dig location 3 tiles east into the correct range.
      Remove npc highlights on task completed message. (#5416)

Magic fTail (3):
      Add Quest to quest screenshots
      WorldMapPlugin: Add tooltip to minigame icons
      Don&#39;t show party size in overlay when solo raiding

Max Weber (7):
      diaryreqs: Update scrollbar with new length
      cache: name InterfaceDefinition fields
      cache: Disassemble CS1s
      runelite-api: Update widget field names
      cache: Store ID in ScriptLoader
      cache: add various world map related opcodes
      runelite-mixins: Add setter for varcint

Ron Young (1):
      Add missing widget types to WidgetType class (#5306)

Ruben Amendoeira (1):
      loot tracker: add view for grouping loot by npc/event

Sebastiaan Vanspauwen (6):
      Added Kurask Slayer Room Overlay
      Added Godwars Crossbow Shortcut
      Worldmap: Added Weiss and Troll Stronghold teleports
      Worldmap: Fixed Ape Atoll Arceuus Location
      Worldmap: Added Kharedst&#39;s Memoirs teleports
      Fishing: Added Dark Crab Overlay

Spencer (1):
      Added fairy ring code to wizard tower clue solutions

Tomas Slusny (14):
      Make bottom-right snap corner not account for chatbox
      Fix fishing plugin inventory/equipment check
      Fix Achievment Diary widget ids
      Add Sacred Eeels cutting to idle notifier
      Make fishing overlays use hidden instead of manager
      Make cannon plugin use hidden instead of manager
      Make Kourend library use hidden field instead of manager
      Reorder time tracker tabs by priority
      Replace Tithe Farm overlay with layoutable widget
      Deprecate queries with already existing events
      Add mappings for mouse last pressed millis
      Use mouse/keyboard idle state properly in IdleNotifier
      Simulate ItemContainerChange events on plugin startup
      Remove unnecessary fishing spot configuration

davidyip50 (1):
      Add troll stronghold portal icon support to POH (#5404)

johnhamilto (1):
      Add quest name tooltips to the world map (#5410)

oplosthee (1):
      Add Weiss herb patch to the farming tracker
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-06-1.4.16-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-09-06-1.4.16-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.16 Release</title>
        <summary>Layoutable Runescape widgets, top-center snap point, and automatic bounty target hiscore lookup</summary>
        <updated>2018-09-06T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>RuneScape widgets are now layoutable, meaning they can be anchored to the overlay hotspots like
Runelite overlays. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@Deathbeam</a> for this feature!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.16-Release/layoutable-runescape-widgets.gif" alt="layoutable-runescape-widgets"/></p>
<p>A top-center snap point has been added, and the XP Globes plugin has been set to use it by default,
also thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@Deathbeam</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.16-Release/top-center-snap-point.gif" alt="top-center-snap-point"/></p>
<p>An option has been added to the hiscore plugin to automatically look up bounty targets when they are
assigned, thanks to <a href="https://github.com/noelkeijzer">@noelkeijzer</a>.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Loot tracker now behaves correctly when multiple enemies die on same tick,
when player is despawned and when receiving Theatre of Blood drops</li>
<li>Some common items have been added to the ground item plugin&#39;s hidden items list by default</li>
<li>The idle logout timer supports checking the logout timer when in combat</li>
<li>The dense essence idle animation has been fixed and will correctly trigger the idle notifier</li>
<li>The fossil island oxygen bar and pest control info widgets are now movable</li>
<li>Some noisy plugin features have been disabled by default, or made to display only when in use</li>
<li>&quot;Trade-with&quot; is now swapped also with the trade option of the menu entry swapper plugin</li>
<li>Fixed the magic training arena dragonstone hint arrow not being cleared</li>
<li>Prayer and run orb tooltips no longer display when the minimap is hidden</li>
<li>The run energy tooltip now shows remaining energy when the orb shows run time remaining</li>
<li>Some achievement diary requirements texts have been corrected</li>
<li>Various skill calculator entries have been re-ordered to come in level requirement order</li>
<li>Ourania teleport has been added to the skill calculator</li>
<li>Fixed binding necklace charge counter when checking a necklace with one charge</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Jordan</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 14 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (2):
      Revert &quot;Make same-tick same-tile loot event fire once&quot;
      loot manager: limit to one kill per location per tick

CC007 (1):
      Fix locale not being applied for StackFormatterTest (#5216)

Magic fTail (2):
      Fix dense essence idle animation
      Add support for combat idle 20 minute timer

Max Weber (3):
      cache: Do not depend on Index insertion ordering
      cache: Properly produce `\n` only on windows on jdk9+
      Import Widget::fontId

Michael Goodwin (4):
      Make same-tick same-tile loot event fire once
      Check for player HP being 0 in player loot event
      Add common method for converting local to world point
      Check for correct ToB region when receiving loot

Noël Keijzer (1):
      Add automatic bounty hunter target lookup in HiScore plugin (#5193)

Sebastiaan Vanspauwen (1):
      WidgetOverlay: Make fossil island oxygen bar moveable (#5246)

Shaun Dreclin (4):
      Add clear button to var inspector devtool
      Add trade-with swap to menu entry swapper
      Fix ground markers getting set at wrong position
      Fix mta dragonstone hint arrow not clearing

Tomas Slusny (12):
      Make RuneScape widgets layoutable
      Take preferred position into account when ordering
      Add common hidden items to GroundItemsPlugin
      Disable blast furnace clickboxes by default
      Disable lit/unlit burner indicators by default
      Make KourendLibrary overlay show only on interact
      Show fishing overlays only when player can fish
      Show cannon spot overlay only with cannon
      Disable XP globes plugin by default
      Add TOP_CENTER snap corner to snap center viewport
      Make XP globes use TOP_CENTER snap point
      Fix sorting order of overlays

Unmoon (3):
      Don&#39;t show prayer orb hover overlay if prayer orb is hidden
      Don&#39;t show run energy hover overlay if run energy orb is hidden
      Show run energy instead of time remaining if tooltip shows time remaining

astaninger (7):
      Fix watchtower Achievment Diary requirement (#5218)
      Fix ape atoll Achievment Diary agility requirement (#5220)
      Properly order prayer skill calculator (#5290)
      Fix dragonstone necklace name in skill calculator (#5287)
      Order tiaras in RC skill calc by experience gained (#5288)
      Sort planks in construction guide by XP in skill calc (#5289)
      Add ourania teleport to skill calculator (#5285)

ltvill (1):
      Fix formatting of &#39;s in OSRS location names

oplosthee (1):
      runecraft: fix binding necklace regex

raiyni (5):
      Widgets: add setItemId
      widget: add setItemQuantity
      widgets: setBorderThickness
      expose text shadowed
      Make pest control widgets layoutable
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-30-1.4.15-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-30-1.4.15-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.15 Release</title>
        <summary>Run energy plugin, friend list counter, team cape plugin improvements and hop-to in chat</summary>
        <updated>2018-08-30T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Run energy plugin was added thanks to <a href="https://github.com/seandewar">@seandewar</a>. This plugin will show tooltip with
your current weight, how much run time you have remaining and how much time it will take until your run energy fully
regens. Also it has optional setting for displaying remaining run seconds instead of run percentage in the run energy
bar.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/runenergy1.png" alt="runenergy1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/runenergy2.png" alt="runenergy2"/></p>
<p>Thanks to work of <a href="https://github.com/forsco">@forsco</a> and <a href="https://github.com/Adam-">@Adam-</a> friend and ignore list
counter has been added, that will simply show max amount and used amount of friends/ignored players in the respective
interfaces.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/friendlist.png" alt="friendlist"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/ItsSebas">@ItsSebas</a> improved team capes plugin interface to display team cape icons with counts
instead of text in panel. This new design should be more compact and less intrusive than old one (and also looks way
better!).</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/teamcapes.png" alt="teamcapes"/></p>
<p>The world hopper plugin now has support for hopping to people in chat via right-click menu thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/Retoxified">@Retoxified</a>:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/hopto.png" alt="hopto"/></p>
<p>Loose railing shortcut near Tree Gnome Village highlighting has been added to agility plugin thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/ItsSebas">@ItsSebas</a>:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.15-Release/looserailing.png" alt="looserailing"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The idle notifier plugin has been significantly improved, now it should not throw false warnings while
in combat or when doing activity that is using same animations as some of the animations that display
idle warning</li>
<li>Barrows kill count chat message will now properly update the !kc data</li>
<li>Time tracking plugin now also has &quot;Special patches&quot; in the overview tab</li>
<li>Teleblock timers are now removed on logout</li>
<li>Corp plugin now has option to hide the damage overlay</li>
<li>&quot;Pause all&quot; menu option has been added to XP tracker right-click menu</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 12 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (9):
      Fix friend and ignore widget id changes
      http service: improve update detection logic
      runelite-api: add method for getting number of friends
      Add Ignore API
      runelite-client: add friend list plugin
      widget id: update bottom line stones widget ids
      woodcutting plugin: fix npe rendering redwood trees if axe is null
      Revert &quot;Merge pull request #4568 from deathbeam/proper-shutdown&quot;
      Update sprite ids and overrides

DannysPVM (1):
      Add camera setters to Client.java and RSClient.java.

Karolcz125 (1):
      Add LMS to ignored type in WorldHopper (#5139)

Max Weber (1):
      Update Scripts to 2018-08-30-rev174

Michael Goodwin (1):
      Fix Hot/Cold Nardah Genie Cave location

Retoxified (1):
      Add Hop-To option in chat

Robbe De Neve (2):
      Add special patches to overview tab
      Add pause all button to xp tracker (#5126)

Ron Young (2):
      corp: hide damage overlay
      Reduce world map icon sizes (#5086)

RuneLite Cache-Code Autoupdater (3):
      Update Item IDs to 2018-08-30-rev174
      Update Object IDs to 2018-08-30-rev174
      Update Widget IDs to 2018-08-30-rev174

Sean Dewar (1):
      Add run energy plugin

Sebastiaan (2):
      Add Tree Gnome Village loose railing shortcut (#5093)
      Make teleblock timers disappear on logout/hop (#5090)

Sebastiaan Vanspauwen (1):
      Teamcapes plugin: Teamcape image instead of text (#5107)

Tomas Slusny (10):
      Add exports for GameEngine#shutDown
      Properly shutdown everything on window close
      Stop plugins on shutdown
      Reset idle timers when player clicks in-game
      Properly reset idle timers on logout and login
      Make animation idle remember last animating ID
      Make combat idle notifier use interacting changed
      Add idle notifier plugin tests
      Remove dupe PVP_HR entry in world hopper
      Fix setting of barrows kc from chat
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-23-1.4.13-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-23-1.4.13-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.13 &amp; 1.4.14 Release</title>
        <summary>Small enhancements and world hopper, WASD camera plugin fixes</summary>
        <updated>2018-08-23T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Jordan</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Minimap icons have been added for wilderness obelisk teleports and achievement
diary set item teleports. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/raiyni">@raiyni</a> for
contributing these icons.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/ardougne-cloak-teleport-icon.png" alt="ardougne cloak teleport icon"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/explorers-ring-teleport-icon.png" alt="explorer&#39;s ring teleport icon"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/fremennik-sea-boots-teleport-icon.png" alt="fremennik sea boots teleport icon"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/wilderness-obelisk-teleport-icons.png" alt="wilderness obelisk teleport icons"/></p>
<p>Several agility shortcuts and obstacles have been added to the agility shortcut
highlighter.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/falador-wall-shortcut.png" alt="falador wall shortcut"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/river-salve-shortcut.png" alt="river salve shortcut"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/underwater-obstacles.png" alt="underwater obstacles"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.13-Release/underwater-shortcuts.png" alt="underwater shortcuts"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The WASD plugin is now smarter at deciding when to block inputs to the game</li>
<li>Fix world hopper freezing client when trying to hop during times the game
prevents you from hopping</li>
<li>Add option to Corporeal Beast plugin to make left click on the Dark Energey
core &quot;Walk here&quot;</li>
<li>Fix Corporal Beast plugin overlay sometimes not showing</li>
<li>Fix Brimhaven agility alrena timer from resetting whenever an obstacle makes
you fall to the ground floor</li>
<li>Fix GE plugin not to show the OSB actively traded price more reliably</li>
<li>Fix NPCs with empty names being highlighted in some cases</li>
<li>Fix Pest control plugin detecting shield status</li>
<li>Time tracker stopwatches and timers now also accept more user-friendly time
strings, such as &quot;01h30m15s&quot;</li>
<li>Adjusted Autumn and Winter Deadman Mode teleblock timers have been created in
advance of the upcoming DMM tournaments</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Jordan</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (16):
      wasd plugin: pass through shift and escape
      wasd plugin: disable key listener if not logged in
      wasd plugin: pass through ctrl, alt, and tab
      wasd plugin: allow input to chat dialogs
      wasd plugin: fix slash to talk
      wasd plugin: check chatbox input widget visibility to determine if a dialog is open
      wasd plugin: release same keychar as pressed when changing to typing mode
      wasd plugin: allow input to world map search when focused
      mixins: fix friend manager mixin to implement friend manager
      corp plugin: deprioritize attack option on dark energy core
      barrows plugin: fix double counting price of coins
      pest control plugin: move portal text overlay underneath progress bar
      pest control plugin: cleanup &amp; lombokize
      corp plugin: fix losing track of corp when it spawns during loading
      agility plugin: fix brimhaven timer resetting when failing obstacles
      ge plugin: more reliably show actively traded price

ItsSebas (3):
      Add other side of Falador grapple wall highlight (#5028)
      Add missing agility shortcut near North River Salve (#5048)
      Add boss skill screenshots (#5030)

Jamy C (2):
      TimeTracking: Refactor time parsing and add tests (#5050)
      TimeTracking: Add support for intuitive time notations like &quot;1h 30m 10s&quot;

Jordan Atwood (3):
      Add CHAT_SCROLLBAR_ON_LEFT Varbit
      timers plugin: Add fall/winter DMM teleblock timers
      screenmarker plugin: Remove extra images

Lotto (1):
      worldhopper: fix spam in chatbox when trying to open switcher in bank

Magic fTail (4):
      Add Bastion and Battlemage potions
      Fix KBD respawn timer
      Add debugging to npc highlighter plugin
      Change boss kill screenshot naming

Robbie McLeod (1):
      Fix sidebar hotkey leaking into game client

Ron Young (4):
      Add wilderness obelisk teleport spots on map (#4937)
      Fix pest control shield state checks (#4977)
      Add ardougne cloak map teleport icons (#4998)
      Add Missing Achievement Diary Teleport Map Icons (#5027)

Sebastiaan (1):
      Add Fossil Island underwater agility obstacles (#5055)

Tomas Slusny (4):
      Omit empty strings in NPC indicators
      Add tests for parsing NPC list
      Make pressing BkSPACE with empty chat exit chat
      Remove unused Objects import in AgilityPlugin

astaninger (1):
      Fix fire surge icon and remove redundant smithing entries (#4979)

gandalfthegoat (1):
      add the fairy ring CKS to speak to Ulizius cryptic clue step

psikoi (2):
      Add activity priority to world list
      Fix activity ordering incosistency

trimbe (1):
      wasd plugin: use clientscript to determine what input to block
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-16-1.4.12-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-16-1.4.12-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.12 Release</title>
        <summary>World hopper and WASD camera plugins</summary>
        <updated>2018-08-16T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A world hopper plugin has been added to ease hopping. You can use the key
combination ctrl+shift+left/right, or right click a friend or clanmates name in
game and click Hop-to. There is also a plugin panel with the worlds listed which
can be double clicked.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.12-Release/whop1.png" alt="whop1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.12-Release/whop2.png" alt="whop2"/></p>
<p>A WASD camera plugin was added which lets you use the WASD keys (or, any other
keys) instead of the arrow keys to control the camera. It is off by default and
needs to be enabled in the configuration panel. You must press Enter to chat
when the plugin is enabled.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix puzzle box solver showing solution arrows</li>
<li>Fix player indicators plugin coloring entire menu option of other players</li>
<li>Add Wintertodt to Discord plugin activity</li>
<li>Add Woodcutting guild to Discord plugin activity</li>
<li>Fix SDMM normal spellbook freeze timers</li>
<li>Fix ancient freeze timers resetting on each animation</li>
<li>Fix Grotesque Guardian loot tracker</li>
<li>Fix seaweed patch times in the timer plugin</li>
<li>Fix Chambers of Xeric plugin to not add multiple timers</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (9):
      mixins: simplify acquiring client thread reference
      world service: split controller from service and add cache
      world controller: fix caching, move to scheduled method
      runescape-api: GameEngine doesn&#39;t extend KeyFocusListener
      timers plugin: don&#39;t reset freeze timers each animation
      Revert &quot;player indicators plugin: Use ColorUtil functions&quot;
      Add world load event
      cache: fix outputstream writeString to not write unicode strings
      runelite-client: add wasd camera plugin

Heikki Jetsonen (2):
      DiscordPlugin: Add wintertodt Activity
      Cluescrolls: Added fairy ring to Kalphite Lair Entrance clue

Jordan Atwood (2):
      time tracking plugin: Fix timers header color
      timers plugin: Fix SDMM normal spellbook freezes

Kamiel (1):
      Update npc_health.json

Lotto (12):
      runelite-api: add world switcher widget info
      mixins: add world hopping mixin
      runelite-api: expose ChatPlayer.world
      runelite-api: make ClanMember extend ChatPlayer
      runelite-api: add total level api
      runelite-client: add world hopper plugin
      runescape-api: add Protect annotation
      clues: allow any imbued crystal bow for emote clue
      clues: add fairy ring to sinclair mansion clue solution
      fpsindicator: fix overlay disappearing when using stretched fixed mode
      fpsindicator: fix overlay being cut off outside the canvas
      fpsindicator: remove caching of fps strings

Magic fTail (2):
      Fix Grotesque Guardian loot tracker
      Actually add special case for Grotesque Guardians

Max Weber (2):
      Make the second argument of SpriteManager::getSprite work
      runelite-client: Don&#39;t consume keyReleased events

Sean Dewar (1):
      Fix Entangle timer description typo

SoyChai (1):
      UI: Add a clear button (×) to IconTextField (#3451)

SquirrelHub (2):
      DiscordPlugin: Add Woodcutting Guild to Activities (#4813)
      Add Lumber Yard Fence to Agility Plugin (#4878)

Tomas Slusny (2):
      Fix adding of raid timer multiple times in Raids
      Fix FlatTextField unsafe swing access

psikoi (1):
      Fix exp tracker UI margin incosistency

takuyakanbr (2):
      time tracking: add empty case to overview tab
      time tracking: fix detection of state for seaweed patches
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-09-1.4.11-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-09-1.4.11-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.11 Release</title>
        <summary>Birdhouse timers, movable xp globes, and bug fixes</summary>
        <updated>2018-08-09T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The farming plugin has been renamed to the timer plugin and now includes timers,
stopwatches, and birdhouse timers. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/takuyakanbr">@takuyakanbr</a> for contributing this awesome
feature!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.11-Release/timer1.png" alt="timer1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.11-Release/timer2.png" alt="timer2"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.11-Release/timer3.png" alt="timer3"/></p>
<p>The RuneLite XP globes are now movable similar to other overlays:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.11-Release/globes.gif" alt="globes"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Add !cmb chat command</li>
<li>Add agility clickbox overlay to Werewolf course</li>
<li>Add tablet creation to idle notifier</li>
<li>Fix pest control and report button plugins which broke in the Monday game
update</li>
<li>Fix screen shake interfering with vertical camera</li>
<li>Add option to raids plugin to show scouter interface throughout the raid</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (9):
      Disable zoom extender when a cache overlay fails to load
      Fix applying default config to session settings
      modelviewer: fix some incorrect gl usage, add error logging
      modelviewer: fix zfighting of models
      item manager: assert item composition access is done from client thread
      ge plugin: fix accessing item composition from executor thread
      config service: update key name too when setting config
      chat commands: add !cmb command
      scripts: update for game update

Brady (2):
      Add missing shortcuts to trollheim (#4711)
      Move greater demon cannon spot to better location

Jaimy Smets (2):
      Add obstacles to Werewolf court
      Add tablet creation animation to idle notifier

Jordan Atwood (20):
      achievement diary plugin: Fix coal mining req
      chat commands plugin: Use consistent message check
      resources: Remove unused images
      SwingUtil: Fix grayscaleOffset to not modify alpha
      Add image utility class
      resources: Remove derivative images
      clan manager: Use Sprite IDs for rank badges
      plugins: Use shared clue arrow and reset images
      agility plugin: Use Item ID for arena timer
      clue scroll plugin: Use Item IDs for overlays
      death indicator plugin: Use Item IDs for overlays
      fight caves plugin: Use Sprite IDs for overlay images
      hiscores plugin: Remove duplicate skill icon images
      kingdom plugin: Use Item ID for overlay image
      puzzle solver plugin: Use Sprite ID for overlay image
      raids plugin: Use Sprite ID for raids timer
      screenshot plugin: Use Sprite ID for overlay image
      xp tracker plugin: Use shared image for icon
      ImageUtil: Add getResourceStreamFromClass method
      Remove unused @Slf4j annotations and imports

Kamiel (9):
      chat history: clear public chat when menu option is clicked
      item stats: fix tooltip not appearing when hovering over item
      menu entry swapper: fix last destination on arceuus fairy ring
      menu entry swapper: fix zanaris fairy ring not being recognized
      menu entry swapper: fix zanaris swap not working for PoH tree-ring combo
      player indicators: draw tile highlight on ABOVE_SCENE layer (#4629)
      Update chatbox widget IDs
      Update pest control widget IDs
      Update nightmare zone widget ID

Magic fTail (1):
      Add pharaoh&#39;s sceptres, Toxic staff of the dead, tome of fire item maps

Max Weber (4):
      mixins: Fix camera pitch relaxer not fully relaxing after a screen shake
      cache-client: Return failure to the handshake Future
      runelite-client: Make ItemManager&#39;s price update thread safe
      runelite-client: Always use the mapped price for items

Tomas Slusny (10):
      Add support for making XP globes moveable
      Use correct marker name when cancelling edit
      Add mappings for indexed script db
      Move isOverlayOutdated to IndexDatabase
      Account for linked item id, format tooltip
      Add Tournament world type
      Remove unnecessary headers from plugin panels
      Add null-check for game canvas
      Properly check for changing values in raids plugin
      Add setting to preserve scouter in raid

c01dc0ffee (1):
      Make DeathIndicatorPlugin use LocalPlayerDeath (#4745)

takuyakanbr (4):
      Convert farming tracker to time tracking plugin
      time tracking: add bird house tracker
      time tracking: add clock panel
      time tracking: add overview tab
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-02-1.4.10-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-08-02-1.4.10-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.10 Release</title>
        <summary>Loot tracker, minnows overlay, prayer bar flick helper and bug fixes</summary>
        <updated>2018-08-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A loot tracker plugin has been added which will be able to track your loot from:</p>
<ul>
<li>Monsters</li>
<li>Bosses (like Vorkath and Zulrah)</li>
<li>Clue scrolls</li>
<li>Chambers of Xeric</li>
<li>Theatre of Blood</li>
<li>Barrows Brothers</li>
<li>Players you PK (!)</li>
</ul>
<p>For now, all these data will be tracked only per-session and not persisted and there is only per-kill view,
but we are planning to extend both these areas in future. This plugin is disabled by default, so make sure
to enable it in settings under <strong>Loot tracker</strong>.</p>
<p>This feature is result of hard work of <a href="https://github.com/WooxSolo">@WooxSolo</a>, <a href="https://github.com/Adam-">@Adam-</a>,
<a href="https://github.com/TheStonedTurtle">@TheStonedTurtle</a> and <a href="https://github.com/Psikoi">@Psikoi</a>, so thank you all for
your great work on it:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/loottracker1.png" alt="loottracker1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/loottracker2.png" alt="loottracker2"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/loottracker3.png" alt="loottracker3"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/loottracker4.png" alt="loottracker4"/></p>
<p>Support for minnows timers has been added to the Fishing plugin which displays a countdown until the minnow spot will
move. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/jkybtw">@jkybtw</a> who contributed this feature.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/minnows.png" alt="minnows"/></p>
<p>The flicking helper in Prayer plugin has been extended to also display in prayer bar, if it is enabled, thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/forsco">@forsco</a>:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.10-Release/prayerbarflick.gif" alt="prayerbarflick"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Ungael (Vorkath) obstacles has been added to agility plugin</li>
<li>Meyerditch obstacles has been added to agility plugin</li>
<li>Fairy ring clues will now warn about missing spade from inventory</li>
<li>Lumbridge swamp emote clue now shows correct location</li>
<li>Loading of window sidebar has been fixed, now it should not mysteriously disappear anymore</li>
<li>Dig location for Barbarian Villag Hot&amp;Cold clue is now correct</li>
<li>Idle notifier now notify on crafting leather idle</li>
<li>Requirement for slaying an Abyssal Demon corrected in Achievement Diary
plugin</li>
<li>Fix tile overlay height when highlighting a tile next to the edge of a bridge</li>
<li>Add config for whether the killcount command is enabled</li>
<li>Fix minimap overlay dot overlay being slightly off</li>
<li>Crafting leather has been added to the idle notifier</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 18 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (12):
      perspective: fix worldToCanvas to convert from local to scene coords correctly
      Revert &quot;perspective: fix worldToCanvas to convert from local to scene coords correctly&quot;
      perspective: use less magic constants in getTileHeight
      Revert &quot;perspective: fix regression caused by 2599db2&quot;
      perspective: split tile height logic out of local to world
      perspective: fix getCanvasTileAreaPoly when getting tile next to a bridge
      perspective: fix checkstyle
      runelite-mixins: correct worldToCanvas arguments
      perspective: change worldToMinimap location calculation back
      fishing plugin: add minnows overlay
      fishing plugin: add position to config
      Add LootManager

Devin (1):
      kourend library plugin: Use correct enum naming convention

Jacob McElroy (1):
      Fix dig location of the West Barbarian Village H/C clue (#4524)

Jaimy Smets (1):
      Add alternative dragon pickaxes to emote clue

Jordan Atwood (23):
      item charge plugin: Use constant for checked string
      timers plugin: Use constants for checked strings
      Add color utility class
      notifier: Use ColorUtil functions
      chat message manager: Use ColorUtil functions
      widget menu option: Use ColorUtil functions
      achievement diary plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      boosts plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      friend notes plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      ground items plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      inventory tags plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      item prices plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      item stats plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      menu entry swapper plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      player indicators plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      puzzle solver plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      rune pouch plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      slayer plugin: Use ColorUtil functions
      achievement diary plugin: Fix Abyssal demon req
      achievement diary plugin: Fix Belladonna farming req
      achievement diary plugin: Fix waka canoe requirement
      clues: Fix Lumbridge swamp cave emote clue location
      agility: Add Ungael obstacles

Juul Damen (1):
      Add missing killcount command config (#4489)

Kristian Welsh (1):
      overlay util: adjust renderMinimapLocation for newer worldToMinimap

Magic fTail (3):
      TimerPlugin: Fix prayer enhance length
      Clarify wording of default log tracker message (#4602)
      Fix Theatre Of Blood InventoryID (#4608)

Max Weber (5):
      mixins: Prevent runScript from being called recursively
      runelite-client: Rename ClientThread::invokeLater to invoke
      runelite-client: Always call done after changed in ChatboxInptutManager
      fairyring: Always run scripts outside of chatbox input callbacks
      runelite-client: Make hotkeys run on KeyPressed

Michael Goodwin (3):
      Add Chambers Of Xeric and TOB inventories
      Add TOB varbits
      Add TOB widget ids

Mitch Barnett (1):
      Add Meyerditch to agility obstacles (#4538)

Su-Shing Chen (1):
      Fix Assembler tests when autocrlf=true on Windows

Tomas Slusny (12):
      Fix loading of chat colors on startup
      Use consistent API and order for title and sides
      Add isTab property to title buttons
      Merge PluginToolbar and TitleToolbar together
      Add simple info log with startup time
      Properly use javax.inject.Provider
      Pack and show frame only after properties update
      Fix NPE when trying to draw null names
      Add null check for Perspective.getCanvasTextLoc
      Account for plane in TileObject canvas location
      Fix FontManagerTest package
      Fix getCanvasTileAreaPoly ArrayOutOfBounds

WooxSolo (1):
      Add NPC death animations

aquivers (1):
      Add spade requirement reminder to fairy ring clues (#4585)

forsco (1):
      Add flick helper to player bar (#3882)

psikoi (1):
      Add loot tracker plugin

rswindows10 (2):
      Add support for crafting leather idle notification (#4600)
      Remove comment regarding crafting leather (#4601)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-26-1.4.9-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-26-1.4.9-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.9 Release</title>
        <summary>Movable minimap and xptracker, achievement diary skill requirements, and bug fixes</summary>
        <updated>2018-07-26T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The minimap and xp tracker can now be moved by holding alt:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.9-Release/movable-widgets.gif" alt="movable-widgets"/></p>
<p>An achievement diary plugin was added which shows skill requirements on each
task in the diaries:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.9-Release/diary.png" alt="diary"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix minimap overlays drawing on the minimap when it was hidden</li>
<li>Fix minimap plugin to be able to hide the minimap on &#39;bottom line&#39; side stones
arrangement</li>
<li>Fix !kc not working in private messages</li>
<li>Rewrite ge plugin alt+click search to work more reliably on more interfaces,
such as the inventory when in the grand exchange.</li>
<li>Add abyssal sire stun timer</li>
<li>Fix opponent info plugin hiscore lookup on seasonal deadman worlds</li>
<li>Fix menaphite emote clue requirements</li>
<li>Fix XP tracker to no longer track skills while they are not being trained</li>
<li>Fix XP tracker to track past virtual level 126, up to 200m</li>
<li>Add &quot;show exact value&quot; option to bank value plugin</li>
<li>Move banana plantation clue out of tree</li>
<li>Fix height of ground items</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (8):
      runelite-api: add fixed minimap widgets
      mixins: only update render parent of nested widget if widget would have been rendererd
      mixins: optimize widget isHidden and getParent
      perspective: account for minimap being hidden or moved in worldToMiniMap
      Add private message input event and add !kc to chatcommands for private messages
      Merge runelite-scripts into runelite-client
      Add achievement diary plugin
      cache: fix assembler to set correct switch table index

Bert De Geyter (1):
      Render abyss rift portals as soon as visible (#3841)

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      ge plugin: rewrite alt-click searching

John Pettenger (1):
      timers plugin: add abyssal sire stun timer

Jordan Atwood (2):
      opponent info plugin: Fix SDMM hiscore lookup
      clues: Fix menaphite emote requirements

Joshua Filby (1):
      fix: use the supplied actor to check against in isInteractingWith

Kamiel (1):
      perspective: fix regression caused by 2599db2

Levi (2):
      Check for skill being trained while ticking change (#4469)
      Fix level 126 next goal to be max XP (200,000,000) instead of -1 xp

Magic fTail (1):
      bank value plugin: add option to display exact value

Max Weber (5):
      runelite-client: Consume hotkeys in HotkeyListener
      runelite-client: Handle releasing modifiers first correctly
      cluescrolls: Move banana plantation clue out of tree
      cluescrolls: Add description to map clues
      mixins: Don&#39;t post mouse events that have already been posted

Timo van Veenendaal (2):
      Inventory viewer: make padding between items same as in inventory.
      Inventory viewer: Fix vertical spacing of items to match inventory.

Tomas Slusny (20):
      Add support for mod public chat to ChatCommands
      Add JMod clan member rank
      Add new WidgetIDs for minimap
      Use correct widget when hiding minimap
      Move private methods to bottom of minimap plugin
      Hide only inside of minimap but not logout
      Follow GitHub templates for bug report and issue (#4205)
      Move rs-client related classes to own package
      Allow RS loading classes to be used with Guice
      Inject and load RS client and applet through Guice
      Send launch properties around as bound constants
      Remove recursive dependency on RuneLite
      Properly load configuration when showing ClientUI
      Move Discord and EventBus after ClientUI
      Add support for resetting the detached overlays
      Use Overlay#getBounds for getting correct bounds
      Add experience tracker widget WidgetInfo
      Add support for RS movable widgets
      Update frame config when needed
      Propagate height to ground items

aquivers (1):
      Add more chat !kc abbreviations (#4372)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-19-1.4.8-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-19-1.4.8-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.8 Release</title>
        <summary>Fairy Ring search, XP tracker pausing and RoW !kc support</summary>
        <updated>2018-07-19T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>You can now filter through the Fairy Ring travel log while having the <code>configure</code> interface open. (Contributed by <a href="https://github.com/Abextm">@Abextm</a>)</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.8-Release/fairy-ring-filter.png" alt="fairy-ring-filter"/></p>
<p>The XP tracker now can be paused either on logout or after a configurable time period. (Contributed by <a href="https://github.com/LeviSchuck">@LeviSchuck</a>)</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.8-Release/xp-tracker-pause.png" alt="xp-tracker-pause"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Reading the Ring of Wealth boss log now updates the !kc command kill counts</li>
<li>Theatre of Blood rewards are now automatically screenshotted</li>
<li>Hunter level-ups are now properly screenshotted</li>
<li>Screenshots taken in Deadman mode now reside in separate directory</li>
<li>The King percival clue now also contains informations about nearest fairy ring</li>
<li>Added Mounted Mythical Cape to the skill calculator</li>
<li>Fix slayer plugin sometimes highlighting nonexistent NPCs</li>
<li>Fix bug with ground items not always showing ground items</li>
<li>Cacti in farming plugin now work correctly</li>
<li>Untradeable versions of Sanguinesti Staff and Scythe now calculate GE value correctly</li>
<li>Fix alignment of xpdrops when sprites are configured to be hidden</li>
<li>Fix hiscore autocomplete when typing too quickly</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (28):
      Revert &quot;command manager: post events to immediate eventbus&quot;
      Revert &quot;plugin manager: register plugins with immediate event bus&quot;
      Revert &quot;runelite-client: add immediate event bus&quot;
      Add chatbox input listener and use for chatbox input event
      slayer plugin: fix parsing points and streaks with commas
      chat commands: add test
      chat commands: loosen regex for boss names
      runelite-scripts: add bank search script
      Add matches found to bank tag search dialog message
      chat commands: count barrows chests too
      screenshot plugin: move level up and quest screenshots to after widget load
      screenshot plugin: rename &quot;raids&quot; to &quot;chambers of xeric&quot;
      screenshot plugin: fix hunter level up screenshots
      config invocation handler: don&#39;t set config values if already set
      hiscore plugin: fix race with inserting next character with autocomplete
      slayer plugin: clear highlighted targets on login
      ground items: scan entire scene for items not just ones within range
      Add item spawn events
      grounditems: rewrite to use item spawn events
      region tile manager: send item spawns at plugin start
      agility plugin: use item events
      mta plugin: use item events
      Remove item layer changed event
      Remove MAZE_GUARDIAN_MOVING npc id
      prayer plugin: update zamorak robe itemids
      xp drop plugin: fix alignment of xpdrops when hiding skill icons
      xp drop plugin: add positions for config
      Add item despawn events when ground items is nulled

Aquivers (1):
      Add fairy ring information to King Percival clue #4344

JHPinto (1):
      Slayer overlay use query idEquals, use consts (#4322)

Jordan (1):
      timers plugin: Use item and sprite IDs for timers

Jordan Atwood (5):
      screenshot plugin: Use separate directory for DMM
      text: Fix removeTags for isolated &lt; and &gt; chars
      timers plugin: Reduce visibilities
      Remove freeze timer on Vorkath Zombified spawn death
      clue scroll plugin: Remove useless null check

Levi Schuck (2):
      Add dimming UI to progress bar
      Add feature to pause skill timers on logout or after idle period

Magic fTail (5):
      Update dialog widget ids from game update
      chat commands: add raids pattern
      ScreenshotPlugin: fix naming of event
      chat commands: update boss kc from boss log
      screenshot plugin: capture ToB rewards

Max Weber (8):
      farmingtracker: Fix cactus implementation
      cache: Relax label name constraints
      Rename Region to Scene
      runelite-api: Update autogenerated ID files to 171-7
      runelite-client: Allow ChatboxInputManager to callback early
      Add API to create new widgets
      runelite-client: Add fairy ring search to fairy ring plugin
      devtools: Show index on dynamic widgets in the tree

Qatell (1):
      Fixed objects of variable width and length from being positioned incorrectly on the map.

Tomas Slusny (5):
      Remove investigate menu entry swap
      Add Sanguinesti Staff to ItemMapping
      Add mapping for Scythe to ItemMappings
      Remove unused import from RSTileMixin
      Fix camels type in varrock museum quiz

Tyler Hardy (1):
      runelite-api: Add/Correct fairy ring panel widgets

forsco (1):
      Add mythical cape and teak kitchen table to skill calc (#4341)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-12-1.4.7-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-12-1.4.7-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.7 Release</title>
        <summary>Kill count command, prayer bars, and Tears of Guthix plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-07-12T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A kill count command was added which can share your kill count with other
players who are also using RuneLite. The client must first observe you
getting a kill count message to record the kill count. It can not read
the kill counts off of the boss log in game yet, but maybe that will come soon.</p>
<p>Note that as the kill count data is sent from the client it is trusted and is not
difficult for someone to fake.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.7-Release/kc.png" alt="kc"/></p>
<p>The prayer plugin now can show a prayer bar, below your hitpoints bar, showing
how much prayer you have left.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.7-Release/prayerbar.png" alt="prayerbar"/></p>
<p>A Tears of Guthix plugin was added which displays time remaining on the blue streams:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.7-Release/tog.png" alt="tog"/></p>
<p>The special attack orb now indicates when you have special attack enabled.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.7-Release/specorb.gif" alt="specorb"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Add broad arrows to the fletching skill calculator</li>
<li>XP drop plugin will now center text of XP if skill icons are hidden</li>
<li>Fix agility plugin counting laps on the agility pyramid</li>
<li>The runecraft plugin can now send a notification when rune pouches degrade</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>Adam (12):
      slayer plugin: don&#39;t lowercase task names
      slayer plugin: add spiritual creatures, and fix a few other tasks
      slayer plugin: move target highlight building to use events
      Add killcount command
      Add getVarpValue and setVarpValue to RSClientMixin and Client
      runecraft plugin: add positions for config options
      runelite-scripts: check length check in chatbox input
      runelite-client: add immediate event bus
      chat commands: fix kc command in friends chat
      plugin manager: register plugins with immediate event bus
      command manager: post events to immediate eventbus
      widgetid: update barrows interface ids

Forsco (1):
      Add broad arrows to fletching skill calc

Infinitay (2):
      Add &quot;getvarp&quot;, &quot;setvarp&quot;, &quot;getvarb&quot;, &quot;setvarb&quot; dev-tool chat commands
      Add stream progress overlay for Tears of Guthix

Isha Dijcks (1):
      runecraft plugin: add a notification when a runepouch degrades

Jordan Atwood (9):
      clues: Fix SW-of-deserted-keep hot-cold location
      xp drop plugin: Move text to use hidden icon&#39;s space
      xp tracker plugin: Reduce visibilities
      xp tracker plugin: Remove WorldClient usages
      agility plugin: Remove unused variables and imports
      agility plugin: Reduce visibility of classes
      agility plugin: Fix course spellings
      agility plugin: Check for endpoints only when defined
      agility plugin: Add pyramid end point

Nathen Sample (1):
      Add prayer bonus for suffering R and RI

Oliver Atkinson (1):
      Fix #4101 - Add swap options for Decant

Tomas Slusny (11):
      Rename prayer tooltip option
      Add prayer bar to prayer plugin
      Add api mappings for oculus orb normal speed
      Set oculus speed to 36 (x3) in DevTools
      Add spec active indicator to spec orb
      Do not explode on illegal unicode chat in settings
      Fix &quot;verxik&quot; typo in ChatCommandsPlugin
      Add more !kc abbreviations
      Check if infobox can render in InfoBoxOverlay
      Add debuff/buff change indicators
      Add support for preserving boost indicators
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-05-1.4.6-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-07-05-1.4.6-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.6 Release</title>
        <summary>Lightbox and Varrock Museum quiz solver, config panel tags and favorites, Discord bosses &amp; minigames</summary>
        <updated>2018-07-05T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A lightbox solver plugin was added which tells you the pattern to solve lightboxes after
observing a few of the switches. Contributed by <a href="https://github.com/Adam-">@Adam-</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/lightboxsolver.png" alt="lightboxsolver"/></p>
<p>A helper for Varrock Museum Quiz was added as well that highlights correct answer to
questions in Varrock Museum basement. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/vikke1234">@vikke1234</a>
who contributed this feature.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/varrockmuseumsolver.png" alt="varrockmuseumsolver"/></p>
<p>The configuration panel was significantly improved thanks to big contribution from
<a href="https://github.com/takuyakanbr">@takuyakanbr</a>. Some of the improvements are:</p>
<ul>
<li>Each plugin now has a short description when hovered</li>
<li>Each plugin now has tags that will make plugins easier to search for</li>
<li>Plugins can now be pinned to the top of the panel (a new star icon was added next to each plugin name
that when clicked will pin the config option to top)</li>
<li>Search bar in configuration panel will now always stay on top</li>
<li>Each configuration page for plugins now have back and on/off buttons at the top of panel</li>
</ul>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/configbackbutton.png" alt="configbackbutton"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/configfavorites.png" alt="configfavorites"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/configtags.png" alt="configtags"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/configtooltip.png" alt="configtooltip"/></p>
<p>Thanks to another awesome contribution from <a href="https://github.com/PandahRS">@PandahRS</a> who spent
a lot of time manually mapping a lot of RuneScape surface to regions, the Discord plugin now has
a lot of new features, including display of <strong>city</strong> you are in, <strong>dungeon</strong> you are currently
exploring, <strong>boss</strong> you are currently fighting and even <strong>minigame</strong> you are currently playing.</p>
<p>Due to privacy reasons, these new location-based features are disabled in any PVP scenario, such
as PVP worlds, High Risk worlds, DMM and Seasonal DMM worlds.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/discord1.png" alt="discord1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.4.6-Release/discord2.png" alt="discord2"/></p>
<p>In addition to the highlighted features, there have been several other improvements and bugfixes this release:</p>
<ul>
<li>!total, !clues and !lvl commands now properly show ranks based on account types</li>
<li>Plenty of new food types have been added to Item Stats plugin</li>
<li>SOTD timer now properly works also for SOTL</li>
<li>Obstacles for Agility Pyramid entrance and Morytania pirate ship have been added to Agility plugin</li>
<li>Al-Kharid lap counter has been fixed</li>
<li>XP tracker now shows dots instead of commas to follow OSRS style of displaying numbers</li>
<li>Fishing plugin now supports all types of eels</li>
<li>Bug with inventory tagger plugin showing items with different models depending on the quantity
incorrectly have been fixed</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (8):
      runelite-api: make HashTable a generic
      Calculate and store widget parent id and position when the interfaces are rendered
      Revert &quot;Add ironman status and AccountType to API&quot;
      chat commands: fix to use exiting accounttype api
      agility plugin: fix Al Kharid lap counter
      puzzle solver: add lightbox solver
      chat commands: store kill counts in config
      Change Widget::parentId behavior to work again if the widget hasn&#39;t been drawn yet

Damen (2):
      Fix Dark Crab req lvl in skill calculator (#4071)
      Prevent cannonball count conflicting with health bars (#2857)

Gamer1120 (1):
      Fix hiscore lookup for ironman in chat commands

JHPinto (1):
      slayer plugin: move item count overlay checks to render

Jeremy Plsek (2):
      item manager: add item outline caching
      inventory tags: use item manager for outlines

Jordan (1):
      Ignore level goals which have been passed (#3805)

Jordan Atwood (17):
      item stats plugin: Add Edible seaweed
      chat color: Fix description typo
      Update Veng Other / Energy Transfer animation ID
      Add Vengeance Other graphic ID
      timers plugin: Check for Vengeance Other graphic
      item stats: Add missing RFD foods
      fishing plugin: Add cave eel and slimy eel spots
      agility plugin: Add Lumbridge swamp cave shortcuts
      item stats plugin: Add field ration
      grand exchange plugin: Fix error message typos
      grand exchange plugin: Clear render on empty string
      item stats plugin: Fix import ordering
      item stats plugin: Fix Zamorak brew stat changes
      skill calculator: Fix combined items with decimals
      item stats: Add negative attack bonus to wines
      clues: Fix Cap&#39;n Izzy No-Beard anagram clue
      agility plugin: Add pyramid entrance obstacles

Kamiel (1):
      screen-markers: fix graphical bug

Magic fTail (1):
      AgilityPlugin: Add obstacles north of pirate ship (#4084)

Max Weber (3):
      mixins: Don&#39;t show siblings in dynamic widget&#39;s child lists
      farmingtracker: Correct several patch timings
      itemstats: Add variable healing food

Nathen Sample (1):
      Represent decimals as .&#39;s not ,&#39;s (#4059)

PandahRS (5):
      Make skilling activity configurable in Discord
      Add bosses to Discord plugin
      Add cities to Discord plugin
      Add dungeons to discord plugin
      Add minigames to Discord plugin

Tomas Slusny (7):
      Add ironman status and AccountType to API
      Make SOTD/SOTL timer use chat messsage
      Return preferredSize.width from TitleComponent
      Make !clues command respect account type
      Add logging of presence to DiscordService
      Make Discord plugin more extensible/support region
      Reset Discord state if now &gt; updated + timeout

Viktor Horsmanheimo (2):
      Add widget IDs for the varrock museum quiz
      Add Varrock museum quiz solver

takuyakanbr (5):
      Add description and tags fields to PluginDescriptor
      config panel: change plugin search to use plugin name + tags
      config panel: add ability to pin plugins to the top
      config panel: keep search bar at the top while scrolling Add back and toggle buttons at the top of plugin configuration pages
      Replace fields in ConfigGroup with a single `value` field
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-28-1.4.5-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-28-1.4.5-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.5 Release</title>
        <summary>Inventory tags, opponent comparison, inventory viewer, and corporeal beast plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-06-28T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>An inventory tag plugin was added which lets you tag items in your inventory,
which then get outlined a specific color. Contributed by
<a href="https://github.com/kulershk">@kulers</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.5-Release/inventorytags.png" alt="inventorytags"/></p>
<p>The opponent info plugin now has an option to show and compare the stats of an
opponent you interact with. Contributed by
<a href="https://github.com/nightfirecat">@Nightfirecat</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.5-Release/playercomparison.png" alt="playercomparison"/></p>
<p>An inventory viewer was added by <a href="https://github.com/jplsek">@jplsek</a> which lets
you overlay a view of your inventory:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.5-Release/inventoryviewer.png" alt="inventoryviewer"/></p>
<p>Finally, a corporeal beast plugin was added:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.5-Release/corp.png" alt="corp"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix animation smoother with interpolating rotation frames</li>
<li>Fix animation smoother to not smooth hellhound defence animation</li>
<li>Fix agility plugin to not reset arena timer when falling from obstacles</li>
<li>Fix fight cave plugin to work more reliably</li>
<li>Fix price of tentacle tridents</li>
<li>Add informative dialog for when the client is outdated due to game updates</li>
<li>Add configuration setting for chat commands clear chat keyboard shortcuts</li>
<li>The screenshot plugin now has a configurable hotkey for screenshots</li>
<li>Add Battle staffs to the idle notifier</li>
<li>Add !clues chat command</li>
<li>Add timer for stamina mixes</li>
<li>Add (slayer) assignment to menu swapper</li>
<li>Fix binding necklaces charges to reset when the necklace is destroyed</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>AWPH-I (1):
      Add inventory viewer plugin

Adam (20):
      runelite-client: add outdated dialog
      runescape-api: remove no longer used annotations
      Add logback-parent to dependency management and use a consistent slf4j version everywhere
      Add interface representing all callbacks the client does, and convert mixins to use it
      hooks: dispose graphics after using
      actor mixin: fix getInteracting when index is 65535
      Add interacting changed event
      chat message manager: set default colors for GAME messages
      Add corporeal beast plugin
      modelviewer: add basic animation support
      devtools: add transform command
      animation smoothing: do not interpolate to angle 0
      Revert &quot;animation smoothing: do not interpolate to angle 0&quot;
      animation smoothing: don&#39;t interpolate hellhound defence animation
      chat commands: add config setting for chat clear shortcuts
      cache: rename additional npc definition fields
      queries: replace some isHidden checks with isSelfHidden
      hiscore client: check response code of hiscore lookups
      opponent info: move interacting logic to plugin and use interacting changed event
      opponent info: add player comparison overlay

Dennis (1):
      animation smoothing: fix angle bounds for rotation

HSJ-OSRS (2):
      Add battlestaff crafting to AnimationID
      Add battlestaff crafting to idle notifier

James (1):
      Show correct text for master clue command (#3989)

JavaLeg (1):
      chat commands: add clues command

Jordan Atwood (3):
      Fix &quot;West of Barbarian Village&quot; hot-cold location
      Fix East of Brimhaven fruit tree hot-cold location
      timers plugin: Create timer for stamina mixes

Kamiel (1):
      npc indicators: fix consuming tag menu clicks on non-npcs

Max Weber (4):
      runelite-client: Add Keybind class for configs to save and set hotkeys
      screenshot plugin: Allow hotkey to be changed from insert
      kourendlibrary: Make hiding the navbutton optional
      runelite-client: Add a equals implementation to Keybind

Nathen (1):
      Update library plugin encapsulation

Nathen Sample (1):
      Update prayer plugin encapsulation (#3962)

ScottMCarr (1):
      agility plugin: do not update arena timer when there is no hint arrow

Su-Shing Chen (1):
      agilityShortcutLocation: Fix SE Karamja agility marker

Tomas Slusny (24):
      Center stretched fixed mode horizontally
      Move onActorHitsplat to mixins
      Move menuOpened to mixins
      Move updateNpcs call to mixins
      Move focusGained to mixins
      Move focusLost to mixins
      Move postItemComposition to mixins
      Move setMessage to mixins
      Move projectileMoved to mixins
      Move addChatMessage to mixins
      Move graphicsObjectCreated to mixins
      Move drawAboveOverheads call to mixins
      Move drawRegion call to mixins
      Move clientMainLoop to mixins
      Move menuActionHook to mixins
      Add documentation for Hooks
      Remove Age menu entry swapping
      Move shift-click config to top of menu swapper
      Update documentation for Callbacks interface
      Add new toBufferedOutline method to SpritePixels
      Add inventory tagging plugin
      Remove title from corp panel
      Make Fight Cave plugin more accurate
      Fix price of tentacle tridents

Trees (1):
      Menu Swapper - Add Age/Assignment

honeyhoney (2):
      Added destroy item widgets
      Fixed binding necklace charges not being reset when necklace is destroyed
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-21-1.4.4-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-21-1.4.4-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.4 Release</title>
        <summary>Mage training arena plugin, prayer potion indicator, and preserve prayer tracking</summary>
        <updated>2018-06-21T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A Mage Training Arena was added from
<a href="https://github.com/Jasper-ketelaar">@Jasper Ketelaar</a> which can solve
telekinetic mazes, and deduce alchemy room rotations from discovery of items in
it.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.4-Release/mta.png" alt="mta"/></p>
<p>The prayer plugin now indicates when you can drink a prayer potion to get the
full effect by flashing the prayer orb. It also has a new tooltip which shows
your current prayer bonus and approximation on how much longer your prayer
points will last.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.4-Release/prayer.gif" alt="prayer"/></p>
<p>The boosts plugin now takes into account the preserve prayer when showing when
the next stat drain takes place.</p>
<p>The grand exchange plugin can now show the &quot;actively traded&quot; OSBuddy price on
the grand exchange interface now, if enabled.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.4-Release/osbprice.png" alt="osbprice"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix infobox overlay resetting its position after each client restart.</li>
<li>Add dodgy necklace charge counter and notification to item charges plugin</li>
<li>Fix attack styles plugin not correctly hiding staff of the dead defence style</li>
<li>Made tagging NPCs no longer interrupt actions</li>
<li>Hide Kourend Library navigation button when not in the library</li>
<li>Fix Shilo Village stepping stones agilty marker</li>
<li>Add option to highlight tiles under ground items</li>
<li>Re-add ability to show hidden items on right click menu, with a toggle this
time</li>
<li>Added a link to the wiki to the info panel</li>
<li>More clue fixes</li>
<li>Fix icons of onyx items in skill calculator</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<pre><code>4th8 (1):
      skill calculator: fix item id for some zenyte and onyx items

Adam (20):
      Revert &quot; Fix NMZ points overlay appearing in the KBD instance lair&quot;
      ground items: default highlight over value to 0
      ground items: rename highlight &gt; value key to reset the defaults
      ground items: don&#39;t recolor menu if hidden
      ground items: remove unnecessary copy of collected ground items
      examine plugin: update object examine id unpacking
      runelite-client: close properties input stream
      world map plugin: add missing break after agility shortcuts/tooltips case
      overlay util: mark explicit fallthrough in transformPosition
      demonic gorillas plugin: remove unused variable
      config invocation handler: replace args with literal null
      screenshot plugin: fix unsafe multithreaded usage of DateFormat
      runelite-client: remove various redundant null checks
      timers plugin: fix sotd timer removal logic
      prayer plugin: add dose indicator
      runelite-client: use new bulk item price api
      http-service: crawl tradable item prices instead of queueing on demand
      item charges plugin: add dodgy necklace
      attack styles: add defensive casting to weapon types for staffs
      http-service: switch json serializer to jackson

AeonLucid (1):
      ge plugin: add OSB actively traded price

Alexsuperfly (1):
      Preserve prayer tracking in boost timer (#3530)

Harry (1):
      Improve and cleanup code in runelite-client (#3859)

Jasper Ketelaar (1):
      runelite-client: add mage training arena plugin

Jonathan Beaudoin (1):
      Add tooltip to absorption panel

Jordan Atwood (8):
      Add Staff of the Dead timer
      Prevent NPC tagging from interrupting actions
      Fix ancient cavern emote clue location
      Fix south-of-mausoleum hot-cold clue location
      Fix Slayer Tower emote clue
      Fix Al Kharid mine hot-cold clue location
      Fix South of Jiggig hot-cold clue location
      Fix stepping stone object IDs east of Shilo Village

Lars (1):
      CONTRIBUTING.md - Provide link to coding conventions

Matthew Smith (1):
      Toggle confirmation on exit (#3834)

Max Weber (6):
      runelite-client: Test Overlay equality
      runelite-client: Prevent recursion when chat notifier notifies to chat
      cache: consolidate ID class printing and split ObjectID
      Update autogenerated ID files
      runelite-client: remove unused import in DemonicGorillaOverlay
      kourendlibrary: Hide navbutton when not in the library

Seth (2):
      agilityShortcutLocation: Fix shilo village agility marker
      configPanel: remove tooltips for JTextArea

Tememexas (1):
      Add option to highlight tiles under ground items (#3895)

Tomas Slusny (16):
      Disable camera zoom by default
      Use Object.equals for Overlays
      Fix overlay collection modification checks
      Consider anything with GE &gt; 0 as tradeable too
      Ignore highlights when value is set to 0 (disable)
      Make hidden items color configurable
      Reduce code duplicity in resetOverlay method
      Fix loading of core overlay properties
      Mark InfoboxOverlay as singleton
      Fix UnsupportedOperationException in ground items
      Change ground items box size from 6 px to 8 px
      Reload overlay settings on plugin change
      Disable OSB prices by default
      Fix ground item swapped price values
      Optional support for recoloring right-click menu
      Fix ground marker plugin layer

psikoi (2):
      Added boolean onSelectedEvent to Material Tabs
      Refactor Hiscore EndPoints to Material Tab

raqes (1):
      Add wiki link to info panel
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-14-1.4.3-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-14-1.4.3-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.3 Release</title>
        <summary>Blast mine plugin, chat highlights and notifications, and resizable infoboxes</summary>
        <updated>2018-06-14T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A blast mine plugin was added which keeps track of lit dynamite charges, as well
as which stage the rock is in.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.3-Release/blastmine.png" alt="blastmine"/></p>
<p>A chat notifications plugin was added which can underscore your name when spoken
in public chat, as well as optionally send you notifications for trade, duel,
and other chat messages.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.3-Release/chatnotif.png" alt="chatnotif"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.3-Release/chatnotif2.png" alt="chatnotif2"/></p>
<p>A Crystal Math Labs plugin was added which, when enabled, automatically updates
your stats on CML whenever you log out.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>ctrl+w and backspace can now be used to delete the last word and the entire
line from the chatbox input, respectively</li>
<li>Add public chat friend name color in chat color config</li>
<li>The boosts plugin can now notify you when your boost gets low</li>
<li>Add Isafdar and Jatizso fishing spots to fishing plugin</li>
<li>Remove &#39;Actions left&#39; and &#39;Xp per hour&#39; from Xp Globes when Xp Tracker is disabled</li>
<li>Add fungicide spray to item stats plugin</li>
<li>The ground items plugin can now grey hidden items from the take menu</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (13):
      xtea plugin: batch xteas on gamestate change event
      Remove map region changed event
      Add gson to dependency management
      Update gson to 2.8.5
      http-service: import spring boot dependencies in dependency management
      travis: remove old secrets
      travis: remove old discord notification [ci skip]
      Add public chat friend name color in chat color config
      Fix genie cryptic clue to display proper requirements
      overlay renderer: bound overlays position to viewport at render time instead of at config load time
      runelite-api: add setVar for setting varclientstr
      item controller: expose bulk item prices
      chat commands: alow clearing words and chat with ctrl w/backspace

Arman (1):
      Adds notification when boost gets low

Chris Jimenez (1):
      Small contributing.md clarification

Hydrox6 (7):
      Fix &quot;Clan Channel Name&quot; typo, fix capitalisation (#3671)
      Make Color config options show their colour instead of &quot;Pick a color&quot; (#3583)
      [chat-color] Add support for Public Chat from Mods
      Clean up the Examine Colour loading
      Fix JColorChooser text not updating properly
      Fix NMZ points overlay appearing in the KBD instance lair
      runelite-client: add chat notifications plugin

Jordan Atwood (1):
      Add Jatizso fishing spots to fishing plugin

Marshall Briggs (1):
      Remove &#39;Actions left&#39; and &#39;Xp per hour&#39; from Xp Globes when Xp Tracker is disabled

Max Weber (6):
      runelite-api: Correct actor documentation
      runelite-client: Don&#39;t fail on invalid config values.
      runelite-client: add detached camera devtool
      runelite-client: Make OverlayManager thread safe
      runelite-client: Use an ArrayList to store overlays
      runelite-client: Allow new screenmarkers to be created

Mitchell Kovacs (4):
      Reworked Jewellery Charge to item charge.
      item charges: add charge warning threshold color configuration
      Moved the watering can overlay from tithe farming plugin to item charge plugin.
      Add counter for fungicide spray #3727

SieBrum (1):
      Add CrystalMathLabs plugin

Tim Granata (1):
      Add Isafdar dense forest agility boxes north of Tyras Camp (#3731)

Timmy-Jim (2):
      Move BAKED_POTATO to 4 HP healing food (#3724)
      Add Isafdar fishing spots

Tomas Slusny (14):
      Remove auto-expanding from PanelComponent
      Show GE and HA only when showing both prices
      Add mappings for isTradeable to ItemComposition
      Add option to always draw untradeable items
      Remove 4th invalid state from ground boxes
      Add full item name clickboxes
      Add highlight &gt; value, merge hide &lt; ge and ha
      Split OverlayRenderer logic to OverlayManager
      Make plugins work with new OverlayManager
      Add support for wrapping to PanelComponent
      Add support for preferred location to Panel
      Change InfoBoxOverlay to use PanelComponent
      Change the default size of infoboxes to be smaller
      Add support for configurable infobox size

Unmoon (1):
      Add blast mine plugin

WooxSolo (1):
      Fix demonic gorilla overlay position on fixed screen

drivfe (1):
      Fix combined action slot not updating when an input field was changed
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-07-1.4.2-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-06-07-1.4.2-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.2 Release</title>
        <summary>Respawn timers, death indicator plugin, prayer indicators</summary>
        <updated>2018-06-07T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The NPC indicators plugin now has an option to show respawn times for tagged
NPCS. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/WooxSolo">@WooxSolo</a> for his work on this.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.2-Release/respawn.png" alt="respawn"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/DannysPVM">@DannysPVM</a> added a death indicator plugin which
remembers where you&#39;ve died last, and on what world.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.2-Release/deathindicators.png" alt="deathindicator"/></p>
<p>The prayer flicking plugin was renamed to the prayer plugin - and now shows
prayer indicator infoboxes, from <a href="https://github.com/raqes">@raqes</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.2-Release/prayerindicator.png" alt="prayindicator"/></p>
<p>The full screen mode added in last weeks update was removed as it is not working
for some users and getting their client stuck in a nonworking state. We may add
it back in the future if we can make it work better.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The screenshot plugin now screenshots pvp kills and pet drops</li>
<li>A &#39;Reset others&#39; option was added to the xp tracker panel</li>
<li>A Charge timer was added</li>
<li>Fix Callisto and Venenatis boss timers from previous release</li>
<li>Fix regen plugin showing when orb is hidden</li>
<li>Added Zeah fishing spots to fishing plugin</li>
<li>Add dragonfire-charged items to untradeable item mappings</li>
<li>Fix expeditious bracelet charge tracking, which was broke last release</li>
<li>Add support for swapping all options on the house portal to the menu entry
swapper</li>
<li>Show RuneLite launcher version in the info panel</li>
<li>Add bake pie and string jewellery to idle notifier</li>
<li>Fix rare crash when drawing clickboxes</li>
</ul>
<p>Additionally, there were clue fixes from Jordan Atwood, StanleyMole, and Trig.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 26 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (25):
      perspective: do not remove culled faces from clickbox calculation
      chat color config: set default color for examine highlight
      Fix prayer enumation order back to the order the prayers are in game
      chat message manager: set default colors for examine
      hooks: move combat info callback to actor mixin
      Flag npc as dead when their health ratio hits 0
      runelite-client: update to use isDead
      pom: update rs.version
      runelite-mixins: once again reset menu on widget close
      Rename CONTRRIBUTING.md -&gt; CONTRIBUTING.md
      Fix null names for quest objects in cryptic clues
      config invocation handler: fix setting config values to null
      config manager: support Instant
      runelite-client: add death indicator plugin
      config manager: only apply default config from methods which read configuration
      antidrag: remove unused config setter
      death indicators: only set death mark after respawning in a known respawn location
      death indicator: move location check to after respawn
      death indicator: use animation to detect death
      Revert &quot;Merge pull request #3192 from deathbeam/add-support-for-fullscreen&quot;
      clientui: reimport ExpandResizeType from fullscreen revert
      screenshot plugin: capitalize pet messages constant
      screenshot plugin: screenshot pvp kills
      info panel: use revision number from client
      npc scene overlay: fix respawn time

Evan Sloan (1):
      Add reset others to XpPanel right click menu

Gert de Pagter (1):
      Use github issue templates

Hydrox6 (7):
      Add Charge Timer
      Fix Callisto and Venenatis Boss Timers using the incorrect ID
      Reorder updateConfig to match TimerConfig
      Add support for Clan Chat Info highlights for the Raids Plugin
      Add default highlight for Game Messages to fix Daily Task message colour
      Fix Charge timer showing with every teleport
      Remove Charge Timer when the effect ends

Infinitay (1):
      Add hyperlinks to project layout in README (#3509)

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      regen plugin: don&#39;t show regen if widget is hidden

Jordan (2):
      Reword Dad hot-cold clue hint (#3513)
      Fix McGrubor and Cow pen hot-cold locations (#3603)

Jordan Atwood (3):
      Fix &quot;The hand ain&#39;t listening.&quot; clue step
      Add missing Zeah fishing spots
      Fix Guard Vemmeldo anagram clue location

Juuso Lapinlampi (1):
      Fix spelling of Taverley

Kamiel (1):
      Allow screenmarker resizing below base point

Lars (2):
      Fix typo in BarrowsPlugin (Spanwed to Spawned)
      Update tooltip for Grand Exchange Panel Icon to &quot;Grand Exchange&quot; (#3618)

Magic fTail (2):
      Add dragonfire-charged armour item mappings
      screenshot plugin: screenshot receiving pet

Max Weber (1):
      runelite-client: Require assertions when developer mode is on

Reasel (1):
      Add Tile location tooltip option to dev tools. Remove extra empty line.

Ruben Amendoeira (1):
      Remove Skill Calc unused code (#3568)

Seth (1):
      slayer plugin: fix expeditious regex pattern

Snakk (1):
      menu entry swapper: add options for house portal

StanleyMole (1):
      Fix TzHaar and Castle Draken emote clues

Tomas Slusny (5):
      Change tithe farm to use PieComponent
      Change schedule to GameTick sub in Tithe plugin
      Cleanup RuneLite class (use Lombok)
      Add support for getting runelite launcher version
      Show RuneLite launcher version in info panel

Trig (1):
      Fix &quot;hosptial&quot; anagram clue typo (#3600)

TzZek (1):
      Add bake pie &amp; string jewelry to idle notifier (#3486)

WooxSolo (5):
      Fix remember screen bounds for KEEP_GAME_SIZE
      Move frame to right screen border when expanding large window
      Fix Jarvis infinite loop
      perspective: fix getCanvasTileAreaPoly for even number sizes
      npc indicators: add respawn timer

psikoi (2):
      Add Icon Material Tab + Hover effects
      Refactor plugin panels for new Icon Tabs

raqes (2):
      Rename Prayer Flicking plugin to Prayer
      Add prayer indicators to prayer plugin

shmeeps (1):
      Use chat messages for GE notifications (#3492)

ypperlig (1):
      Change tickrate for giant seaweed from 10 to 5
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-31-1.4.1-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-31-1.4.1-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.1 Release</title>
        <summary>Chat recolor, redwood tree markers, and grand exchange notifications</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-31T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>First, lately there have been several targeted phishing attacks against
RuneLite, including targeted ad buys on both Google and Reddit. If in doubt,
cross reference the site with the official GitHub and Discord. The main tell is
the official Windows download is an executable digitally signed by Alexander
Henne, and not a .jar. We can generally get these sites taken down, but it
usually takes some time to do so.</p>
<p>Now for the update:</p>
<p>Chat color for each chat type (public, private, clan, trade, etc.) are now
configurable in the &quot;Chat Colors&quot; configuratrion.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.1-Release/chatcolors.png" alt="chatcolors"/></p>
<p>The woodcutting plugin now can overlay redwood tree locations.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.1-Release/redwood.png" alt="redwood"/></p>
<p>The grand exchange plugin can now notify you when something buys or sells.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.1-Release/genotification.png" alt="genotification"/></p>
<p>Also a special thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sainttx">@Matthew Steglinski</a> who
contributed Javadoc for <a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite/pull/3236">155
files</a> in the API. This greatly
improves our <a href="https://static.runelite.net/api/runelite-api/">published Javadoc</a>.</p>
<p>Screen markers can now be assigned names, making it easy to save and reuse them
later without having to re-add and position them. Existing screen markers will
need to be deleted and readded.</p>
<p>Full screen mode was added and is toggleable in RuneLite settings.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.1-Release/fullscreen.png" alt="fullscreen"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix hiscore lookup autocomplete</li>
<li>Fix hiscore and GE lookups getting stuck when given invalid input</li>
<li>Improve boss timer spawn timers by start them when the NPC despawns instead of
at the beginning of the death animation</li>
<li>Add miscellaneous and scroll teleports to the world map plugin</li>
<li>Skill calculator now turns actions that will become available before target
level orange</li>
<li>The bank evaluator plugin now includes the price of untradeable items
tradeable versions</li>
<li>Optimize clickbox calculation code</li>
<li>Fix Vet&#39;ion boss timer and add KQ boss timer</li>
<li>Add option to swap &quot;interact&quot; with &quot;empty&quot; on birdhouses</li>
<li>Update menu swapper to support multiple fairy ring defaults</li>
<li>Fix slayer plugin to work with NPC contact</li>
<li>Add Bandit Camp fishing spot to fishing plugin</li>
<li>Fix MLM plugin when it is started/stopped from within the MLM</li>
<li>Fix UI responsiveness when closing skill calculator</li>
<li>Add Limestone attack stone to skill calc</li>
<li>Reset gorillas in demonic gorilla plugin on startup and world hop</li>
<li>Add gilded altar to idle notifier</li>
<li>Add wine making to idle notifier</li>
<li>Add option to swap minecart menu option to travel from GE to Keldagrim</li>
<li>Add bar dispenser clickbox overlay to blast furnace plugin</li>
<li>Show clickbox of the Boiler in Dorgesh-Kaan agility course in the agility
plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>Additionally, there were clue fixes from Eadgars-Ruse, Jordan Atwood, and Maiddog.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 26 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (30):
      pom: set updatePolicy always for runelite snapshots
      pom: remove tomcat deploy execution
      hiscore panel: properly error if result is null
      ge search panel: catch cache load exception from search returning null
      Revert &quot;boss timers: improve accuracy of boss respawn timer&quot;
      boss timers plugin: change to use npc despawn event
      agility plugin: fix exception on reconnect
      poh plugin: fix exception when tile for burner is not fully visible
      Remove actor death event, use despawn event instead
      woodcutting plugin: timeout woodcutting sessions
      woodcutting plugin: show redwood trees
      world map plugin: merge jewellery teleports and magic teleports
      world map plugin: add misc teleports
      skill calculator: lombok some of UIActionSlot
      skill calculator: turn indicators orange for actions that will become available before target
      screen marker overlay: stop if preferred size is null
      antidrag: reset drag when focus is lost
      runelite-client: add ItemMapping to map untradeable items to tradeable versions
      item manager: use item mapping
      item manager: cache unable to look up on unsuccessful bulk lookup too
      runelite-client: update bank calculation and barrows calculation to use item mapping
      runelite-api: optimize ChatMessageType.of()
      config manager: fix resetting configuration items with no default value
      config panel: allow color configs with no value
      runelite-client: add chat color config
      runelite-client: remove chat color config from plugins
      Revert &quot;perspective: use viewport offset in get2DGeometry&quot;
      perspective: use viewport offset for offsetting rectangle in get2DGeometry
      runelite-api: use lombok constructors for Vertex/Triangle
      perspective: optimize clickbox generation

Alexsuperfly (3):
      boss timers: improve accuracy of boss respawn timer
      boss timers: fix Vet&#39;ion timer to start after 2nd phase death
      boss timers: add KQ to boss list

BeefaloKing (1):
      Stretched Fixed Mode Plugin: Add Integer Scaling option (#2863)

Eadgars-Ruse (2):
      Change hot/cold overlay to only show outline of dig area (#3166)
      Fix coordinates for venenatis hot cold clue (#3212)

Ethan (5):
      Exclude ironmen from daily herb box notifications
      Add option to swap &quot;interact&quot; with &quot;empty&quot; on birdhouses
      Update menu swapper to support multiple fairy ring defaults
      Add teleport scroll locations to map
      Add notifications to Grand Exchange plugin

Hydrox6 (1):
      Fix items with no Grand Exchange Price using Store Price for the right click menu instead of High Alchemy value

Iguaan (2):
      slayer plugin: read bracelet charges directly from chat message
      slayerplugin: fix current task regex and new task via npc contact regex

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      enqueue most post/put/delete requests

Jordan Atwood (6):
      Allow imbued Ring of Wealth for emote clue (#3230)
      Fix location for West Ardougne emote clue (#3231)
      Fix Grand Tree mushrooms clue
      Improve Yanille anvil room map clue location
      Add Wilderness Bandit Camp fishing spot
      Fix Iban&#39;s Temple emote clue

Kelvin (1):
      Use single DynamicGridLayout for XPTracker stats (#3432)

Kruithne (1):
      skill calculator: allow XP values up to 200,000,000 rather than 188,884,740

Lars (3):
      Motherlode Mine - Startup / shutdown bugs (#3124)
      XpInfoBox - Remove min/max experience check (#3397)
      Use screenmarker name not ID for displaying it (#3423)

Magic fTail (3):
      BossTimerPlugin: Find bosses based on id instead of name
      More accurate respawn timers
      MenuEntrySwapper: Reorder config items to alphabetical order

Maiddog (1):
      Fix typo in Pyramid Plunder emote clue (#3419)

Matthew Steglinski (6):
      runelite-api: Add missing documentation
      Fix ArrayIndexOutOfBoundsException when an empty command is typed
      devtools: Add camera position overlay
      devtools: Add base, local, and region coordinates to LocationOverlay
      grandexchange: Format &#39;Price each&#39; value for items in additional information layout
      Add local player death event

Morgan Lewis (3):
      Clue Scroll Plugin: Add wording to direct users to world map
      Dev-tools: Add location overlay to show world map position
      Remove WorldMapOverlayTest Plugin

Ruben Amendoeira (6):
      Hiscore auto-complete fix
      Skill calcs performance improvement
      Refactor ClientUI using CardLayout
      Remove feed refresh button
      Add top margin to the XP tracker error panel (#3343)
      Add naming to screenmarkers

Simon Landry (1):
      Add Boiler to Dorgesh-Kaan obstacles IDs (#3437)

Tomas Slusny (11):
      Unify NPC highlighting color settings
      Use NpcSpawned and despawned for getting cacheNpc
      Move private methods at bottom of NPC plugin
      Add support for fullscreen mode
      Change default PluginPanel layout to DynamicGrid
      Change config TextField to TextArea
      Move highlighted/hidden to top
      Store markers based on epoch millis
      Properly set preferredSize of navContainer
      Add Limestone attack stone to skill calc
      Update Lombok to 1.16.22

TzZek (1):
      Add making wines to idle notifications (#3441)

WooxSolo (1):
      Reset gorillas in demonic gorilla plugin on startup and world hop

drivfe (1):
      screen markers: fix for confirm dialog appearing behind main UI window

iguaan (3):
      idlenotifier: add support for gilded altar
      timers: use correct capitalisation for antifire in settings
      slayerplugin: fixed bracelet charge counter

iskarky (1):
      Swap menu entry for minecart travel from GE to Keldagrim

shmeeps (2):
      Capitalize world map configuration names (#3301)
      Account for slightly different dimensions of first and second/third floors (#3249)

ypperlig (1):
      blast furance plugin: add bar dispenser to clickbox overlay
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-25-Phishing-Attempts</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-25-Phishing-Attempts"/>
        <title>Phishing attempts</title>
        <summary>Phishing attempts</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-25T23:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Lately there have been an increase in people advertising malicious websites
impersonating runelite.net, which will instead hack you. It looks like this has
been mostly in Twitch chat.</p>
<p>This is a reminder the only safe download is from runelite.net. The checksums
for the download are available from the official github, and the Windows binary
is digitally signed by Alexander Henne.</p>
<p>I sent an abuse report to one of their providers, NameCheap, over 24 hours
ago... but it does not seem to be very effective. If anyone here happens to work
at NameCheap NOC contact me.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-24-1.4.0-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-24-1.4.0-Release"/>
        <title>1.4.0 Release</title>
        <summary>Obsidian theme, 05/10 interface styles, and screen markers</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-24T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The new Obsidian theme has been released, which re-skins the client UI and most
of the plugin panel intefaces. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/psikoi">@psikoi</a>
who has been working on this for the last month.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/obsidian1.png" alt="obsidian1"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/obsidian2.png" alt="obsidian2"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/obsidian3.png" alt="obsidian3"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/obsidian4.png" alt="obsidian4"/></p>
<p>An interface style plugin was added to allow switching the 2005 or 2010 game
frames.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/2005.png" alt="2005"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/2010.png" alt="2010"/></p>
<p>A screenmarker plugin was added to mark areas on the screen.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/marker.png" alt="screenmarker"/></p>
<p>Support for level goals has been added, that loads the XP/level goals from the
Vanilla goals interface and displays it in XP tracker.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/goals.png" alt="goals"/></p>
<p>The world map plugin now shows all teleport locations, and detailed requirements
for all agility obstacles.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/tele.png" alt="tele"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.4.0-Release/shortcut.png" alt="shortcut"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix agility plugin to not show obstacles in Vespula&#39;s raid room</li>
<li>Fix impling plugin incorrectly showing imps after a world hop (1.3.9.1)</li>
<li>Add Corsair Cove fishing spots to fishing plugin</li>
<li>Add Gu&#39;Tanoth bridge obstacles to agility plugin</li>
<li>Improve performance of stretched fixed mode by utilizing volatile images</li>
<li>Check inventory for required emote clue items too</li>
<li>Add gem rocks to mining calculator</li>
<li>Fix plugin toolbar tooltips</li>
<li>Fix low detail mode sometimes causing game sounds to not load</li>
<li>Change the anti-drag plugin to only work with shift held</li>
<li>Fix slayer bracelet charges not updating when there is only one charge left</li>
<li>Add commas to ground item quantities</li>
<li>Add Burgh de Rott fishing spots to fishing plugin</li>
<li>Fix bounds for west bookcases in the Kourend Library (1.3.9.1)</li>
<li>Add teak garden bench to construction calculator</li>
<li>A notification and timer were added to the agility plugin for the agility
arena</li>
<li>XP boosts for bones have been corrected in the skill calculator</li>
<li>Farming, fishing, herblore, and hunter have been expanded on in the skill
calculator</li>
</ul>
<p>Additionally there were clue fixes from user35557, Jouni Pikkarainen, and Jordan
Atwood.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 26 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Abex (1):
      interfacestyles: Run on game thread (#3129)

Adam (21):
      Update substance to 8.0.02
      Bump to 1.4.0-SNAPSHOT
      runescape-api: add sprite related imports for interface style plugin
      runelite-api: add sprite override api
      runelite-api: add widget positioned event
      Add interface styles plugin
      runelite-client: fix usage of npc despawn event
      agility plugin: limit obstacles to agility pyramid regions
      modelviewer: begin work on tile shapes
      Revert &quot;Delay setting of low detail mode&quot;
      low detail plugin: apply low detail on startup if on login screen
      runelite-mixins: fix hasHintArrow
      runelite-api: expand hint arrow api
      Revert &quot;Fix early stop of player lookup in HiScores (#3035)&quot;
      hiscore panel: wrap lookup in a runnable exception logger
      hiscore panel: clear tooltips when clearing levels
      hiscore panel: pass result to detailsHtml and remove reduncant null check
      hiscore panel: remove duplicate getExperience
      runelite-client: add detached overlay position
      runelite-client: add screen markers plugin
      screen marker panel: fix toggling hide/show

Alex Kolpa (5):
      Clear plugin skill tracking on reset
      Add agility arena notifier
      Add agility arena timer
      Don&#39;t show experience progress for unranked skills
      Change AgilityArenaTimer contact to GitHub account (#3121)

Joel (1):
      Add missing Corsair Cove fishing spots (#3096)

Jordan Atwood (2):
      Add puzzle box indicator to Drunken Dwarf clue
      Add Gu&#39;Tanoth bridge obstacles

Jouni Pikkarainen (1):
      Fixed typo in a cryptic clue solution

Levi Schuck (2):
      Fix til next level time for low xp amounts
      Switch to safer division method without floats Use custom formatter since LocalTime.toString rolls over the amount of days.

Lotto (5):
      entityhider: don&#39;t hide npcs by default
      client: use Image instead of BufferedImage
      stretchedfixedmode: use volatile image instead of buffered image
      emoteclues: change symbols to ✓ and ✗
      emoteclues: display when item is in inventory

Magic fTail (2):
      Fix edgeville monastery emote clue scroll (#2909)
      Add missing Port Sarim and Ape Toll fishing spots (#2837)

Max Weber (5):
      Cleanup FarmingTracker panels
      Add VarC events
      Allow get/setVarbitValue to operate on arbitrary varp sets
      devtools: Replace Var tracker with Var Inspector
      varinspector: Lazily initialize var arrays

Morgan Lewis (4):
      WorldMap: Add teleport destinations for spells and jewellery
      WorldMapPointManager: Fix concurrent modification exception
      WorldMap: Add agility shortcut level requirements
      WorldMap: Fix jewellery item name loading bugs

Rheon-D (1):
      Fix friend note not displaying due to color tags

Ruben (3):
      Restore Plugin Toolbar Button Tooltips (#2833)
      Add Gem rocks to mining calculator plugin (#2907)
      Add mouse hover changes to various ui elements

Ruben Amendoeira (22):
      Restyled the client frame
      Added custom components + moved/rewrote some
      Grand Exchange Plugin redesign
      Hiscore Plugin redesign
      Kourend Library Plugin slight design tweak
      News Feed Plugin slight design tweak
      Notes Plugin slight design tweak
      Configs slight design tweak
      Exp trackers plugin redesign
      Info panel redesign
      Farming plugin panel redesign
      Plugin side toolbar design tweak
      Skilling Calculators Plugin design tweak
      SetOpaque performance fix
      Fix Config search bar focus
      Moved the new text selection colors globally
      Removed unused styling on JComboBox
      Fixed exp tracker pop-up in the progress bar
      Recolour config names to white
      Expanded SkillIconManager to include smaller versions
      Added/Changed custom UI components
      Skill Calc plugin redesign

Seth (1):
      impling plugin: fix impling list not clearing on hopping worlds

SoyChai (1):
      Friend notes plugin: Add documentation and increase code readability (#2714)

Tomas Slusny (7):
      Delay setting of low detail mode
      Change Anti-Drag plugin to work only with SHIFT
      Fix access levels in XpStateSingle
      Add Varps for player experience goals
      Add support for player experience goals to tracker
      Add support for preferredSize to OverlayRenderer
      Change ScreenMarkers to use OverlayRenderer

Unknown (1):
      Change string to match for slayer bracelet

William Metcalf (1):
      Add commas to ground item quantities

WooxSolo (1):
      Add RSTileMixin.getGroundItems and RSNPCMixin.getTransformedComposition

Xavier Bergeron (1):
      Fix early stop of player lookup in HiScores (#3035)

raqes (1):
      Fix 2005 interface container alignment, add scrollbar and spellbooks

shmeeps (1):
      Add Burgh de Rott fishing spots to fishing overlays (#3132)

trimbe (1):
      Fix bounds for west bookcases in Kourend library (#2875)

user35557 (1):
      Clue Scrolls: fix dark warrior fortress clue coordinates (#3083)

wa1id (1):
      Add teak garden bench to construction calculator.
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-18-1.3.9-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-18-1.3.9-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.9 Release</title>
        <summary>Hot/cold world map improvements, skill calculator, and anti-drag plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>I have been given the go ahead to continue on with RuneLite development by MMK,
so here is release 1.3.9.</p>
<p>I have had to move most of my tools to be internal to
the project, and it is taking some time. We will probably be able to begin
accepting PRs again in full force sometime this weekend.</p>
<p>Hot/cold clue locations are now shown on the world map, and fairy ring teleport
icons now have a tooltip showing the fairy ring code. Contributed by
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> and
<a href="https://github.com/MESLewis">@MESLewis</a> respectively.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.9-Release/hotcold.png" alt="hotcold"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/Kruithne">@Kruithne</a> has added a skill calculator plugin.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.9-Release/skillcalc.png" alt="skillcalc"/></p>
<p>An anti-drag plugin has been added from
<a href="https://github.com/devdennis">@devdennis</a>. It lets you configure the &quot;drag
delay&quot; which can help prevent you from dragging items you meant to click on.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The opponent info plugin now displays approximate players hitpoints instead of
a percentage</li>
<li>Show GE and high alch prices on shop items when examined</li>
<li>Made existing config option for higlighting marks of grace also affect overlay
color</li>
<li>Add trap obstacles to agility plugin</li>
<li>Fix motherlode mine plugin when it is enabled when inside of the mine</li>
<li>Mitigate a rare crash in the official client at certain areas ingame</li>
<li>Add a tooltip font type configuration option</li>
<li>Auto complete hiscore lookups based on friends, clan members, and players</li>
</ul>
<p>Also thanks to trimbe, Shuhao Wu, Jordan Atwood, and Alex Kolpa for contributing
clue fixes.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 22 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (20):
      agility plugin: use immutableset
      slayer plugin: move widget inventory check to game tick
      runelite-api: expose friends
      runelite-mixins: fix setting menu preventing menu add event from being fired
      friend notes plugin: only add menu entry after &quot;Message&quot;
      agility plugin: fix exception if obstacle is off screen
      runelite-api: add getWorldType()
      runelite-client: add hiscore manager
      opponent info: use player hitpoints from hiscores
      item controller: don&#39;t return duplicate items in bulk lookup
      http-service: optimize bulk item price lookup
      http-service: lombok item api
      item manager: cache no price when unable to batch lookup
      injector: support field hooks prior to field being changed
      runelite-mixins: fire npc despawn event before composition is nulled
      runelite-mixins: wrap drawTileUnderlay in try/catch
      Revert &quot;fix: Hide vanilla raid points box when inside chambers of xeric&quot;
      speccounter plugin: fix kalphite queen spelling
      Update pom and README to reflect changes to project structure
      Remove distribution management

Alex Kolpa (2):
      Fix typo cryptic clue
      Check player position on state change

Dennis (1):
      runelite-client: add anti drag plugin

Dimitris Karittevlis (1):
      shows ge and high alch prices for shop items that are examined

HSJ-OSRS (1):
      Make existing config options for highlighting marks of grace also affect the overlay color

Hashes (1):
      Fix ProgressBar percentage displaying (#2609)

Jeremy Plsek (2):
      agility plugin: add trap obstacle overlay
      overlayutil: reset stroke for renderpolygon

Jordan Atwood (4):
      Fix wording/locations of kill x elite cryptic clues (#2628)
      Fix Warrior&#39;s guild emote clue
      Use British floor numbering in cipher clues
      Fix Gypsy Aris cryptic clue

Kamiel (1):
      fix: Hide vanilla raid points box when inside chambers of xeric

Kruithne (1):
      Implement Skill Calculator plug-in

Lars Ørnlo (1):
      Motherlode Mine - Region check on plugin startup

Max Weber (10):
      http-api: print a more helpful error message when resources are not filtered
      Make VarbitChanged only fire once, after everything has settled
      runelite-api: Annotate Perspective methods with `@Nonnull`
      groundmarkers: Fix NPE in drawTile
      kourendlibrary: Fix for rev 170 menu code
      runelite-api: Update ID files
      cache: Strip tags from java names
      Rename varcs &gt; varCInts
      Rename varcstrings &gt; varCStrings
      Revert #2530 &quot;Make VarbitChanged only fire once...&quot;

Morgan Lewis (2):
      Fix world map overlay to draw pixel perfect on the World Map
      Add tooltip and custom icon to World Map fairy ring destinations

Reasel (1):
      runelite-client: add tooltip font type dropdown

Sebastiaan Holthuis (1):
      Add &quot; fps&quot; after the number of FPS

Shuhao Wu (1):
      Fix &quot;Clap in the magic axe&quot; master clue. (#2685)

Tomas Slusny (13):
      Improve ProgressBarComponent to support %/FULL
      Update opponent info to use PanelComponent
      Add ItemLayer height to GroundItems overlay
      Fix World Map widget check in Hooks.java
      Reset Fight Cave plugin prayer background color
      Merge clearMapPoint with resetClue
      Improve performance of ClueScrollWorldMapPoint
      Move Hot/Cold message logic to HotColdClue
      Add support for map for hot/cold clues
      Do not floor percentage in progress bars
      Fix updating of Hot/Cold clue
      Reset clue overlay preferred size each render
      Calculate child preferred size based on max size

TzZek (1):
      Add Elf Area Obstacles

Unknown (1):
      Add Overlay for Silver Jewelry to Slayer Plugin

pettenge (1):
      hiscore plugin: autocomplete name lookup based on friends, clan members, and players

trimbe (1):
      Fix hot cold location south of gnome stronghold

ypperlig (1):
      Clear previous image components in fight caves overlay
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-16-Update-2-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-16-Update-2-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown"/>
        <title>RuneLite threatened to shutdown - Update 2</title>
        <summary>RuneLite threatened to shutdown - Update 2</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-16T03:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>I have just finished speaking to MMK. I have agreed on a 1-2 day halt on
development pending further discussion, and I have closed sourced the
deobfuscator and the deobfuscated RuneScape client. RuneLite is allowed to
operate during this time.</p>
<p>The new OSBuddy API that has been announced is also a nice step forward. The two
clients become not too dissimilar at that point, both with a closed API
implementation.</p>
<p>What this means for developers is you must rely on our exposed API and are no
longer able to extend or modify it. This limits development some certainly but
it is what we must do.</p>
<p>The closed sourced components are both build-time and update-time tools, and are
not artifacts shipped to the end user. So, the level of difficulty required for
someone to independently prove that a given build of RuneLite is safe (eg. not
going to hack you) is approximately the same as before, and still certainly very
possible.</p>
<p>Hopefully it gets better from here...</p>
<p>- Adam</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-16-Update-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-16-Update-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown"/>
        <title>RuneLite threatened to shutdown - Update</title>
        <summary>RuneLite threatened to shutdown - Update</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-16T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>First off, I would like to thank everyone in the community showing so much
support for RuneLite. What Jagex did was clearly a great injustice.</p>
<p>It is unfortunate the only way I seem to be able to have any meaningful
discussion with Jagex is via loud blog posts.</p>
<p>I have read the <a href="http://services.runescape.com/m=news/third-party-client-update?oldschool=1">Third Party Client
Update</a>
and it contains some new details to me. Specifically, the &quot;sharing
of tools used to deobfuscate Old School RuneScape code, and then re-publishing
said code.&quot;.</p>
<p>So, I have stripped the aforementioned tools and RuneScape client from GitHub. I
will be removing the other distributions off of the server shortly.</p>
<p>Unfortunately this means now RuneLite will be only partially-open source.
RuneLite is BSD-2 licensed and the license permits me to do this. This will
hinder new contributions some in that they cannot learn of and create new APIs
for client access, but we already have a well established API which can be used
in the majority of cases.</p>
<p>I don&#39;t really agree with some of the reasoning behind this, bots have existed
before RuneLite existed, and I&#39;m sure some of them have a better knowledge of
the game than I do, but if it must be taken down, then okay.</p>
<p>Regarding &quot;The conversation with RuneLite is part of the long-term strategy and
approach for all 3rd party clients and the future of our own official client.&quot;,
as started in the initial post, I have no problem shutting down
RuneLite if all third party clients are to be shut down. But I will not shut it
down with the other clients still running.</p>
<p>Jagex, if you have objections to any other aspect of RuneLite, I would prefer if
you contacted me and told me about it, instead of threatening me to take down the
entire project. I have no problem working with you to address any concerns.</p>
<p>There is a large portion of RuneLite code that Jagex definitely has no claim over,
and it belongs to me, and to the many contributors to the project, and I think
it is wrong for you to claim it must all be removed.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-15-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-15-RuneLite-threatened-to-shutdown"/>
        <title>RuneLite threatened to shutdown</title>
        <summary>RuneLite threatened to shutdown</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>I have just finished having a discussion with Mod Mat K, who is threatening
legal action against RuneLite for copyright infringement if it is not shut down
by the end of the week.</p>
<p>I inquired specifically what parts of RuneLite violate Jagex&#39;s copyright so that
I could take it down, and even offered to close source the project, but MMK
insisted that the entire project must be shut down, and gave no specifics about
the copyright infringement claims, and only said legal action would be taken.</p>
<p>I was also informed that they were &quot;working on&quot; shutting down both OSB and
Konduit, and that I was the &quot;first&quot; to be contacted.</p>
<p>RuneLite is certainly in a grey area to my knowledge of copyright law. I have no
issue working with Jagex to remove parts of it from the public eye if requested.
I would also have no issue shutting down the entire client if all 3rd party
clients were banned. However, I do have an issue with shutting down the entire
client while OSBuddy is allowed to operate.</p>
<p>While I agree that RuneLite does threaten the integrity of the game, what
threatens it even more is that I have to <em>buy</em> OSBuddy in order to gain the same
competitive advantages of other players in game. RuneLite exists to try and
level the playing field as to who can develop on the client, of which I think it
has done well.</p>
<p>Jagex, please work with me here instead of singling us out. We love the game,
and have great respect for you, but this is not an acceptable way of dealing
with the third party clients.</p>
<p>If anyone within the community happens to be a (copyright) lawyer, please
contact me.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-10-1.3.8-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-10-1.3.8-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.8 Release</title>
        <summary>World map clue overlay, friend notes, hot-cold helper, and special attack counter</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-10T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Clue scroll locations are now shown on the in-game world map. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/MESLewis">@MESLewis</a> for his work on this over the past
weeks.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.8-Release/cluemap.png" alt="cluemap"/></p>
<p>A friend notes plugin has been added which lets you associate notes to friends
on your friends list.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.8-Release/friendnotes.png" alt="friendnotes"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/Eadgars-Ruse">@Eadgars-Ruse</a> added a hot-cold helper to the
clue plugin which helps you narrow down which location the clue is at each time
you check the orb. It marks the possible locations to dig on the map.</p>
<p>A special attack counter was added which counts draining special attacks done
against certain bosses like the Corporeal Beast.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.8-Release/speccounter.png" alt="speccounter"/></p>
<p>A FPS plugin was added from <a href="https://github.com/LeviSchuck">@LeviSchuck</a> which
displays the current FPS, and allows you to configure a max FPS limit.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix agility plugin calculating laps to level when you level up on a lap</li>
<li>Add missing Rellekka fishing spots to fishing plugin</li>
<li>XP globes mouseover now shows xp per hour</li>
<li>Fix date placement in screenshot with stretched fixed mode</li>
<li>Fix xp tracker sometimes showing negative XP</li>
<li>Fix bank tags to be case insensitive</li>
<li>Add Puro-Puro static spawn locations to imp plugin</li>
<li>A chest price evaluator was added to the barrows plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 29 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>AWarbear (4):
      Make farming tracker use english for dates by default (#2345)
      agility plugin: identify active course based on its region
      agility plugin: fix calculating laps to level when leveling up from a lap
      Move system tray icon to be created before the client requests focus

Adam (17):
      impling plugin: use spawn events
      npc indicators: remove unnecessary tagged npcs list
      npc indicators: use events for highlighted npcs
      runelite-client: add tick counter
      demonic gollias: use tick counter
      mixins: inject get/set tick count
      runescape-client: refactor Nameable
      runescape-client: class304 -&gt; FriendContainer
      runescape-client: class298 -&gt; IgnoreContainer
      runescape-client: refactor FriendManager
      runescape-client: method1792 -&gt; removeFriend
      runelite-api: expose Friend
      runelite-api: add nameable name change event
      injector: add method hooks
      Add removed friend event
      chatbox input manager: add support for character limit
      Add friend notes plugin

Alex Kolpa (1):
      Ensure tile spawns on all planes are simulated (#2495)

Eadgars-Ruse (2):
      Add hot-cold clue scroll plugin
      Fix warmer/colder consideration for hot-cold plugin

Jeroen (1):
      Show missing fishing spots in Rellekka in overlay.

Jonathan (1):
      Add xp per hour to xp globes mouse-over tooltip

Jordan (2):
      Add all bracelets to Argdougne emote clue item requirement (#2417)
      Fix Sinclair Mansion emote clue (#2468)

Jordan Atwood (2):
      Fix &quot;No boots&quot; requirement in Mausoleum clue
      Fix Shadow dungeon emote clue location

Joshua Filby (11):
      feat: add a way to get AccountType
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#field787 to ScriptEvent#mouseX
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#field780 to ScriptEvent#mouseY
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#widget to ScriptEvent#source
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#field779 to ScriptEvent#op
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#field776 to ScriptEvent#target
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#pressedKey to ScriptEvent#typedKeyCode
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#typedKey to ScriptEvent#typedKeyChar
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#objs to ScriptEvent#params
      refactor: rename ScriptEvent#string to ScriptEvent#opbase
      fix: import correct field

Kamiel (1):
      Add missing overhead icons to API

Lars Ørnlo (1):
      Add config option that enables/disables mouse tooltip on rune pouch however since information is already available on screen if rune pouch is enabled.

Levi (1):
      FPS Plugin

Levi Schuck (2):
      Fix negative total XP calculation when skill starts
      FPS plugin: fix startup not applying limits

Lotto (3):
      screenshotplugin: fix timestamp &quot;button&quot; not being stretched
      screenshotplugin: fix screenshot button ignoring displayDate setting
      screenshotplugin: fix Hunter levelup widget ignoring toggle

Magic fTail (3):
      BossTimerPlugin: Add missing bosses (#2150)
      bank tag plugin: fix searching to be case insensitive
      HunterPlugin: Fix deadfall trap

Maid Dog (2):
      Use Immenizz&#39;s in-game name
      Fix monastery clue position

Mantautas Jurksa (1):
      Add Puro-Puro static spawn locations

Max Weber (6):
      runelite-client: Cleanup cli arguments
      runelite-client: Log uncaught exceptions
      method3836 &gt; getSpriteAsSpritePixels
      Add SpriteManager to get sprites from the cache.
      runelite-client: Make notification options not mutually excusive
      Add Burgh de Rott map clue

Morgan Lewis (7):
      runescape-client: export more world map related methods
      runescape-api: import world map methods
      Add world map api and mixin
      runelite-client: add world map overlay renderer
      runelite-client: add world map test plugin
      clue plugin: add world map overlay for clue location
      WorldMapOverlay: Add check for current plane

Rheon (1):
      Add spade req, fix item reqs for emote clues (#1753)

Shuhao Wu (1):
      Updated cryptic clue solution for Kalphite area

SoyChai (2):
      demonicgorilla: Rename plugin to &quot;Demonic Gorillas&quot; with capital G
      demonicgorilla: Use proper inverse methods instead of the ! operator

Tomas Slusny (14):
      Option to only recolor right click menu on ground
      Add 2 new notifications modes (message, flash)
      Disable filtering on logback.xml
      Merge ImagePanelComponent with PanelComponent
      Update all overlays to support new PanelComponent
      Make ProgressPie follow component pattern
      Move the xp/hr in globes to new system
      Sanitize player indicators options
      Clear children in LocationOverlay
      Simplify component system
      Update plugins to use the new TitleComponent
      Add support for customizable gap and border
      Restore min width when keeping window size small
      Iron platelegs -&gt; platebody for Draynor emote clue

Tyler Nichols (1):
      Update to Solution of speaking to Falo the Bard (#2352)

WooxSolo (5):
      Add graphics object API
      Add graphics object created event
      Add graphics objects to devtools
      Add option to keep either window or client size
      Change WorldPoint::distanceTo to use chebyshev distance instead of euclidean distance

iguaan (1):
      correct hard entrana cryptic clue

raqes (1):
      Add special attack counter

trimbe (3):
      Add missing Dorgesh-Kaan clue, fix dagganoth king cryptic
      item manager: change batch item price to accept a collection
      barrows plugin: add barrows chest price evaluator

wa1id (1):
      Add Elite Map clue at Zul-andra (#2306)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-03-1.3.7-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-05-03-1.3.7-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.7 Release</title>
        <summary>Farming plugin, demonic gorilla plugin, and cerberus plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-05-03T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>This release adds a farming tracker plugin, which keeps track of what time your
crops were planted and will notify you after a time when it would be fully
grown. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/abextm">@abextm</a> and
<a href="https://github.com/NotFoxtrot">@NotFoxtrot</a> for their work on this over the
last few weeks.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.7-Release/farming.png" alt="farming"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/wooxsolo">@WooxSolo</a> contributed a demonic gorilla plugin,
which counts the attacks against you so you can tell when it will switch attack
styles. After it switches, the new style is displayed.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.7-Release/gorillas.png" alt="gorillas"/></p>
<p>A Cerberus plugin has been added, from
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> which shows the ghost order.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.7-Release/cerberus.png" alt="cerberus"/></p>
<p>Also, a special thanks to Brandon Kase, FatalWaffles, Jordan Atwood, Maiddog,
NotFoxtrot, and Rprrr for continuing to correct and update the clues.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The cannonball count plugin tracks the count correctly again</li>
<li>The side toolbar can now be hidden via a button in the menu bar, or ctrl+f11</li>
<li>There is now a toggle for highlighting agility shortcuts</li>
<li>A vengeance other timer has been added</li>
<li>The XP orbs stay on screen while hovered</li>
<li>Third age tools added to idle notifier</li>
<li>XP tracker &quot;actions left&quot; no longer rounds down, and doesn&#39;t get confused by
hopping accounts anymore</li>
<li>Screenshots can now be taken with the &quot;insert&quot; key</li>
<li>Add ability to disable low HP and prayer notifications</li>
<li>Add skill progress bar to hiscore panel</li>
<li>Add stat change indicator to boosts plugin when indicators are selected</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 25 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (22):
      update check: set read timeout on socket, move off of request thread
      item controller: remove all synchronous fetching
      item service: move overflow of pending lookups log message to debug
      ws service: optimize session storage
      Revert &quot;Fix cannon cannonball count&quot;
      runelite: fix check for client before requesting itemmanager
      runelite: add --disable-update-check
      account service: fix not setting autoincrement on user id
      runescape-client: export changedSkills and changedSkillsCount
      runelite-api: add VisibleForDevtools annotation for methods only visible for use in devtools
      devtools: add addxp
      runelite-api: add headicon enum
      demonic gorilla plugin: use headicon api
      http-service: fix sql2o statement leak
      Add maven-compiler-plugin to plugin management
      devtools: post xp changed event too
      runescape-client: export world map related symbols
      Use only southermost ghost wave for cerb plugin
      scripts: update comand script from live
      scripts: update options panel rebuilder from live
      scripts: apply zoom limits to options panel rebuilder
      scripts: apply command callback to command script

Brandon Kase (2):
      Adjust stomp dragon-axe clue location
      Add missing comma to hard cryptic

Dennis (1):
      fix prayer reorder shutdown

FatalWaffles (1):
      Fix Beckon in Digsite location

Grant (1):
      Add Agility shortcut highlight toggle

Hydrox6 (2):
      Add Vengeance Other indicator
      Reorder Timer configuration options

Jeroen (1):
      XpGlobe now stays on screen while hovered over it.

Jordan (1):
      Add Zeah Altar elite map clue (#2283)

Jordan Atwood (5):
      Add missing Pyramid emote clue item
      Fix Shayzien command tent emote clue
      Fix hard cryptic clue
      Allow &quot;degree&quot; and &quot;minute&quot; in coordinate clues
      Use British floor numbering in clue scroll hints

Kamiel (6):
      Expose Actor animation and actionFrame to API
      Add anim command to developer tools
      Expose Actor graphic and spotAnimFrame to API
      Add gfx command to developer tools
      Add logger command to change the logger level
      Add 3rd Age Axe and 3rd Age Pickaxe animations to Idle Notifier

Levi (2):
      Refactor overlay renderer screenshot code into a draw manager
      xp tracker: rewrite tracking datastructures

Lotto (1):
      cluescrolls: support any type of ring of dueling in emote clues

Maiddog (3):
      clues: fix spotted cape not being detected
      clues: change npc name check to nameEquals
      Fix various clue objects and locations.

Mantautas Jurksa (1):
      Fix master fire cape emote clue

Marcus Heine (1):
      Enable screenshotting with INSERT

Max Weber (17):
      Initialize ItemManager to a complete state
      Allow ClientThread to re-run invokeLater-ed methods
      Allow ItemManager to be ran off the client thread
      Use ItemManager in KourendLibraryPlugin
      Use ItemManager in GrandExchangePlugin
      cache: Name ObjectDefiniton&#39;s varpID and configID correctly
      Add various animation IDs
      Add UsernameChanged event
      Add WorldPoint::getRegionID
      Allow PluginPanels to opt-out of the scrollbar
      Add FarmingTracker plugin
      configmanager: Allow multiple delimiters
      Add missing U+00A0 NO-BREAK SPACE character
      Rename Setting to VarPlayer
      Merge Varcs into Client::getVar
      Rename SettingsTracker
      farmingtracker: Prevent saving when teleporting

Morgan Lewis (1):
      Add support for mapping parameter names

NotFoxtrot (2):
      Fix cryptic elite clue: Father Aereck
      Fix master clue emote: Entrana church

Reasel (1):
      Add ability to disable HP and Prayer notifications (#2007)

Rprrr (2):
      screenshot plugin: fix exception when taking screenshots on login
      Fixes #2146 (Brother Tranquility &#39;talk-to&#39; &amp; &#39;&#39;transport&#39; option swap w/Menu Swapper plugin)

Samuel Beresford (1):
      Adds skill progress bar to hiscore panel Matches existing progress bar (look&amp;feel) as xp tracker

Seth (6):
      boosts overlay: move next change text to display at the top
      boosts plugin: Add stat change indicator when indicators are selected
      opponent info: reduce padding size
      clue scroll: add toggle for hint arrows
      clue scroll: fix easy clue
      farming panel: reset progress bar background

SoyChai (5):
      Correct misspellings of &quot;transparent&quot;
      Add underscores to minigame names in WidgetInfo
      agilityplugin: Rename plugin package to agility
      reportbutton: Double frequency of time updates to avoid skipping seconds
      discord: Display skill icons in Discord while training

Tomas Slusny (10):
      Agility plugin small code cleanup
      Do not draw text on top of Mark Of Grace
      Add support for hiding the sidebar
      Fix clue requiring platebody, but wanting legs
      Remove unused imports in ClientUI (#2061)
      Reset clues based on item ID
      Reset clue on unknown clues
      Add Cerberus plugin
      Verify game&#39;s minimum size
      Add mappings for currentLoginField

WooxSolo (12):
      Add rectangle support to config
      Remember screen position after closing and reopening
      Add ability to lock client to screen
      runescape-client: export hitsplatValues and applyActorHitsplat
      runelite-api: add hitsplat applied event
      runelite-api: export collision data
      runelite-api: add line of sight algorithm
      runelite-api: add WorldArea
      devtools: add line of sight and valid moves
      Add demonic gorilla plugin
      cannon plugin: fix cannonball count when loading and firing on the same tick
      cannon plugin: add granite cannonball to unload check

oplosthee (1):
      Add toggle for drawing overhead player names to PlayerIndicators plugin

u6077743 (1):
      Improved low hp notif. by considering nmz absorption, 2210
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-26-1.3.6-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-26-1.3.6-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.6 Release</title>
        <summary>Tile marking, clue bugfixes, and entity hider</summary>
        <updated>2018-04-26T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A tile marker plugin has been added which allows you to highlight arbitrary
tiles by holding shift and selecting &quot;Mark&quot;. The markers are saved with your
client settings, and work even in instances.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.6-Release/tilemarker.gif" alt="tilemarker"/></p>
<p>Agility shortcuts throughout the game are now highlighted, and the agility
plugin now highlights marks of grace:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.6-Release/agilityshortcut.png" alt="agilityshortcut"/></p>
<p>A fairy ring location plugin was added which tells you the location fairy rings
are configured to:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.6-Release/fairyring.png" alt="fairyring"/></p>
<p>An entity hider plugin was added which lets you hide other players and npcs from
view.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.6-Release/entityhider.png" alt="entityhider"/></p>
<p>There has been a large effort to fix and correct all of the clues from the
cluescroll plugin. I expect a few more releases before it is solid, but it
should no longer point at random objects anymore.</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Opponent info should no longer sometimes show &quot;null&quot; for opponent name</li>
<li>The infoboxes now have a configurable wrap limit, and can be configured to
stack verically instead.</li>
<li>Support for slayer braclets have been added to the slayer plugin</li>
<li>The MLM plugin now only shows veins on the same floor as you are</li>
<li>Fix notes plugin to textwrap</li>
<li>Add kingdom of misc. to screenshot plugin</li>
<li>The length XP globes are shown is now configurable</li>
<li>Fix client resizing itself when the plugin panel is collapsed and the client
is maximized</li>
<li>Color HP xp drops when praying too if XP drops are split</li>
<li>&quot;Actions Left&quot; has been added to XP globes</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 26 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (22):
      ge plugin: use query runner for bank query
      perspective: use LOCAL_COORD_BITS in getTileHeight and document that parameters are local coords
      Remove unnecessary groupdIds that are equivalent to the parents
      Rename runelite api artifact to runelite-api
      Rename runescape api artifact to runescape-api
      Change pushingpixels groupId to be under net/runelite
      Update cache-server test to use cache 165 too
      overlay renderer: fix npe when client is null
      devtools: show instance location information
      Add ground marker plugin
      tile mixin: don&#39;t fire itemlayer change events when loading regions
      update check service: set a lower connect timeout
      Add command executed event
      runescape-client: rename pendingVarbitChanges/Count
      devtools plugin: add commands to get and set varbits
      idle notifier plugin: use wildcard import for animation ids
      runelite config: add position to config items
      infobox overlay: Configure the amount of boxes per row
      npc mixin: transform npc in getName/getCombatLevel/getId
      npc indicators: fix npe building npcs
      Revert &quot;Merge pull request #1886 from deathbeam/cleanup-sidebar&quot;
      xp tracker service: fix deadlock acquiring connections

Cas van Dongen (1):
      Slayer plugin: Added support for slayer bracelets.

Gabriel (2):
      Fix and add a few medium clue steps
      Fix anagram, cryptic and emote medium clues (#1876)

Gamer1120 (1):
      Only render mining spots on same floor in MLM. Fixes #1642

Grant Dellar (1):
      Change JEditorPane to JTextArea

HypoxiaOSRS (3):
      screenshot plugin: add Kingdom screenshot
      Add rune and addy dragon slayer icons (#1725)
      Fix gnome agility arena emote clue

Håkon Rosseland Paulsen (1):
      xpglobes: add duration of xp orbs in config

Infinitay (2):
      kingdom plugin: only show favour when in kingdom
      Add fairy ring plugin

Jeremy Plsek (5):
      clientui: don&#39;t update size if already maximized
      geplugin: create input listener class
      geplugin: replace default action when pressing alt
      stretched mode: pass extended modifiers on click
      Highlight agility shortcuts

Jeroen (2):
      Added an idle notification for when crushing infernal eels.
      Add support for colored HP xp drops if XP drops are split and a combat prayer is active

JerwuQu (1):
      Allow customization of barrows brother location colors

Jordan Atwood (1):
      Fix Canifis emote clue

Kamiel (4):
      Change regen meter arc position and size to match with orb background
      Draw player indicator clan icon further away from player name
      Add VarClientStr to api and rename VarClient to VarClientInt
      Change ground marker plugin to use selected region tile coords instead of basing them off of mouse location

Levi Schuck (1):
      Sort Fishing spots by distance from camera

Lotto (2):
      cluescroll-plugin: group item variants + display when to unequip items
      Add entity hider plugin

Mantautas Jurksa (2):
      cluescroll plugin: remove tags from clue text
      Fix barbarian chest and abbot langley clue steps

Reasel (1):
      Add dropdown for font style for in-game overlays

Rheon-D (1):
      agility plugin: add highlighting for marks of grace

Rune Nielsen (3):
      Clue plugin: fix easy and medium cryptic and emote clues (#1726)
      IdleNotifierPlugin: Add big net fishing
      IdleNotifier: Add infernal harpoon

Samlof (1):
      Add more travel menu swap options and claim slime swap

Seth (3):
      overlay util: remove white outline on minimap dots
      barrows overlay: Reorder enum to match in game overlay/use full name
      barrows overlay: Replace existing slain brother overlay with our own

SomeZer0 (1):
      Fix spirit tree cryptic clue step

Tomas Slusny (8):
      Add back support for regular overload (NMZ)
      Stronger visual indicators for MLM sack
      Do not use object world locations
      Make ObjectClueScroll extend LocationClueScroll
      Fix runelite-client shading
      Remove unnecessary code from GroundMarkerPlugin
      Fix herbiboar performance/blinking
      Cleanup sidebar expanding/closing

Trees (1):
      Add Sacred Eels and Barehand Fishing (#1857)

Valmir Memeti (1):
      Add &quot;Actions left&quot; for Xp globes

WooxSolo (2):
      Fix cannon cannonball count
      Fix 2 emote clues
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-19-1.3.5-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-19-1.3.5-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.5 Release</title>
        <summary>Web XP tracker, Clue scroll arrows, improved HiScore lookup, clue &amp; bug fixes</summary>
        <updated>2018-04-19T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Kamielvf</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>The new Web XP Tracker can now easily be accessed from within the client, simply click the &#39;Open xp tracker&#39; button or right click on one of the skill panels.
Share your gains with your friends and clanmates!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.5-Release/web-xp-tracker.png" alt="xptracker"/></p>
<p>Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> the clue scrolls will now point out the location, npc or object you have to go to for your current step when you are in the area!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.5-Release/clue-arrows.gif" alt="cluearrows"/></p>
<p>The motherlode overlay has been updated to show more information. You can now see the amount of gems received thanks to <a href="https://github.com/ypperlig">@ypperlig</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.5-Release/motherlode.png" alt="motherlode"/></p>
<p>The HiScore lookup within the client now supports virtual levels and shows clue stats for each individual clue tier now.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.5-Release/lookup.png" alt="lookup"/></p>
<p>NPCs can now be tagged with either their hull or their tile, this makes it easy to see where you have to click to interact with the tagged NPC. <a href="https://github.com/raqes">@raqes</a></p>
<p>For a list of all changes, see the list below.</p>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Kamiel</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 33 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (17):
      wsservice: move log messages to debug
      item stats: add raids combat potions
      item stats: fix sara brew
      item stats: fix zammy brew
      geplugin: add alt-click to bank items and bank inventory
      slayer plugin: add several missing slayer tasks
      Use built in player index field
      bank value plugin: make calculator more testable
      Fix bank value overflow
      Add deferred eventbus for posting events on the next tick
      Add item container changed event
      runelite-api: add events for actor spawning and despawning
      screenshot plugin: create screenshot folder on startup
      screenshot plugin: remove unused import
      ge search panel: show &quot;No results found&quot; if search is empty, clear on empty lookup
      worldpoint: add dx/dy/dz methods
      Add Angle and Direction

AdenKenny (1):
      Add challenge answer to Clocktower clue

Bart van Helvert (1):
      More accurately draw tile indicators

Dennis (1):
      fix bank placeholder release option

FatalWaffles (7):
      Fix worldpoint for mausoleum
      Add 2nd emote for mausoleum clue
      Fix barb agil and digsite emote clues
      Fix referee cryptic clue
      Fix &amp; add emote clues.
      Add &quot;Teleport to Abyss&quot; to Menu Entry Swapper
      Fix fight arena pub emote clue

Gamer1120 (1):
      TRISTESSAS_TRAGEDY spelling error

HypoxiaOSRS (1):
      Fix shilo village and white wolf mountain hard clues

haakonrp (1):
      menu swapper: swap reset on dismantled traps and lay on expired traps

Jack (1):
      Fix XP Drop plugin recolouring ALL drops whenever a combat prayer is enabled

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      tooltips: hug edge of screen instead of jumping

Kamiel (6):
      Remove tags from highscore lookup
      Set herbiboar and mlm overlays to draw ABOVE_SCENE
      Move herbiboar minimap overlay to its own class
      Fix cat chasing menu entry swap
      Show grand exchange offer type on cancelled state
      Change menuOpened from FieldHook to Hook

Lars Ørnlo (3):
      Add upgraded sack to varbits (5556)
      Some quality of life changes to the Motherlode Mine Plugin.
      Added option that allows a player to see the number of gems found during the current mining session.

Lotto (7):
      hiscore: lookup local player on double-click
      hiscore: display levels above 99 in the panel
      hiscore panel: fix clue/lms/bh breakage
      hiscore panel: fix total level breakage
      Revert &quot;hiscore panel: fix total level breakage&quot;
      hiscore panel: fix not displaying total level correctly
      cluescrolls: fix confusing solution text for Luthas

Marcus Ramse (2):
      Fix worldToMiniMap for locations outside of range
      Change brother name color when killed

Morgan Lewis (1):
      Add object and location to a Ardougne armour shop clue

Nuno Rodrigues (1):
      Fishing Plugin: Add new Lure fishing spots at Barbarian Village, Fix Karamja Spots

OShadowz (2):
      imp plugin: fix magpie impling name and spelling
      imp plugin: add config option to display impling names on minimap

Ocelot (1):
      clue scroll plugin: fix various clues with incorrect steps

Raqes (1):
      npc tag plugin: add option for highlight type and drawing names

Richard Goodman (1):
      Add more POH minimap overlays

Seth (1):
      ge plugin: Display spent price instead of original offer price

ShaunDreclin (2):
      slayer plugin: add slayer target highlighting
      Fix UnsupportedOperationException error in Slayer plugin

SoyChai (1):
      api: Add 1461 labelled sprites to SpriteId

Tomas Slusny (14):
      Add link to web XP tracker to XP panel
      Apply small font option only to dynamic overlays
      Change magic imbue timer to 12 seconds
      Swap also dismantle/reset on box traps
      Universal warning message support in config
      Make condition for H.A.M. pickpockets lowercase
      Add clue hint arrows for clues
      Set default offset to center of tile for arrows
      Do not reuse HttpUrl.builder for building xp urls
      Remove &quot;cast bloom&quot; swapping and make teleport off
      Move reordering of items after shift-click
      Hide clue scroll interface when no clue present
      Fix layer of MotherlodeOverlay
      Centralize setting of hint arrows for clues

Trees (1):
      Refactor FriendManager + Name

Tunnelsnake52 (1):
      Fix Dance a jig under Shantay&#39;s Awning coords

Tyler Bochard (2):
      Reduce player indicators overlay priority to MED
      Prevent artifacts in stretched fixed mode

raqes (1):
      Alphabetize the config entries of the menu entry swapper plugin.

nshusa (1):
      Refactored some variables in NPCComposition

nuno (2):
      Add Corsair Cove net fishing spot
      hunter plugin: fix salamander net display

richardbadman (1):
      Fixes easy clue

rune3132 (4):
      Adds individual clue counts to highscore plugin
      jewellery count plugin: add ring of recoil breaking notification
      clue plugin: order map clues after type and id
      clue plugin: fix/add various clues

winterdaze (1):
      fix prayer enhance duration
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-12-1.3.4-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-12-1.3.4-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.4 Release</title>
        <summary>Smooth animations, easier HiScore lookups, and smarter Abyss runs</summary>
        <updated>2018-04-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Soy</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Animation smoothing is here to showcase the bleeding edge of oldschool visuals.
Players, NPCs, and environmental objects can now be interpolated (or &#39;tweened&#39;)
to animate at higher framerates. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/DevDennis">@DevDennis</a> for bringing this eye candy to life.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.4-Release/animsmoothing1.gif" alt="animsmoothing1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.3.4-Release/animsmoothing2.gif" alt="animsmoothing2"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.3.4-Release/animsmoothing3.gif" alt="animsmoothing3"/></p>
<p>HiScore lookups can now be accessed from many more right-click menus, including
in the chatbox, your friends list, from private messages, in the clan chat
sidebar, and on the raiding party menu (for members with at least a kick-rank).
<a href="https://github.com/Kamielvf">@Kamielvf</a> worked on this quality of life change,
big thanks to him.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.4-Release/lookups.png" alt="lookups"/></p>
<p>The Dark Mage in the Abyss can now be highlighted whenever your inventory
contains a degraded pouch in need of repairs. Props to
<a href="https://github.com/jaeger25">@jaeger25</a> for looking after our forgetful
runecrafters.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.4-Release/darkmage.png" alt="darkmage"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Added healing values for 30+ missing foods; most importantly, easter eggs!</li>
<li>Menu entry swapper: updated the Travel option to include balloons and
Fremennik boats, and added a new Chase option for cats who love rat-hunting.
Pickpocket swapping is now limited to H.A.M. members only, due to unintended
thieving balance issues (eg. with blackjacking).</li>
<li>Removed the Pyramid Plunder plugin because
<a href="http://services.runescape.com/m=news/quality-of-life-improvements?oldschool=1">we don&#39;t need it any more</a>.
Good Jagex.</li>
<li>Renamed the Attack Indicators plugin to Attack Styles, and added better
control over when the indicator appears.</li>
<li>Added a toggle for displaying skilling session stats.</li>
<li>Updated our overlay text to use the current oldschool font, complete with
slashed 0&#39;s.</li>
<li>Fixed several clue scroll helpers which pointed to wrong spots, suggested
the wrong dance emote, or contained typos.</li>
<li>Hunter plugin: fix bug related to setting traps and walking in the same tick.</li>
<li>Fixed report button not returning to normal when the plugin was disabled.</li>
<li>Fixed the bank tag search forgetting to match item placeholders.</li>
<li>Fixed the screenshot plugin crashing on certain dialogs, like grabbing a
hammer from a Motherlode crate.</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Soy</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 19 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (15):
      deobfuscator: add fernflower dependency
      runescape-client: refactor item composition int2 -&gt; placeholderId
      runescape-client: refactor item composition int3 -&gt; placeholderTemplateId
      runelite-api: add idEquals to inventory item query
      player indicators: add config for recoloring menu and showing clan rank
      indicators plugin: fix not always identifying menus by type
      runescape-client: item comp team -&gt; shiftClickIndex
      runescape-client: item comp int1 -&gt; team
      runescape-client: field3671 -&gt; params
      runelite-client: remove old plugin classloader
      runelite-client: remove old Plugin.file too
      pluginmanager: don&#39;t store plugin enabled/disabled state in config
      runescape-client: export hintArrowOffsetX/Y/Z
      Add animation smoothing plugin
      xp tracker plugin: don&#39;t throw from startUp if unable to fetch worlds

Dennis (3):
      runelite-api: expose item composition placeholder ids
      runelite-client: fix bank tags search for placeholder items
      runelite-client: only update the actions if the item id matches

FatalWaffles (6):
      Fixed typo for lighthouse clue
      Fix mess hall emote clue
      Fix &quot;JIG&quot; emote clues
      Fix errors with emote clues (#1312)
      Update worldpoint for map clue 2713
      Fix manor, swamp and lumber yard clue wordpoints (#1356)

Griffin Quarles (2):
      Update README.md
      Update CONTRIBUTING.md

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      itemprices plugin: fix noted items not showing ge

Kamiel (3):
      Reset report button text to default when plugin is disabled
      Add HiScore lookup to right click menus
      Update the runescape font to match current OSRS font

Levi (1):
      Average actions left between last 10 XP drops (#1323)

Levi Schuck (2):
      Lumbridge npcs have some bad compositions and return null in the dev
      tools.
      Reset XP on log-in of another character / mode

Lotto (1):
      cluescroll-plugin: remove duplicate anagram answers

Matt Jaeger (1):
      Highlight dark mage NPC in the center of the abyss when inventory
      contains a degraded pouch

Morgan Lewis (1):
      Add small clarification to Account Plugin tooltip

Rune Nielsen (2):
      Fixed misspelling in clue and added missing clue (#1274)
      Added UGTHANKI_KEBAB_1885 to itemstats plugin (#1263)

Septron (2):
      Add player index to api
      Add hint arrows to api

Seth (1):
      skill sessions: Add a toggle for displaying session stats

SoyChai (12):
      Add healing values (+14) for pumpkins and easter eggs
      itemstats: Add anchovies (+1), fruit battas (+11), and missing (sliced)
      fruits (+2) including peaches (+8)
      itemstats: Fix errant healing stats for sweetcorn variants
      itemstats: Add Dorgeshuun foods with wiki-claimed healing values
      itemstats: Add chocolatey milk (+4) and giant carp (+6)
      banktags: Adjust dialog text to match Withdraw-X dialog
      screenshot: Fix ArrayIndexOutOfBounds errors caused by unsafe parsing of
      level-up widget
      screenshot: Add documentation for primary methods
      screenshot: Define more accurate method names and access levels
      attackstyles: Rename Attack Indicators plugin to Attack Styles
      attackstyles: Add a toggle to Always show style
      attackstyles: Simplify config descriptions

TheLonelyDev (1):
      menu swapper: add Fly, Rellekka travel options, and Chase

Tomas Slusny (4):
      Save text configuration value on enter
      Swap pickpocket only on H.A.M. members
      Revert &quot;Reset XP on log-in of another character / mode&quot;
      Remove pyramid plunder plugin

WooxSolo (3):
      Fix Actor.getWorldLocation to use pathX/pathY instead of getX/getY
      Update game tick event to run after packets have been processed
      hunter plugin: fix setting trap and walking at once

psikoi (1):
      Add a null check to avoid a NullPointerException when the query returns
      null.
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-05-1.3.3-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-04-05-1.3.3-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.3 Release</title>
        <summary>Bank tags, item shift click configuration, and improved player indicators</summary>
        <updated>2018-04-05T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Bank tags have been added, which allow tagging items in the bank which can later
be searched on. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/devdennis">@devdennis</a> for this,
and <a href="https://github.com/abextm">@abextm</a> for the input dialog work.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.3-Release/banktags.png" alt="banktags"/></p>
<p>You may now also customize the shift click option of any item in the inventory.
Right click the inventory and select &quot;Configure&quot;, then select the option on the
item you want to use for shift click. Thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/Kamielvf">@Kamielvf</a> for this!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.3-Release/shiftclick.gif" alt="shiftclick"/></p>
<p>The player indicator plugin can now render players clan ranks next to their
names and also show friends, teammates, and clan members in the right click menu.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.3-Release/indicators.png" alt="indicators"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fix prayer reoder plugin not always reodering prayers since the last update</li>
<li>Disable kingdom of misc plugin by default</li>
<li>Add last destination for spiritual fairy tree to menu swapper plugin</li>
<li>Allow configuring gp thresholds for ground items highlighting</li>
<li>Add options to disable mouse tooltips on interfaces and in chatbox</li>
<li>Fix nmz plugin informing you your absorption is low immediately after entering
nmz</li>
<li>Require shift to be held for npc tag option to be visibile</li>
<li>Fix overlays drawing over the minimap area in fixed mode</li>
<li>Move titlebar buttons to side bar when custom chrome is disabled</li>
<li>Add option to enable the small font on all of the overlays</li>
<li>Fix grounditems showing items as Members only when hopping from f2p to p2p</li>
<li>Add fishing spots at Mount Quidamortem</li>
<li>Add turquoise slayer helmet to the slayer plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 11 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (21):
      cache: split color palette code into its own class
      cache: add and compute hsl in underlay
      cache: add and compute hsl in overlay
      cache: add post to object loader
      cache: rewrite map image dumper with logic from client
      ground items overlay: use a loop
      Add item layer changed event
      ground items: use item layer changed event
      Add maven-jar-plugin 3.0.2 to plugin management
      overlay renderer: use copyonwritelist for overlays
      overlay renderer: clip above scene and under widgets to viewport on fixed
      perspective: use viewport offset in get2DGeometry
      Revert &quot;Merge pull request #1154 from deathbeam/team-member-names&quot;
      clanchat plugin: change cache to expire after write
      Add clan member manager to cache clanmember ranks, use in clanchat plugin
      Move clanmember icon logic to clanmanager
      clanmanager: expose way to get bufferedimages for clan icons
      player indicator overlay: render clan rank next to names
      player indicators plugin: change color of menus
      bank tag plugin: use chatbox input manager
      Change MenuEntry type to int

Dennis (7):
      refactor method1721 to runWidgetOnLoadListener
      fix widget loaded event
      expose integer node fields
      expose widget flags
      expose widget actions
      add show menu option nine widget config
      add bank tags plugin

Infinitay (1):
      Disabled kingdom plugin by default, and it&#39;s options

Kamiel (6):
      Menu entry swapper: Swap last destination for spiritual fairy tree
      runescape-client: export getShiftClickActionIndex
      Add event for ItemComposition post()
      Add shift click customization to menu swapper plugin
      Add MenuOpened event
      Change shift-click customization behaviour

Max Weber (6):
      ScriptEvent &gt; ScriptCallbackEvent
      Expose methods to execute scripts
      cache: Allow scripts to start with comments
      Mixins: Give scripts a log.debug callback
      Allow assembly and loading of new scripts
      Add ChatboxInputManager to provide a RuneScape styled input box

Morgan Lewis (4):
      Add configuration options for ground item plugin
      Add names from widgetInfo to the Widget Inspector
      Add options to disable mouse tooltip on interfaces and chatbox
      Fix challenge answer for Nurse Wooned clue

Seth (6):
      nmz plugin: reset absorption notification when not in NMZ
      impling plugin: Move minimap overlay into it&#39;s own overlay
      agility plugin: Add region check to lap counter
      npc indicator: add shift right click to add tag option
      agility plugin: remove duplicate gamestate event
      ground item overlay: Fix boxes appearing very small with small font

ShaunDreclin (2):
      Fix capitalization of &#39;Black demon&#39; in npc_health.json
      Highlight current region in Location devtool

Tomas Slusny (24):
      Move loading of session before starting plugins
      Move viewport check below gamestate and CTP
      Save overlay data after resetting position
      Move title toolbar buttons to sidebar in native
      Improve ground items plugin
      Color the hidden items gray when in highlight mode
      Reduce the amount of temporary objects in items
      Invalidate ground items cache properly
      Invalidate item manager cache on hopping and login
      Use provider for client in item manager
      Add option for enabling small font
      Add support for drawing player team&#39;s names
      Add mappings and api for DMM player names
      Use built-in name rendering in player indicators
      Merge clan chat and player indicators plugin
      Always remove tags from player.getName()
      Add DMM name drawing opcodes to cache
      Add clan changed hook
      Properly invalidate clan ranks and names
      Add clan changed hook
      Add support for drawing player team&#39;s names
      Add mappings for DMM player names
      Add raids fishing spot
      Cache all ground items and then check their state

WooxSolo (1):
      Add chunk borders and map square borders to devtools

rune3132 (1):
      Added the turquoise slayer helmet to the slayer plugin
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-29-1.3.2-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-29-1.3.2-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.2 Release</title>
        <summary>Movable overlays, revamped clue scoll plugin, and tithe farm plugin</summary>
        <updated>2018-03-29T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Movable overlay support is finally here! This allows you to move any RuneLite
Overlay to any position on the screen. Hold alt to do so. There are 4 (or 5 on
resizable) &quot;snap corners&quot; provided where, if you move an overlay to a snap
corner, the client will dynamically place the overlay to not draw on top of
other overlays. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> for this
feature.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.2-Release/overlays.gif" alt="overlay"/></p>
<p>The clue scroll plugin has been rewritten, and now supports all clue types.
Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/devlotto">@devLotto</a> for their work on this.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.2-Release/clue1.png" alt="clue1"/>
<img src="/img/blog/1.3.2-Release/clue2.png" alt="clue2"/></p>
<p>A tithe farm plugin was added by <a href="https://github.com/unmoon">@Unmoon</a>, which tracks plant growth stages and state.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.2-Release/tithe.png" alt="tithe"/></p>
<p>The agility plugin now has an additional lap counter overlay by <a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@sethtroll</a>:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.2-Release/agility.png" alt="agility"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The instance map plugin maps now look the same as the ingame minimap</li>
<li>Mouse tooltips were moved to the bottom right corner of the mouse, and are now
hidden when the game has a tooltip open.</li>
<li>Fixed slayer points and streak being lost on restart</li>
<li>A kingdom of Miscellania plugin has been added to show you your support, and
optionally warn if it is unpopular</li>
<li>The raids points interface has been replaced with an overlay that also
includes party size. As with the other overlays, this is now movable.</li>
<li>Antipoison and superantipoision were added to the timers plugin</li>
<li>Add holy wrench effect to itemstats plugin</li>
<li>Sort infoboxes by plugin and priority</li>
<li>Add Silver sickle(b) to menu swapper plugin</li>
<li>Expand list of skill abbreviations for the !lvl command</li>
<li>Add spicey stew to item stats plugin</li>
<li>Add cave horror cannon spot</li>
<li>Fix lizardmen cannon spot</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (14):
      config manager: check for invalid keynames in loadFromFile
      config manager: add get and set configuration methods for objects
      Add movable overlay support
      travis: remove oracle-java8-installer as it broke and use the oraclejdk travis ships, which is new enough now
      feed plugin: make scheduled method public
      wsservice: remove sessions on close or error
      instance map plugin: rewrite to use client minimap code
      runescape-client: export varc related classes/fields
      Add varc api accessors, and tooltip varclient
      mouse highlight plugin: hide tooltips when the client is showing tooltips
      xp globes: move expire check to a scheduled method
      cluescroll overlay: set priority to low
      agility lap overlay: set priority to low
      slayer plugin: load points and streak on login and startup

Charlie Waters (2):
      Fix clue scroll plugin game object query for world overlay
      Fix some clue solutions

Infinitay (4):
      Added Kingdom of Miscellania plugin
      Added daily task indicators plugin
      Fixed checkCanCollectEssence method
      Disabled plugin by default  - Hopefully will encourage users seeking this    feature to configure it to their liking.    For example, if ironman, disable herb box.

Joshua Filby (50):
      refactor: rename widgetSettings to clientVarps
      refactor: rename settings to serverVarps
      refactor: remove unnecessary Client#getSettings(), use Client#getVarps()
      fix: hook clientVarps instead of settings
      refactor: rename get/set settings to get/set varp
      refactor(widget): rename method4463 to decodeListener
      refactor(widget): rename method4464 to decodeTransmitList
      refactor(widget): rename field2898 to onLoadListener
      refactor(widget): rename mouseEnterListener to onMouseOverListener
      refactor(widget): rename mouseExitListener to onMouseLeaveListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2807 to onTargetLeaveListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2908 to onTargetEnterListener
      refactor(widget): rename configListenerArgs to onVarTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename tableListenerArgs to onInvTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename skillListenerArgs to onStatTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename renderListener to onTimerListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2917 to onOpListener
      refactor(widget): rename mouseHoverListener to onMouseRepeatListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2899 to onClickListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2900 to onClickRepeatListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2901 to onReleaseListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2902 to onHoldListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2906 to onDragListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2907 to onDragCompleteListener
      refactor(widget): rename scrollListener to onScrollWheelListener
      refactor(widget): rename configTriggers to varTransmitTriggers
      refactor(widget): rename tableModTriggers to invTransmitTriggers
      refactor(widget): rename skillTriggers to statTransmitTriggers
      refactor(widget): rename selectedAction to targetVerb
      refactor(widget): rename field2895 to dragRenderBehavior
      refactor(widget): rename field2894 to dragDeadTime
      refactor(widget): rename field2817 to dragDeadZone
      refactor(widget): rename config to clickMask
      refactor(widget): rename name to opBase
      refactor(widget): rename field2866 to offsetX2d
      refactor(widget): rename field2867 to offsetY2d
      refactor(widget): rename field2919 to onChatTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2920 to onKeyListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2921 to onFriendTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2922 to onClanTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2923 to onMiscTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2924 to onDialogAbortListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2925 to onSubChangeListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2873 to onStockTransmitListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2820 to onCamFinishedListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2926 to onResizeListener
      refactor(widget): rename mouseActionsPresent to hasListener
      refactor(widget): rename field2951 to noScrollThrough
      fix: import correct field for click masks
      fix: import correct field for op base

Kamiel (6):
      Item price tooltip: use linebreak instead of comma
      Fix ranging potion showing invalid boost value
      Ground items: Only consume mouse clicks when a checkbox has been clicked
      Show remaining time on successful hunter traps
      Add raid party size varbit
      Replace raids points widget with custom overlay

Lotto (9):
      runelite-api: make InventoryItemQuery take in InventoryID
      runelite-api: add emote window widget info
      runelite-client: pass in z offset into renderActorOverlayImage
      runelite-client: extend overlay util to render Areas and LocalPoint
      runelite-client: add line wrapping to PanelComponent lines
      runelite-api: add sprite ids class
      runelite-client: add resource images to clue scroll plugin
      runelite-client: revamp clue scroll plugin
      runelite-client: remove old clue scroll enums

Lyn Levenick (2):
      Add notifications for NMZ power-up spawns
      Fix tray icon crash when clicked quickly on start

Max Weber (10):
      itemstats: Support holy wrench effect
      configmanager: synchronize disk access
      itemstats: use EnergyStat instead of anonymous stat
      menumanager: Actually remove menu options
      injector: Allow &lt;clinit&gt; an &lt;init&gt; injection with multiple mixins on the same class
      deob: Always use / delimters in pool.Class
      injector: Allow assertions to be used in mixins
      mixins: Use assert in scriptvm
      runelite-client: Add ClientThread to aid in synchronizing with the client
      Ensure createItemSprite is called on the game thread

Seth (4):
      info boxes: associate plugins to infoboxes
      info boxes: sort boxes by priority
      jewelrycharges: Add Teleport crystal(5)
      agility plugin: Add lap counter

ShaunDreclin (1):
      Add Silver sickle(b) to menu entry swapper plugin.

SoyChai (4):
      Expand list of skill abbreviations for the !Lvl command
      Expand tests for and document the Experience API
      Add spicy stews to item stats plugin
      Extra documentation for the Stat and StatChange classes

Tomas Slusny (18):
      Add Cave Horror cannon spot
      Fix Lizardmen cannon spot plane
      Add support for points to ConfigManager
      Add support for getting real canvas dimensions
      Calculate overlay bounds also for dynamic overlays
      Create translated copy of OverlayBounds
      Improve caching of game-related variables
      Change multiple overlay lists to map
      Instance map improvements + moving
      Make unsetConfiguration non-blocking
      Disable overlay dragging mode on focus lost
      Remove not needed parent point and minimap orb
      Move tooltip to the right-bottom of the mouse
      Add null-check for overlays in OverlayRenderer
      Add getCanvasOffset to clientUI, fix screenshots
      Add formatNumber methods to StackFormatter
      Expand panels based on click event not isSelected
      Add null-check for Client to MenuManager

Unmoon (1):
      Add Tithe Farm plugin

jamesahhh (1):
      Add antipoison and superantipoison timers (#1159)

rune3132 (1):
      Additions to Jewellery count plugin
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-22-1.3.1-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-22-1.3.1-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.1 Release</title>
        <summary>Prayer reordering, bank price evaluation, and NPC highlighting</summary>
        <updated>2018-03-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A prayer reordering plugin has been added which lets you reorder the prayers in
your prayer book. Big thanks to <a href="https://github.com/devdennis">@devdennis</a> for
the excellent work on making this possible;</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/prayer-reorder.gif" alt="prayorder"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/McSwindler">@McSwindler</a> contributed a NPC highlight plugin
which lets you tag npcs, and also configure a list of npcs which are
highlighted.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/npc-tag.png" alt="npctag"/></p>
<p>A bank evaluator has been added, which is a combination of effort from myself,
<a href="https://github.com/jplsek">@jplsek</a>, and
<a href="https://github.com/TheLonelyDev">@TheLonelyDev</a>. It will tell you the overall
GE and HA price of each tab of your bank.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/bank-eval.png" alt="bankval"/></p>
<p>The ground items plugin now supports quickly hiding and highlighting items.
Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@sethtroll</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/grounditems.gif" alt="grounditems"/></p>
<p>A herbiboar plugin has been added from
<a href="https://github.com/tylerthardy">@Perterter</a>. It highlights the starting rocks,
trail, and the two objects to search at the end of each trail.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/herbiboar.png" alt="herbiboar"/></p>
<p>An item price plugin has been added, from
<a href="https://github.com/ChaoticConundrum">@ChaoticConundrum</a>, which shows the price
of items when hovered over in the bank.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.1-Release/itemprice.png" alt="itemprice"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Ground items now support wildcards in both hidden and highlighted fields, so for example <code>*bone*</code>
will hide/highlight all bones</li>
<li>The boosted stats plugin now shows time until next change</li>
<li>The agility plugin allows configuring of the hitbox overlay color</li>
<li>Game menus options are no longer left broken when moving regions with the menu
option</li>
<li>Attack style plugin now hides attack styles better</li>
<li>Fixed Kourend library plugin, which was broken last release</li>
<li>Show glory location in POH plugin</li>
<li>Common cannon placement spots have been added to the cannon plugin</li>
<li>Remaining XP to level has been added to the hiscore panel</li>
<li>Removed background from the prayer flick overlay, which made the quick prayers
 toggle hard to see</li>
<li>Added godwars altar timer</li>
<li>Superior slayer notifications have been added to the slayer plugin</li>
<li>The slayer plugin infobox (with your current task) now has a configurable
timeout</li>
<li>The time until levelup has been added to the xp tracker panel</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 16 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (26):
      runelite-mixins: add null checks in region mixin
      Bump for 1.3.0.1-SNAPSHOT
      runelite-mixins: add null checks in region mixin
      boosts plugin: show time to next change
      ground items: add support for wildcards
      ge plugin: move item composition and image calls off of awt thread
      runescape-client: export updateNote
      runescape-client: fix sprite originalWidth&lt;-&gt;width and export fields for loading sprites
      cache: add provider interfaces for items, models, sprites, and textures
      cache: add updateNote to ItemDefinition
      cache: fix not invalidating vertexNormals in reset
      cache: expand on texture definition and loader
      cache: store original pixels and palette too, and add normalize()
      cache: add resize, recolor, and retexture to modeldefinirtion
      cache: add item sprite renderer
      cache controller: expose item sprites
      examine service: correct type column enum
      item manager: add batch item price lookup
      Hook to actor health being updated to detect death
      gitignore: add eclipse files
      runelite-api: move getConvexHull to Model
      runelite-api: add getConvexHull to Actor
      Add npc menu options to MenuManager
      devtools: remove double npc transform call
      utils: add wildcard matcher from grounditems
      runelite-client: add npc highlight plugin

Cas (1):
      Agility plugin: Agility configuration with Select Color

Charlie Waters (6):
      Add items to item stats plugin: spinach roll, lava eel, sandwich lady items, jangerberries
      Fix bug with rendering more than two tooltips following mouse
      Add TooltipManager method to add tooltip to front of list, and always add mouse highlight tooltip to front
      Add item prices plugin for item price/value tooltips
      Add FocusChanged event from runescape client
      Fix Groud Items plugin Alt+Tab bug by hooking FocusChanged event

Dennis (10):
      restore menu entries after open/close widget
      fix prayer order resetting after teleporting to a new area
      injector: checkcast return values from replaced methods
      runescape-client: export animation related symbols
      runelite-api: expose dragging widget fields
      runelite-api: add event for dragging widget
      runelite-api: add widget open event
      runelite-mixins: add null check for widget group in getGroup()
      runelite-api: add widget config
      runelite-client: add prayer reordering plugin

Dreyri (2):
      Broadcast widget hidden changed recursively for each child too
      Use isLocalHidden in attack indicator plugin

Jeremy Plsek (4):
      http-api: add batch lookup to ItemClient
      stack formatter: support larger stack sizes
      bank item query: only search items in current tab
      Add bank value plugin

Kamiel (1):
      Add progress pie type overlay

Max Weber (5):
      kourendlibrary: Fix NPE while loading
      kourendlibrary: Use correct coordinate conversion
      jarvis: allow null points
      Add JShadowedLabel
      Change colors in XPInfoPanel to be brighter

Seth (9):
      poh plugin: change gameobject map to tile object
      pog plugin: fix mounted glory minimap icon
      cannon plugin: add common cannon spots
      ground items: add support for quickly hiding/highlighting items
      hiscore panel: make hiscores type more visible
      hiscore panel: add Remaining XP to next level to hover text
      hiscore panel: add loading label when searching
      menu entry swapper: add bury swap
      prayer flick overlay: remove background arc

Tomas Slusny (24):
      Extract utlity methods to SwingUtil class
      Remove the need to extend JFrame in ClientUI
      Make plugins work with new ClientUI
      Remove need to extend JToolBar in PluginToolbar
      Make plugins work with the new PluginToolbar
      Remove the need for custom TitleToolbar component
      Make plugins work with new title toolbar
      Add Discord button through DiscordPlugin
      Add support for popups to navigation button
      Change panel supplier to just getter for panel
      Consistent behaviour between ClientUI and InfoPane
      Set correct offsets to overlays, smaller panels
      Reposition instance map correctly in resizeable
      Use backgroundComponent for drawing border of map
      Lower default width of the PanelComponent
      Fix herbiboar plugin NPE on startup
      Fix AgilityPlugin naming conventions
      Fix Herbiboar plugin naming conventions
      Correctly name Herbiboar classes
      Remove unused variables in Herbiboar plugin
      Fix ClientUI settings loading
      Click the navigation button on selecting in
      Fix tooltip modicon OutOfBounds
      Do not display stack in price tooltips

Toocanzs (1):
      Add God Wars Altar Timer

Tyler Hardy (4):
      Add herbiboar varbits
      Add herbiboar plugin
      Move region check to loading
      Fix improper varbit for trail 31372

Xavier Bergeron (1):
      Add slayer superior foe notification

XrioBtw (1):
      Fix net and harpoon swap for all fishing spots

joshpfox (1):
      configurable slayer infobox expiry timer

nvisser (1):
      Add time till next level to xptracker
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-15-1.3.0-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-15-1.3.0-Release"/>
        <title>1.3.0 Release</title>
        <summary>Menu swapping and highlighting, hp and spec regen meter, and player names on minimap</summary>
        <updated>2018-03-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p><a href="https://github.com/XrioBtw">@Xrio</a> contributed a menu swapper plugin which
swaps the left click menu options on some things.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.0-Release/menuswap.png" alt="menuswap"/></p>
<p>The ground items plugin can now highlight menu options based on item price,
thanks to <a href="https://github.com/devdennis">@devdennis</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.0-Release/menuhighlight.png" alt="menuhighlight"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/abextm">@abex</a> added a regen meter to the hitpoints and
special attack orbs.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.0-Release/regen.png" alt="regen"/></p>
<p>The player indicator plugin can now show player names on the minimap, from
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.3.0-Release/minimap.png" alt="minimap"/></p>
<p>Also, thanks to <a href="https://github.com/josharoo">@josharoo</a> and
<a href="https://github.com/fe-mirino">@fe-mirino</a> for their work on
expanding the <a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite/wiki">wiki</a>.</p>
<p>The minimap plugin now has an option to allow hiding the minimap on resized mode
(<a href="https://github.com/Blizik">@Blizik</a>)</p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The xp tracker plugin has been overhauled to show more information in less
space</li>
<li>Fixed item sprites in the fishing plugin (among other places) sometimes having
the incorrect zoom applied to them</li>
<li>Opponent info overlay will now update hitpoints for opponents you recently
were targeting</li>
<li>Fix hiscore player menu option intefering with other game menu options like
Whack</li>
<li>Fix attack styles not being hidden when attack style plugin configuration is
changed</li>
<li>Add right click menu to screenshot button to open the screenshot folder</li>
<li>Reposition points box in raids to be underneat the xp dropper overlay</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (20):
      Bump to 1.2.19.1-SNAPSHOT
      Bump to 1.3.0-SNAPSHOT
      session client: fix throwing IllegalArgumentException if deserialization of uuid fails
      widget id: fix viewport child widget
      Also bump scm tag
      session client: fix throwing IllegalArgumentException if deserialization of uuid fails
      widget id: fix viewport child widget
      item controller: add method for bulk price lookups
      instance map: fix various races between game and event threads
      runelite-api: add ability to get npc index
      runelite-api: expose cachedNpcs
      opponent info overlay: use last opponent if no opponent is targeted
      Reset player menu types whenever the options are changed
      runelite-api: expose npc composition
      dev tools overlay: transform npcs if applicable
      sessions: decrease session ping frequency
      cache: fix item definition default zoom2d
      runelite-api: add scale to createItemSprite
      http-service: add sprite service
      runelite-client: add github release plugin configuration

Bart van Helvert (1):
      Remove unneeded drawRegionTile calls

Blizik (1):
      Add ability to toggle minimap display

Connor (1):
      Resolving Issue #860 - Warned Attack Styles not properly hiding. Adding automated test coverage for AttackIndicatorPlugin.

Dennis (1):
      ground items plugin: add option to highlight menu

Dennis de V (1):
      Fix ground items nullpointer exception

Infinitay (1):
      Add confirmation dialog to runelite logout button

Jeremy Plsek (1):
      Add right click menu to screenshot button #797

Joshua Filby (2):
      runelite-client: Add Text#removeTags method
      runelite-client: Update plugins to use Text.removeTags

Kamiel (3):
      Raids plugin: Reposition the points box to prevent it from overlapping overlays
      Fix instance map &quot;show&quot; option not displaying in right-click menu
      Fix instance map &quot;show&quot; option not displaying in right-click menu

Max Weber (11):
      injector: Fix scriptvm not updating currentScript
      isRSHidden &gt; isSelfHidden
      Move widget inspector into it&#39;s own window
      jewellerycount: add imp-in-a-box
      Rename Point3D to WorldPoint
      Add conversion methods to WorldPoint and LocalPoint
      Update almost everything to the new API
      Remove old API
      Add planes to planeless tile objects
      hunter plugin: Don&#39;t iterate over all tiles
      Add regen meter plugin

Seth (6):
      dev tools: add location to dev tools plugin
      Remove viewport contains
      xp tracker: add format suffix to reduce string size
      xp tracker: update xp tracker UI
      NpcID: update ids to cache 165
      fishing plugin: remove broken minnow npcs and swap to graphic check

Tomas Slusny (6):
      Add idle anim and combat idle toggles to notifier
      Remove duplicated and unused OverlayUtil code
      Add support for drawing names on minimap
      Allow specifying default world in [0-9]{2} format
      Title-case and remove &quot;plugin&quot; from ME swapper
      Fix drawing of player names on minimap

XrioBtw (1):
      Add menu entry swapper plugin

nvisser (1):
      Round actions remaining up
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-08-1.2.19-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-08-1.2.19-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.19 Release</title>
        <summary>Stretched fixed mode, default world, and grand exchange price search!</summary>
        <updated>2018-03-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>Stretched fixed mode has been added, which stretches the game screen and makes
it more playable on high resolution monitors. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/devLotto">@devLotto</a> for making this happen.</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@sethtroll</a> added a GE search feature to the
existing grand exchange plugin. You may also use alt+click on your inventory to
GE search an item now.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.19-Release/ge-search.png" alt="ge-search"/></p>
<p>A news feed plugin was added which shows the latest RuneLite blog posts, Old
School RuneScape news, and a Twitter feed of JMods.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.19-Release/news-feed.png" alt="news-feed"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/ChaoticConundrum">@ChaoticConundrum</a> added Notes plugin that will allow you to
store notes that will be persisted via RuneLite configuration system.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.19-Release/notes.png" alt="notes"/></p>
<p>Finally, the long-requested default world plugin has been added thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a>, which sets a preconfigured home
world by default.</p>
<p>There were many smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The raids plugin now allows configuring whitelist/blacklist layouts and
rotations.</li>
<li>The screenshot plugin now takes screenshots of raid rewards</li>
<li>Fix length of prayer enhance timer</li>
<li>The instance map can now be closed with escape and floor can be changed with scrollbar</li>
<li>The &quot;You are fishing&quot; overlay now works again since the last OSRS update</li>
<li><a href="https://github.com/arlyon">@arlyon</a> improved native OSX support - with native fullscreen, and focus
requesting</li>
<li>Fix cannon plugin showing incorrect double hit spots after region change</li>
<li>Allow disabling of the skill icons on XP drops</li>
<li>Clear saved private chat history upon clear request</li>
<li>Fix clanchat icons not showing during region loading</li>
<li>Add configuation option to make the client size fixed</li>
<li>Add minimum threshold to teamcape configuration, and now disable by default</li>
<li>Most of the plugins has been renamed to proper names, abbreviations was removed and casing was fixed
(for example Raids plugin is now named &quot;Chambers Of Xeric&quot;)</li>
<li>Special Attack Orb plugin was removed in favour of native OSRS special attack orb</li>
<li>Various notifaction-related settings was moved to &quot;RuneLite&quot; config section, and now they are applied
to all notifications</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 14 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (12):
      runescape-client: add jav_config
      cannon plugin: use infobox counter instead of overlay
      http-service: add session service
      http-api: add session client
      runelite-client: add client session manager
      client session manager: delete session on shutdown too
      http-service: queue item lookups from images
      input: don&#39;t allow duplicate input handlers
      item service: process pending lookups in order
      Change mouse wheel listener back to an interface as the instance map input listener uses it
      ge panel: use static number formatter
      runelite-client: add configuration option for resizable

Charlie Waters (3):
      Add Notes plugin
      Add waterskin charges to jewellerycount plugin. Fixes #825.
      Fix notes plugin loading notes from account

David Kosub (1):
      Notifier improvements and fixes

Desetude (3):
      Fixed HiscorePanel text
      Allow customization of the default color for ground items
      Renamed &#39;Experience drop&#39; -&gt; &#39;XP Drop&#39;

Kamiel (13):
      Add ability to whitelist layouts
      Add ability to highlight rooms
      Add ability to whitelist boss rotations
      Add floor duration(s) to infobox tooltip
      Get points from varbits instead of widget
      Set size properly
      Make rotation whitelist not case-sensitive
      Raids plugin: read proper input for room whitelist
      Instance map: Add support for user input
      Clear saved private chat history upon clear request
      Allow disabling of the skill icons on XP drops
      Fix cannon plugin showing incorrect double hit spots after region change
      Fix clanchat messages not showing rank icons at certain moments

Lotto (18):
      deobfuscator: fix aic failing to determine if a field is imported
      http-api: add feed types
      http-service: add services for getting blog posts, tweets and osrs news
      http-service: add feed api endpoint
      http-api: add client for looking up feed
      runelite-client: add news feed plugin
      Improve deob method finding in the injector
      Use a mixin for calling Hooks.draw instead of a @Hook
      Move the 765x503 constants to a Constants API class
      Add a mixin for storing stretched fixed mode setting states
      Add logic for game image stretching in Hooks#draw
      Modify the size and location of the game canvas if stretched is enabled
      Add support for proxying mouseWheelMoved events
      Add support for specifying the position to insert mouse listeners in
      Add mouse listeners that stretch event x/y
      Add stretched fixed mode plugin
      runelite-client: fix Use tooltip arrow not being displayed
      runelite-api: fix worldToMiniMap not working correctly in stretched mode

Max Weber (52):
      Move the Login and Logout buttons to the TitleToolbar
      draw(IIIIII)V &gt; drawRegion
      AudioInstrument.SINE &gt; AUDIO_SINE
      zoom: Fix pitch relaxer after rev 165 changes
      Reuse NumberFormatter to reduce allocations
      inline RSHashTableMixin.getNodes into RSWidgetMixin.getParentId to reduce allocations
      specorb: Cache draws to reduce allocations
      field429 &gt; WorldMapRegionX
      field432 &gt; worldMapRegionWidth
      field426 &gt; worldMapRegionY
      field427 &gt; worldMapRegionHeight
      field3005 &gt; rsOrdinal
      class41 &gt; MapCacheArchiveNames
      field546 &gt; DETAILS
      field541 &gt; COMPOSITE_MAP
      field548 &gt; COMPOSITE_TEXTURE
      field542 &gt; AREA
      field545 &gt; LABELS
      field542 &gt; name
      field450 &gt; objectDefinitionId
      class247 &gt; WorldMapDecorationType
      field446 &gt; decoration
      field452 &gt; rotation
      class31 &gt; WorldMapDecoration
      field417 &gt; decorations
      class29 &gt; WorldMapRectangle
      method588 &gt; getRegionRectForViewport
      field544 &gt; mapRegions
      class35 &gt; WorldMapRegion
      field3464 &gt; value
      class284 &gt; HorizontalAlignment
      class266 &gt; VerticalAlignment
      field3436 &gt; value
      field3464 &gt; horizontalAlignment
      field3463 &gt; verticalAlignment
      field538 &gt; screenX
      field537 &gt; screenY
      field459 &gt; minX
      method312 &gt; getMinX
      method302 &gt; getMinY
      field453 &gt; minY
      method294 &gt; getFileId
      field465 &gt; identifier
      method296 &gt; getIdentifier
      field455 &gt; name
      method288 &gt; getName
      field4014 &gt; worldMapDataByIdentifier
      method6175 &gt; getWorldMapDataByFileId
      method6077 &gt; getWorldMapDataContainingCoord
      method290 &gt; containsCoord
      vmethod712 &gt; containsCoord
      method6122 &gt; onMapClicked

Seth (7):
      opponent info: remove color tags from opponentOpponent name
      item stat: add raid food
      screenshot plugin: fix up chatMessage events
      screenshot plugin: Add raids reward
      item client: add getIcon method
      ge: Add search feature
      idle notifier: add barbtail/dragon harpoon animation

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (1):
      Remove left click calling from BA plugin

Tomas Slusny (23):
      Add fuzzy searching to config panel
      Move the notification options to Notifier
      Remove duplicate options from IdleNotifier
      Remove notification settings from NMZ
      Add support for oily rod fishing to idle notifier
      Remove unnecessary chatCommandsEnabled from config
      Allow other types of alerts when messages are off
      Fix &quot;You are fishing&quot; in fishing plugin
      Remove the timeout for HP/pray thresholds
      Correctly focus game canvas when requesting focus
      Make idle notifier work for splashing/missing
      Improve scoring of Jaro-Winkler
      Add link browser utility service
      Use new LinkBrowser in SessionManager
      Use new link browser in Grand Exchange plugin
      Use new link browser in feed plugin
      Continue running in case Discord lib load failed
      Restore original username on syncer shutdown
      Disable team capes plugin by default
      Add support for changing world to API
      Simplify RuneLite API world
      Add default world plugin
      Inverse window resize condition

Unknown (1):
      Team Capes: Added minimum cape count

arlyon (4):
      extract mac-specific functionality into OSXUtil
      notifier: fix to request focus on OSX
      extract out number formatting utility
      Update plugins to use either NumberFormat or the StackFormatter

joshpfox (1):
      Remove duplicate anti-venom+ config check

l2- (1):
      fix prayer enhance timer. its actually 10 seconds shorter than 5 minutes
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-01-1.2.18-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-03-01-1.2.18-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.18 Release</title>
        <summary>New grand exchange plugin, pyramid plunder plugin, and the cannon plugin now shows NPC double-hit spots</summary>
        <updated>2018-03-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A grand exchange plugin has been added by
<a href="https://github.com/someonewithaninternetconnection">@Someonewithaninternetconnection</a>.
It shows your current grand exchange offers and their progress:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.18-Release/ge.png" alt="ge"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/NotFoxtrot">@NotFoxtrot</a> contributed a pyramid plunder plugin which uses a less obtrusive interface:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.18-Release/pp.png" alt="pp"/></p>
<p>Finally, the cannon plugin was extended by <a href="https://github.com/SemtexError">@SemtexError</a> to show the NPC double-hit spots:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.18-Release/cannon.png" alt="cannon"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>TzTok-Jad overlay is now shown for the whole fight duration</li>
<li>The puzzle solver now displays the fastest solution</li>
<li>Add Dorgesh-Kaan and Brimhaven agility arenas to the agility plugin</li>
<li>Show skill details on hover instead of click in the hiscore panel</li>
<li>Maniacal monkeys have been added to the hunter plugin</li>
<li>Hunter plugin was improved to be more accurate, and catch rate overlay was removed</li>
<li>Fullscreen support has been added for OSX</li>
<li>Achievement diary plugin has been removed in favour of new OSRS achievement diary interface</li>
<li>World map has been fixed, no more increased memory consumption after it is closed</li>
<li>Positive and negative boosts are now properly colored when using absolute boosts</li>
<li>Cannonball plugin now supports unloading</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (16):
      overlay renderer: remove unnecessary lambda which makes it hard to profile
      xtea service: fix get() query to join on id
      Revert &quot;xtea service: fix get() query to join on id&quot;
      xtea service:try to fix query again
      runescape-client: refactor WorldMapManager
      runescape-api: import world map data
      runelite-api: expose world map data
      Garbage collect world map once closed
      menu manager: add method to remove player menu items
      hiscore plugin: remove player option on shutdown
      hiscore plugin: add config for player option
      text component: allow color tags
      boosts overlay: show boosts in color
      attack indicator plugin: process hidden styles on startup/shutdown and config changes
      mixin injector: fall back to method name if no deobfuscated name is found
      Add support for intercepting mouse and keyboard input

Devin (1):
      Change TzTok-Jad overlay to be persistent

Hexagon (1):
      Use the address returned by the worldlist api instead of building our own

Joshua Filby (1):
      runescape-client: set the close operation for running deob client to exit on close

Kamiel (6):
      Fix minor issues
      Add ability to set custom colors
      Fix overlays not being rendered
      Follow java coding conventions
      Use normal font weight for input field
      Fix panel expanding inconsistency (#464)

Lotto (21):
      grounditems: offset text on z axis
      puzzlesolver: add IDA* + manhattan distance solver
      puzzlesolver: don&#39;t spit out exceptions when the puzzle is finished
      puzzlesolver: use the new solver and display Solving.. + Solved! msgs
      puzzlesolver: update the test to use the new solver
      puzzlesolver: add an option to draw dots instead of arrows
      puzzlesolver: fix solution being reset when clicking the puzzle quickly
      puzzlesolver: remove bounds check from PuzzleSolver#getStep
      Fix Widget#isHidden returning incorrect state when parent is null
      Add grand exchange support to InventoryWidgetItemQuery
      Add varbit for multicombat area
      opponentinfo: display the name of the target of your target
      examineplugin: only capture menuactions with the option &quot;Examine&quot;
      notifier: add option to disable notification sounds
      Add guide prices support to InventoryWidgetItemQuery
      Add equipment window support to InventoryWidgetItemQuery
      modelmixin: use verticesCount/trianglesCount instead of array lengths
      agilityplugin: add support for Dorgesh-Kaan
      agilityplugin: add support for Brimhaven
      hiscoreplugin: show skill details on hover instead of click
      runelite-client: remove diary progress plugin

Max Weber (30):
      cameraPitch &gt; cameraPitchCopy
      field885 &gt; cameraPitch
      method2995 &gt; buildVisibilityMaps
      zoom plugin: Add option to relax the camera&#39;s upper pitch limit.
      cache: Add get_is_mobile opcode.
      cameraPitch &gt; cameraPitchTarget
      cameraPitchCopy &gt; cameraPitch
      method565 &gt; drawMapIcons
      method564 &gt; drawMapRegion
      field3927 &gt; worldMapX
      field3944 &gt; worldMapY
      field3947 &gt; worldMapZoom
      field3948 &gt; worldMapZoomTarget
      method385 &gt; drawFlashingMapIcons
      method406 &gt; drawMapLinks
      method402 &gt; drawNonLinkMapIcons
      class39 &gt; MapIcon
      method4375 &gt; bitpack
      class47 &gt; MapIconReference
      field3406 &gt; id
      field488 &gt; areaId
      field556 &gt; areaId
      field3788 &gt; scriptMapIconReference
      class33 &gt; MapLabel
      field433 &gt; fontSize
      field3935 &gt; mapFonts
      field515 &gt; mapFonts
      field450 &gt; mapFonts
      method648 &gt; popcnt
      field431 &gt; text

NotFoxtrot (2):
      Add Pharaoh&#39;s sceptre to the jewellery count
      Add new overlay for Pyramid Plunder

Seth (5):
      boss timers: replace resource image with itemID images
      boss timers: add tooltips
      boss timers: add chaos elemental
      image component: fix images being off-centered
      poh plugin: Remove unnecessary toggles

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (4):
      Expose isStackable on ItemComposition objects
      Rename progress to state in GrandExchangeOffer
      runelite-api: Add Grand Exchange offer support
      Create Grand Exchange plugin

Tomas Slusny (9):
      Prevent throwing duplacite events for GameObject
      Add support for maniacal monkeys to hunter plugin
      Add default timeout to notify-send on Linux
      Rename &quot;Low memory&quot; to &quot;Low detail&quot; plugin
      Fix crash in ClienUI configChanged event
      Fix NPE in minimap plugin
      Remove animation checks
      Remove catch rate overlay
      Remove inSequence import b/c problems with mapping

XrioBtw (1):
      Add missing cancel menu action

arlyon (2):
      runelite-client: split ostype into its own utility
      runelite-client: enable fullscreen on osx

l2- (1):
      Xp orb fixes (#689)

semtexerror (4):
      cannon plugin: support unloading cannon
      cannon plugin: cleanup
      cannon plugin: add overlay for cannonballs left
      cannon plugin: draw npc double hit spots
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-22-1.2.17-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-22-1.2.17-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.17 Release</title>
        <summary>New raid scouting plugin, Kourend library book finder, and chat history plugin!</summary>
        <updated>2018-02-22T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>A new raids plugin was added by <a href="https://github.com/Kamielvf">@Kamielvf</a>. This plugin will make raids
an even more pleasant experience and adds support for scouting.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/raids-scouting.png" alt="raids-scouting"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/raids-points.png" alt="raids-points"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/raids-timer.png" alt="raids-timer"/></p>
<p>Due to recent success of Woox&#39;s <a href="https://wooxsolo.github.io/KourendLibrary/index.html">Kourend library website</a> one
of our contributors <a href="https://github.com/Abextm">@Abextm</a> decided to top that and implement a similar feature
into RuneLite. It shows where requested books will most likely be and also people who can
request books from you.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/kourend-library.png" alt="kourend-library"/></p>
<p>For everyone who loves smithing, Blast Furnace plugin was added.
It shows the money in the coffer and bars in the dispenser. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@sethtroll</a>!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/blastfurnace.png" alt="blastfurnace.png"/></p>
<p>The configuration system was significantly improved and the plugin manager interface was changed
to provide better access to enabling and disabling of plugins.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/plugin-manager.png" alt="plugin-manager"/></p>
<p>A new chat history plugin was added, that will preserve your chat history during logout and world
hopping. Never miss messages due to hopping again!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/chat-history.png" alt="chat-history"/></p>
<p>If you had problems before differentiating player and NPC minimap dots before, a new plugin for modifying
colors of the dots was added.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.17-Release/minimap.png" alt="minimap"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Screenshot plugin was improved and should now properly work with most of the level ups</li>
<li>Tooltips are now displaying even for game interface actions</li>
<li>Tooltips for ironmen and moderators now show the correct icon when hovered</li>
<li>Toggle to show only highlighted items was added to the Ground Items plugin</li>
<li>Configuration for the color of the NMZ absorption counter was added to the Nightmare Zone plugin</li>
<li>Clan chat icons now look good even in fixed mode</li>
<li>The speed of !price lookups is now quicker</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 10 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (22):
      Use client Varbit for index, lsb, msb
      Hide xtea plugin from list
      Hide config plugin
      config panel: fix check/uncheck image names
      runelite-client: remove many unnecessary bindings in configure() in plugins
      runelite-client: checkstyle fixes
      http-service: split itemservice into service and controller
      item controller: cache empty price lookups
      item service: always use last known price, and queue price updates instead
      Fix varbits to read the other settings[] array
      boosts plugin: check if skills change before removing infoboxes
      remembser name plugin: fix not setting usernames on session open
      runelite-client: add plugin dependencies
      xp tracker: expose xp stats
      woodcutting plugin: use stats from xp plugin
      fishing plugin: use stats from xp plugin
      runelite-client: add minimap dot plugin
      cannon plugin: check cannon location is in scene
      nmz: reformat config
      item service: change search to only search database
      slayer plugin: remove tasks with item image -1
      tooltip component: split text width calculation into its own method

Ben Moyer (1):
      Remove duplicate tracking info in fishing/woodcutting overlays

Joshua Filby (2):
      cache: release the ByteBuf allocated when calling ByteBuf#readBytes(int)
      Release ByteBuf in CacheClient when downloading chunks

Kamiel (3):
      Fix clanchat icons
      Update team cape plugin to make use of new plugin panel toggles
      Raids scouting plugin

Lotto (8):
      screenshot-plugin: extend test to test Attack and Hunter lvlups
      Change copyright header for UniquePassive to Lotto
      screenshot-plugin: adjust time/date format to not include spaces
      screenshot-plugin: run image saving logic in another thread
      Render modicons in tooltips
      Import API for getting remembered username from preferences.dat
      Update RememberUsernamePlugin to save the name from the vanilla feature
      Change name of RememberUsername plugin to UsernameSyncer

Max Weber (10):
      Fix removing items from the TitleToolbar
      injector: Choose the right constructor if multiple exist
      Change perspective to convert world to local points centered on the tile
      hunter plugin: add imp box
      hunter plugin: Fix null pointer when going across a loading zone
      Add Kourend Library plugin
      Fix menu action clicked hook log
      Merge HUNTER_LEVEL_UP* and DIALOG_LIBRARY_FIND* into DIALOG_SPRITE*
      Allow the info panel&#39;s navButton to be removed on shutDown
      Sort the PluginToolbar

Nickolaj Jepsen (1):
      nmz plugin: add color config for the absorption infobox

Seth (6):
      item stat: fix overlay being shown ontop of menu
      imagePanelComponent: Add support for multiple images
      Add Blast furnace plugin
      Remove @Nullable Client annotations
      ground items: Add toggle to show highlighted items only
      ground items: re-order the config

Tomas Slusny (18):
      Add ability to disable/enable all plugins
      Remove enabled() checks
      Fix slayer plugin task reset on config change
      Add region tile manager
      Clear game objects on plugin shutdown
      Add null check for 6 hour waiting time
      Add startup and shutdown methods to DiscordPlugin
      Enable/disable plugins in the ConfigPanel
      Remove &quot;plugin&quot; from each plugin name
      Properly invalidate cache and load icons in Clan
      Re-cache chatMessageManager colors on startup
      Disable configuration button when all items hidden
      Add support for Karambwan/Karambwanji to fishing
      Display tooltips for widget actions
      Fix PuzzleSolverOverlay layer
      Enhance the sending message API
      Add check for clan members &gt; 0 when inserting icon
      Add chat history plugin

UniquePassive (5):
      Add Hunter levelup widget info
      screenshot-plugin: don&#39;t include spaces in file names
      screenshot-plugin: adjust the comments for to-be-parsed text
      screenshot-plugin: don&#39;t depend on &quot;a &quot; in skill name string
      screenshot-plugin: add detection for Hunter levelups
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-15-1.2.16-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-15-1.2.16-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.16 Release</title>
        <summary>New puzzle box solver, barrows plugin, and NMZ plugin!</summary>
        <updated>2018-02-15T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>An awesome puzzle box plugin has been finally added to RuneLite thanks to work of
<a href="https://github.com/UniquePassive">@UniquePassive</a>. Clues are now even easier to do!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/puzzlebox1.png" alt="puzzlebox1"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/puzzlebox2.png" alt="puzzlebox2"/></p>
<p>For everyone who likes to AFK, thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Fire-Proof">@Fire-Proof</a>
a Nightmare Zone plugin was added. It shows your current Nightmare Zone points in nice
RuneLite custom overlay, notifies you when you are low on absorption, and when your
overload runs out.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/nmz.png" alt="nmz"/></p>
<p>Barrows helper has been added in a new Barrows plugin by <a href="https://github.com/Sethtroll">@Sethtroll</a>.
No more black minimap when in tunnels or finding the correct doors!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/barrows1.png" alt="barrows1"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/barrows2.png" alt="barrows2"/></p>
<p>Additionally, abyss rift click boxes are now highlighted thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@Sethtroll</a> (again).</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/abyss.png" alt="abyss"/></p>
<p>And new Rogue&#39;s den plugin has been added to RuneLite as well, that shows click boxes
of the Rogue&#39;s den obstacles. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/ShaunDreclin">@ShaunDreclin</a>!</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.16-Release/roguesden.png" alt="roguesden"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements and bug fixes, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The zoom plugin is now working again thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Abextm">@Abextm</a></li>
<li>New option has been added to RuneLite settings that will make your window stay always on top</li>
<li>Client is now logging the logs to ~/.runelite/logs, so in case you want to report problem,
you can also send the logs that would help us with resolving the problem.</li>
<li>POH icon&#39;s displaying when on the wrong floor was fixed</li>
<li>Slayer task now do not decrements anymore when your slayer level is decremented
(for example in God wars or from KBD special attack)</li>
<li>Title bar buttons are now shown in the info panel when you have custom title bar disabled</li>
</ul>
<p>Enjoy the new release!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 11 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Abex (1):
      Allow titlebar buttons to be moved out of the titlebar

Adam (9):
      mousehighlight: don&#39;t show tooltip on sliding puzzles
      timers plugin: respect enabled configuration
      perspective: add method for checking if world location is in scene
      fishing plugin: move minimap overlay to own overlay
      runelite-client: shut down discord service when closed
      http-service: try to release okhttp resources on shutdown
      rs2asm: allow multiple newlines after header or instruction
      item manager: allow getting images with quantity
      item manager: also allow specifying stackable

Max Weber (6):
      method984 &gt; runScript
      Revert &quot;scripts: disable callbacks&quot;
      injector: copy exceptions on Injected classes
      Add raw injector to hook the script interpreter
      Zoom plugin: Relax inner zoom constraint
      injector: Allow injection of &lt;init&gt; and &lt;clinit&gt;

Nickolaj Jepsen (1):
      Add NMZ plugin

NotFoxtrot (1):
      Add always on top setting

Seth (8):
      runecraft plugin: show click boxes of abyss rifts
      cache: Update ObjectManager to include NULL names
      runelite-api: redump objectid with null names
      runelite-api: add getActions, imposterIds, and imposter to ObjectComposition
      perspective: add getCanvasTextMiniMapLocation
      Add barrows plugin
      slayer plugin: add check for cachedXp when xp changes
      poh plugin: fix icons displaying when changing planes

ShaunDreclin (1):
      Add Rogues&#39; Den plugin

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (1):
      Fix mismapping of MouseWheel

Tomas Slusny (2):
      Fix logging inside info panel plugin
      Add logback logger that will log to file

Tyler Hardy (3):
      Remove unused Zulrah plugin assets
      Update ItemID from 160 cache
      runepouch plugin: use itemmanager to render runepouch item icons

UniquePassive (4):
      Add puzzle box InventoryID
      Add puzzle box WidgetInfo
      Add puzzle solving algorithm
      Add puzzle solver plugin
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-08-1.2.15-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-08-1.2.15-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.15 Release</title>
        <summary>RuneLite 1.2.15 is released!</summary>
        <updated>2018-02-08T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>An agility plugin has been added which shows the click boxes of ability obstaces.
Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/someonewithaninternetconnection">@SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection</a>
for their hard work on reversing the clickbox calculations and making this happen.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/agility1.png" alt="agility1"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/agility2.png" alt="agility2"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/agility3.png" alt="agility3"/></p>
<p><a href="https://discordapp.com/rich-presence">Discord Rich Presence</a> support has been
added in a new Discord plugin from <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a>.
It will show what skill you are training in game as your discord status.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/discord.png" alt="discord"/></p>
<p>Additionally, abyss rift locations and player owned house locations are now
marked on the minimap thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@Sethtroll</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/abyss.png" alt="abyss"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/poh.png" alt="poh"/></p>
<p>And the burners are now marked as lit or unlit:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.15-Release/burners.png" alt="burners"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>The screenshot plugin now has configuration for the auto screenshot of
levelups and rewards</li>
<li>There is now an option to overlay non-clan members in the player indicator
plugin</li>
<li>Theoretical boosts have been added to the item stats plugin</li>
<li>Indicators have been added for stat boots as an alternative to the current
overlay</li>
<li>Fix sometimes drawing overlays at the wrong height above players and npcs</li>
<li>Don&#39;t enable low memory mode on the audio subsystem when the client is
configured in low memory mode, so the sounds sound normal</li>
<li>The teamcape plugin has been readded</li>
</ul>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 9 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (10):
      Revert &quot;runelite-client: remove teamcape plugin&quot;
      cache client: log when index crc changes too
      cache service: fix duplicating index to archive associations
      cache service: split up into cache controller and service
      Split out cache updater into own project
      http service: change cache datasource to runelite-cache2
      runelite-client: add central skill icon cache
      screenshot plugin: add configuration for auto screenshot of levelups and rewards
      screenshot plugin: fix test
      player indicators: use new isFriend/isClanMember api

Ben Moyer (2):
      add option to overlay non-clanmate player names
      Add theoretical boost to item stat overlay

Kamiel (5):
      info box component: vertically center images
      Add indicators to boosts plugin
      Fix several issues with indicators
      Prevent tooltip from being shown when runepouch is empty
      Make examine plugin work for runepouch

Max Weber (4):
      move session management into the SessionManager from the AccountPlugin
      Add info panel plugin
      field1147 &gt; logicalHeight
      change getModelHeight to getLogicalHeight

Seth (5):
      runelite-api: add MiniMapImageLocation to perspective
      runecraft plugin: add Abyss rifts overlay
      make injected fields private
      Fix color tags in OpponentInfo
      Add Poh plugin

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (9):
      Decrease the injector plugin&#39;s verbosity
      runescape-client: Rename some AABB-related fields
      Simplify Triangle and Vertex with lombok
      Move orientation incantation into Vertex.rotate
      Add method to get the clickable area of a TileObject
      Add events for Decorative and Ground TileObjects
      Add agility plugin
      Fix boosts plugin style nits
      Fix NPEs from BoostsPlugin at startup

Tomas Slusny (6):
      Change default overlay position to UNDER_WIDGETS
      Add new overlay layer position
      Adjust overlay layers and priorities
      Fix MLM plugin overlay layer
      Add Discord RPC service
      Add Discord plugin

UniquePassive (3):
      Always use &quot;high memory&quot; audio
      Rename highMemory to audioHighMemory
      Rename ocLowDetail to objectCompositionLowDetail

Unmoon (3):
      Idle Notifier - Change wording and default value of &quot;Alert When Focused&quot;
      Show ground items under widgets and with interfaces open
      Remove unused import
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-01-1.2.14-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-02-01-1.2.14-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.14 Release</title>
        <summary>RuneLite 1.2.14 is released!</summary>
        <updated>2018-02-01T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p><a href="https://github.com/abextm">@Abextm</a> added an item stats plugin which shows a
tooltip on food and potions to show its effect and whether or not it would be
wasteful to consume it.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.14-Release/itemstats.png" alt="itemstats"/></p>
<p>A new zoom plugin was added which extends the zoom limits on the built in client
Zoom feature:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.14-Release/zoom.png" alt="zoom"/></p>
<p>A new motherlode mine plugin was added to mark the locations of ore veins and
rocks, thanks to <a href="https://github.com/sethtroll">@Sethtroll</a>. Additionally, many
new potions and freeze spells have been added to the timer plugin.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.14-Release/mlm.png" alt="mlm"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> reworked the XP tracker plugin to have a nice new UI:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.14-Release/xptracker.png" alt="xptracker"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/oplosthee">@oplosthee</a> added an achievement diary indicator
plugin which shows which sections of diaries have been completed.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.14-Release/diary.png" alt="diary"/></p>
<p>There are also several smaller improvements, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>XP drop plugin to recolor xp drops when prayers are activated</li>
<li>Fix BA plugin for recent game update</li>
<li>Add granite cannonballs to cannon plugin</li>
<li>Add configuration option for the runepouch overaly to only show on hover</li>
<li>Added configurable tick delay to metronome plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 10 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (52):
      injector: fix detecting if garbage value should be appended
      runelite-api: rename InventoryItemQuery -&gt; InventoryWidgetItemQuery
      runelite-api: add ItemContainer
      runelite-api: add inventory item query
      Add item stats plugin
      screenshot plugin: add test for different level up messages
      checkstyle: enforce whitespace after comma
      cache: remove script interpreter
      cache: allow passing instruction set to assembler
      runelite-api: add Script
      cache: add set_zoom_distance
      cache: add get_zoom_distance
      cache: add comment to rs2asm grammar
      cache: add set_camera_focal_point_height
      cache: add get_camera_focal_point_height
      cache: add script id to grammar
      runescape-api: add IndexData and IndexDataBase
      runescape-client: method1102 -&gt; execute6500
      runescape-client: rename conflicting getConfigData method in IndexDataBase
      Add slf4j to mixins and expose logger in Hooks for them
      mixin injector: remove assert for moved code to not have exceptions
      Add ability to overlay cache archives
      Add runelite vm opcode and event
      Add int and string script stack to api
      Add script assembler plugin for packing scripts at build time
      Add runelite-scripts project for packaging overlaid scripts and dependency
      Add zoom plugin
      cache service: fix findArchive to select distinct
      runelite-client: add xp drop plugin which colors based on prayers
      metronome plugin: remove configurable sound ids until a better solution is found
      runelite-api: add rigour and augury prayers
      xo drop plugin: add rigour and augury
      xo drop plugin: set back xp drops to default color too
      mlm plugin: disable until it can be rewritten without scene scans every frame
      ground items: only loop tiles which are within distance
      ground items: REGION_SIZE - 1 since this is inclusive now
      cache: allow carriage returns in newlines in scripts
      Remote projectile target and length tracking
      mixins: fix getProjectiles queue iteration logic
      Remove unused imports
      Remove even more unused imports
      item manager: fix trying to cache null in getItemPrice
      config manager: thread config flushes to disk too
      slayer plugin: fix getting -1 count left on tasks
      runelite-client: fix exception from --no-rs
      xp tracker: don&#39;t add duplicate entries if nothing changes
      xp tracker plugin: update on logout
      runelite-api: add game object and wall object spawn/change/despawn events
      cannon plugin: update for event change
      hunter plugin: update for event change
      mlm plugin: rewrite to use events
      mlm plugin: default to enabled once again

C Gibson (1):
      Disable screenshots on login screen

Cameron Moberg (1):
      Fixed Barbarian Assault plugin to work with osrs update on 2018/25/1

Kamiel (1):
      Add granite cannonball support to plugin

Max Weber (6):
      method2965 &gt; getScript
      method1752 &gt; getScriptByFile
      Enable custom window border warning
      Add low-memory mode warning
      itemstats: Fix SuperRestore and friends
      runescape-api: remove RSCacheableNode::getNext() and getPrevious(). They are different than RSNode&#39;s next and previous, but have the same signature so they can get called instead. This caused the ground overlay to only show 1 item because it was iterating the cache, not the item list.

Seth (14):
      Add hover option to runepouch
      Add graphic changed event
      timers plugin: add more timers
      Fix for screenshot HP level
      Add Wrath rune to Runepouch
      Add timer tooltips
      Fix spelling inconsistencies/add rest of potions
      Add Motherlode plugin
      Add custom colors to ground items
      Fix motherlode Ids
      timers plugin: check config before checking message
      timers plugin: add raids potions
      Fix spelling error on timer
      Add raid varbit check to remove timers

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (3):
      Fishing plugin: Add fishing spots north of seers&#39; village
      Remove unused import
      Include unit prices in examine messages

Tomas Slusny (7):
      Change conversion of config stream to map to pairs
      Fix coloring of warned attack styles
      Fix the frame is displayable exception
      Update XP tracking plugin to include more info
      Preserve guava classes in the shaded jar
      Change AccountSession to use lombok features
      Fix access levels of WSClient

UniquePassive (6):
      Add Dimension to configs
      Add a config setting for the game applet&#39;s size
      Add a Reset button to config panels for resetting to defaults
      Shift local indices only once
      Make sure injected methods don&#39;t invoke copied methods
      screenshot plugin: fix okhttp resource leak on imgur upload

oplosthee (5):
      Add Diary Progress Indicator plugin (#429)
      Change duration of Super Antifire Potions from 2 to 3 minutes
      Extend Metronome Plugin with configurable sound and tick delay (#454)
      Fix Karamja diary displaying incorrect progress
      Remove modification of original diary entry colors
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-25-1.2.13-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-25-1.2.13-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.13 Release</title>
        <summary>RuneLite 1.2.13 is released!</summary>
        <updated>2018-01-25T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>This release includes several notable features, including:</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/UniquePassive">@UniquePassive</a> added a screenshot plugin,
overlay layers, which automatically takes a screen shot on level up, clue
completion, and quest completion. The screenshots may optionally be
automatically uploaded to imgur.</p>
<p>You may manually take a screenshot by clicking the camera icon in the titlebar:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.13-Release/screenshotplugin.png" alt="screenshot-plugin"/></p>
<p>If you enjoy the old Low Detail mode, <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a>
contributed a low detail mode plugin which lets you toggle it.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.13-Release/lowdetail.png" alt="lowdetail"/></p>
<p>Finally, <a href="https://github.com/someonewithaninternetconnection">@SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection</a>
added a metronome plugin to aid with timing game ticks.</p>
<p>There were also several smaller improvements, including:</p>
<ul>
<li>Fixed ground items overlay to correctly account for tile height when drawing item names.</li>
<li>Allow plugin panels, including the configuration panel, to keep state between
being collapsed and expanded.</li>
<li>Fix idle notifier to more reliably notify you</li>
<li>Fix broken glyphs which are evident on some overlays</li>
<li>Add infernal eel to fishing plugin</li>
</ul>
<p>On a more serious note, Jagex has requested removal of the Zulrah Helper,
Volcanic Mine Helper, Teamcape Overlay, and AoE Plugin for being in violation of
the game rules. These plugins have been removed.</p>
<p>Additionally, support for loading external plugins has been removed upon request
from Jagex.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 13 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (19):
      cache service: lazily load store
      cache service: skip loading filedata as it is not necessary for cache updater
      cache service: move database updating to happen during download
      cache service: don&#39;t skip already up to date archives
      cache service: use an identity hashmap as equals checks archive contents
      Revert &quot;cache service: use an identity hashmap as equals checks archive contents&quot;
      Revert &quot;cache service: don&#39;t skip already up to date archives&quot;
      Revert &quot;cache service: move database updating to happen during download&quot;
      cache service: remove unused import
      item service: set cache-control: public too
      config panel: don&#39;t show groups with no visible config items
      runelite-client: move all main loop checks info try/catch
      infobox manager: check infobox isn&#39;t null
      xp tracker: don&#39;t reset on logout or hop
      http-service: split hiscore service from controller
      http-service: add beginning of xp tracker
      deobfuscator: map classes of static fields which are initialized in clinit
      Add maven central to be tried before repo.runelite.net
      runelite-client: remove version and account name from title

Cameron Moberg (2):
      Fixed Slayer task infobox only updating on state change
      Changed how idle checks in combat

Dreyri (16):
      add setter for textColor
      add setter for spriteId
      add setter for width
      add setter for height
      add setter for name
      add setter for contentType
      add setter for type
      add getter/setter for scrollX
      add getter/setter for scrollY
      add setter/getter for originalX
      add getter/setter for originalY
      add getter for paddingX
      add getter for paddingY
      add setter for paddingX
      add setter for paddingY
      dev tools: allow editing widget settings

Martin Tuskevicius (1):
      Swapped viewport width and height fields.

Max Weber (1):
      Allow PluginPanels to keep state

Seth (1):
      Add Clue Scroll/Barrows to screenshot plugin

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (7):
      Name some internal runescape audio bits
      Implement sound-playing API
      Add collection of named SoundEffect IDs
      Add metronome plugin
      Rename debug boundingbox drawmode enums
      Expose runescape click/boundingbox display mode
      Add bounding/clickbox buttons to the devtools plugin

SteveOSRS (1):
      Added infernal eel to fishing plugin

Tomas Slusny (14):
      Add startUp method for attack indicators plugin
      Fix startup and shutdown method of AccountPlugin
      Add shutDown to BossTimersPlugin
      Add shutDown to ConfigPlugin
      Add shutDown to DevtoolsPlugin
      Add shutDown method to HiscorePlugin
      Add startup and shutdown methods to SlayerPlugin
      Add shutDown method to TimersPlugin
      Add shutDown method to XpTrackerPlugin
      Fix NPE in ScreenShotPlugin
      Fix idle notifications for animation changes
      Update Project Lombok version to 1.16.20
      runescape-client: rename low detail fields
      Add low memory mode plugin

Tyler Hardy (1):
      Add gargoyle boss to aoe plugin

UniquePassive (7):
      runescape-client: Fix broken glyphs
      Notify before 5 minute idle and 6h logout
      Add nullcheck for counter in SlayerPlugin#onConfigChanged
      runelite-client: update to substance 8.0.00-dev
      runelite-client: add client ui loaded event
      runelite-client: add screenshot plugin
      http-service: fix exception on empty config setKey request body

noremac201 (2):
      Progress Bar Component to not show 2 decimals percent
      Standardize xpglobe tooltip width

oplosthee (1):
      Incorporate height into the GroundItems overlay
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-18-1.2.12-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-18-1.2.12-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.12 Release</title>
        <summary>RuneLite 1.2.12 is released!</summary>
        <updated>2018-01-18T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Adam</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>This release includes several notable features, including:</p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/UniquePassive">@UniquePassive</a> added overlay layers, which
allows RuneLite to optionally render beneath both the game menu and in-game
interfaces (such as the bank).</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/overlayorder.png" alt="interface-layers"/></p>
<p><a href="https://github.com/Noremac201">@Noremac201</a> added a barbarian assult plugin
which introduces a timer until next change, and allows left-click calls.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/ba-click.png" alt="ba-click"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/ba-timer.png" alt="ba-timer"/></p>
<p>A new cannon plugin was introduced to count the number of cannonballs left in
your cannon, thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Sethtroll">@Sethtroll</a>.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/cannon.png" alt="cannon"/></p>
<p>The new player indicators plugin will draw your friend and clanmates names:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/playernames.png" alt="clannames"/></p>
<p>Some improvements have been made to the attack indicator plugin to hide unwanted
attack styles instantly. Thanks to <a href="https://github.com/Dreyri">@Dreyri</a> for his
work on this.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/attackstyles.gif" alt="attackstyles"/></p>
<p>Additionally, various new AoE attacks have been added to the AoE plugin,
including Vorkath, Galvek, Vet&#39;ion, Chaos Fanatic, and the Corporeal Beast.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/acid.gif" alt="acid"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/fireball.gif" alt="fireball"/></p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/spawn.gif" alt="spawn"/></p>
<p>Finally, the configuration panel is now more searchable with a new search bar thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a>:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.12-Release/configsearch.png" alt="configsearch"/></p>
<p>Enjoy.</p>
<p>- Adam</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 10 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Adam (11):
      runelite-client: fix plugin manager test
      Move RS-related events to runelite-api
      injector: fix copying method code to update code-&gt;method, instructions-&gt;code, and instruction-&gt;instructions pointers
      Move field hooks to mixins
      runelite-plugin-archetype: update for events which moved to api
      readme: update logo url
      player indicators: update isFriend -&gt; isFriended
      aoeprojectileinfo: store projectiles in a map
      runelite-api: expose widget group ids
      runelite-api: fix combat fornula
      xpglobes: don&#39;t break at virt level 126

Bart van Helvert (1):
      Deobfuscation and renaming of object definitions

Cameron Moberg (1):
      Add barbarian assault plugin

Dreyri (31):
      update hz.h to Widget.dynamicX
      update hz.d to Widget.dynamicY
      update hz.v to Widget.dynamicWidth
      update hz.ak to Widget.originalHeight
      update Client.hw to myPlayerIndex
      update ar.ce to KeyFocusListener.keyPressed
      update x.nw to BoundingBox3D.minimapSprite
      update eq.n to getItemStackAmountText
      rename field921 to overheadTextCount
      rename field997 to overheadTexts
      rename field929 to overheadTextsCyclesRemaining
      rename method4886 to getTextWidth
      rename field926 to overheadTextsOffsetX
      rename field925 to overheadTextsOffsetY
      rename field1100 to maxOverheadTexts
      rename method4884 to drawTextCentered
      rename method4903 to drawText
      swap screenX and screenY
      rename field923 to overheadTextsX
      rename field924 to overheadTextsY
      rename method168 to draw2DExtras
      update field1003 to lastLeftClickX
      update field936 to lastLeftClickY
      rename field940 to pressedItemIndex
      renamed method5211 to drawAtOpacity
      rename field 1082 to itemPressedDuration
      rename method3079 to processMouseInput
      rename field679 to mouseLastX
      rename field682 to mouseLastY
      rename class34.field455 to middleMouseMovesCamera
      rename field945 to itemBeingDragged

Frederik Engels (6):
      runescape-client: update Projectile mappings
      Track projectile target and spawn cycle. Add to api with rest of mapings.
      runelite-client: add projectiles to devtools
      runelite-client: add new aoes to aoewarningplugin
      runelite-client: change combat level plugin to use game tick event
      Add widget hidden change event, use in attack indicator plugin

Max Weber (2):
      Update ItemIDs
      Prevent the client from taking focus when it doesn&#39;t have it.

Seth (3):
      Add Wintertodt Aoe
      overlay renderer: add check for chatbox being minimized
      Add Cannon plugin

Tomas Slusny (7):
      Add support for making tar idle notification
      Let overlapping tooltips stack vertically
      Add search bar to ConfigPanel
      Fix runelite-plugin-archetype
      Add tile indicators plugin
      Add plugin for displaying player names
      Fix new player-is-x mixins

Tyler Hardy (1):
      Generalize and add MenuActions

UniquePassive (10):
      Don&#39;t produce erroneous code when @Copy mixin method missing dummy param
      Don&#39;t let @Copy/@Replace methods have more params than ob method
      Implement optimized isFriend, isIgnore and isClanMember
      SpecOrbOverlay: Use fields for position constants + adjust specorb pos
      Remove extra pixels on the right side of minimap_orb_background
      Add API for getting the client BufferProvider
      injector: add injector for drawAfterWidgets call
      runescape-client: add hook for draw under widgets
      runelite-client: add OverlayLayer and rendering logic for multiple overlay layers
      runelite-client: update plugins for new overlay layer
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-12-1.2.11-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2018-01-12-1.2.11-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.11 Release</title>
        <summary>New 1.2.11 release of RuneLite is out. Notable new features are an awesome Hunter Plugin and support for more potion timers</summary>
        <updated>2018-01-12T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>In this release we made a lot of improvements to client source, performance and
overall stability of the client. But there are few new features that are
definitely worth mentioning.</p>
<p>First, and the biggest one is <strong>Hunter</strong> plugin (thanks to
<a href="https://github.com/RobinWeymans">@RobinWeymans</a>). Hunter plugin will show you
state of your traps and also time until they will break. That should improve
your overall hunting experience (and makes the terrible skill less terrible).
Here is small preview:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.11-Release/hunterplugin.png" alt="hunter-plugin"/></p>
<p>We also added support for some missing potions for the <strong>Timers</strong> plugin, and that
also includes the newest released potion, Super Antifire Potion.</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.11-Release/newtimers.png" alt="newtimers"/></p>
<p>And last feature on the list is support for <strong>native window decorations</strong>. That
means now you have option to let your window manager handle the window
decorations (title bar, window borders). Here is small preview using my window
manager (bspwm) without any window borders:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.11-Release/nativewindow.png" alt="native-window"/></p>
<p>As I said in the beginning of the post, we made a lot of improvements to the
client source code (mainly decoupling), so if you are bored Java developer
looking for project to contribute to, you are always welcome!</p>
<p>Hopefully you will like the new release, enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 15 contributors this release!</p>
<pre><code>Abex (1):
      client: Add option to disable custom window chrome/style

Adam (30):
      Skip archetype test by default
      cache: default index data to protocol 6
      runelite-api: add equipment inventory slot id, inventory id, logout widget and chat message type 7
      cache: fix writeBigSmart
      cache: fix readBigSmart
      cache: fix readString to not sign extend negative values
      cache: rename some fields of object and interface
      cache: lombok definitions
      cache: add a few more write* to outputstream
      cache: add savers
      cache: add map and location definition, convert Region loading to use it
      cache: split cache client and server into their own projects
      runelite-proxy: subtree split into separate repository
      cache: disable map image dumper test
      cache: also disable map dumper test
      runelite-client: move infoboxes back to top left
      runelite-client: always render tooltips on top
      cache test: get tmpdir from a system property
      injector: allow method hooking to end of methods with multiple returns
      Consistently capitalize RuneLite
      Update logo
      xp tracker: reset on world hop and on logging in
      xp tracker: remove unused import
      runelite-client: fix --no-rs
      dev tools: draw over everything
      http-service: fix item price cache to use fetched time instead of price time
      http-service: remove junit/mockito dependencies since spring pulls them in
      http-service: disable default cache control provided by spring-security
      http-service: add cache control to item price
      http-service: change item price cache to 30 minutes

Alexander (2):
      Fall back to default font for glyphs not in the custom font
      ExaminePlugin: Make sure widget children array index is valid

Devin (3):
      Add fight cave plugin config
      Update fight cave plugin overlay
      Update zulrah plugin overlay

Devin French (1):
      Combine BOTTOM_RIGHT and ABOVE_CHATBOX_RIGHT overlays for fixed mode

Julian Tith (1):
      Add craft spinning animation ID and idle notification

Max Weber (1):
      runelite-client: add ConfigItem.warnOnDisable and warnOnEnable to configure when confirmationWarning is shown

Onvo (6):
      New MenuActions related to the hunter plugin
      Add Widget.contains point
      Add GameObjectsChanged event
      Make ground items overlay use new Widget.contains
      Add hunter plugin
      Add colors for impling types

Runelite auto updater (2):
      [maven-release-plugin] prepare for next development iteration
      [maven-release-plugin] prepare release runelite-parent-1.2.11

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (5):
      Actually fix example plugin archetype
      Add tests for archetype-plugin compilability
      Reduce clearRect calls to improve framerate
      Prevent cursor icon from getting stuck as the wrong shape
      Slayer plugin - fix &quot;count on items&quot; feature

Tomas Slusny (20):
      Fix OkHttp connection leaks on connection error
      Change UIManager defaults to use OSRS font
      Change XP tracker button to use image
      Simplify navigation button code
      Move IconTextField to Hiscore plugin
      Normalize plugin panel display
      Change Notifier to be injectable service
      Extract session-related logic to SessionManager
      Extract runQuery to QueryRunner service
      Move creation of client to RuneLite
      Move setTitle to ClientUI
      Move creation of tray icon to ClientUI
      Cleanup RuneLite class fields
      Move creation of UI to ClientUI class
      Remove unnecessary null checks for game client
      Show account and config plugins when outdated
      Change warning for not found task to debug
      Add support for super antifire potion
      Add Antidote++ timer to TimerPlugin
      Improve clan rank caching

UniquePassive (10):
      Don&#39;t NPE when Player name is null
      Expand the hiscore panel when looking up players
      Fix BackgroundComponent&#39;s background overflow
      Fix previous result not being cleared in hiscore plugin
      Fix ground items not being toggleable
      Fix the UI freezing when refreshing widgets in the Dev Tools
      runescape-client: Rename RSCanvas to GameCanvas
      runescape-client: Rename RSSocket to GameSocket
      Add a world list lookup client
      Add world types

Unmoon (4):
      Ground Items - Fix alch value not applying to whole stack
      Ground Items - Fix coins not having value
      Ground Items - Fix quantity in high alch value display
      Ground Items - Always show highlighted items

kokkue (1):
      idle plugin: add ornament dragon pickaxe

noremac201 (11):
      Added missing skilling skills from boosts overlay. Reordered from left to right and up to down.
      Add new overlay position for above right side of chatbox
      Change attack style plugin to use overlay position ABOVE_CHATBOX_RIGHT
      Added ProgressBar Component
      Modified PanelComponent to hold a ProgressBarComponent
      Updated XpGlobes to use new Components
      Fixed setStroke not being reset in Graphics object
      Added ReportButton Widget to api
      Added Report Button Utilities Plugin
      Fixed attackStyle not being correct without configChangeEvent
      Fixed type 20 attack weapon styles

utsukami (1):
      Fixes idle notifications occurring when they shouldn&#39;t (interacting with bankers/players). See #282
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2017-12-21-1.2.10-Release</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2017-12-21-1.2.10-Release"/>
        <title>1.2.10 Release</title>
        <summary>New 1.2.10 release of RuneLite is out. We added many new features, like native UI, notifications and few plugin improvements.</summary>
        <updated>2017-12-21T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>This release adds lots of new functionality to RuneLite to make the end-user
experience even better, and to compete with well established third-party
clients.</p>
<p>The most notable new feature is the <strong>new UI design</strong>. I tried to make it look as
close to the native OSRS interfaces as possible. Here is the end result:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.10-Release/native-ui.png" alt="native ui"/></p>
<p>The UI was updated for all of the current RuneLite plugins, and the new API for
it is really easy to use, so it can be used in future plugins too. An example
of plugin using the new UI api is the new <strong>Team Capes</strong> plugin.</p>
<p>The plugin is showing the amount of players wearing specific team capes
currently visible on the map, which is very useful for pking clans. Here is how
it looks in game:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.10-Release/team-cape.png" alt="team capes plugin"/></p>
<p>Till now it was hard to check the price of item you just got as a drop
from monster, or just simply to check price of stack of your precious magic
logs in bank. That is why there were quite a few improvements to examine plugin
in the client. Now you are able to examine items and item stacks in you bank,
inventory, equipment screen or even in the Miscellania screen and it shows
Grand Exchange and High Alchemy price of that item in the game chat. Here is
small example:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.10-Release/examine-plugin.png" alt="examine plugin"/></p>
<p>To make talking to your clan mates easier, there is new clan chat plugin
that shows current ranks of every clan chat member next to his/her name.
Example:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.10-Release/clan-chat.png" alt="clan chat plugin"/></p>
<p>There were also some background changes in the client to make it work better,
fix some bugs and possibly make it faster. One of the background improvements
that is also visible to end users is the use of the native notification system,
so it now supports every Linux distribution with working notification system
and even Mac OS (with same notification support for Windows as before). Example
of the notification system in action on Arch Linux with Dunst notification
daemon:</p>
<p><img src="/img/blog/1.2.10-Release/native-notifications.png" alt="native notifications"/></p>
<p>Well, hopefully you like new release, and as usual, enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>
<h3 id="new-commits">New commits</h3>
<p>We had 9 contributors this release! Special thanks to <a href="https://github.com/deathbeam">@deathbeam</a> for his hard work.</p>
<pre><code>Adam (26):
      runelite-client: use lombok for slf4j logger creation
      runelite-client: lombok events
      runelite-client: change AnimationChanged event to have an Actor
      executor: optimize processExceptions()
      deobfuscator: do not cfg deob methods with exceptions in them
      runescape-client: redump
      runelite-client: fix infoboxes
      injector: cast object references to the field type in setters
      injector: add construct injector to create new instances of classes
      injector: ignore synthetic methods in InjectConstruct
      runescape-api: fix javadoc error
      injector: support hooking to ends of methods
      Move setMessage hook to end of method
      clanchat: don&#39;t load icons more than once
      runelite-client: fix scheduler for concurrent modifications
      chat message manager: avoid adding chat messages on threads
      cache: remove whirlpool as it is not in osrs
      cache: improve xtea test
      cache: use own Xtea implmentation instead of bouncycastle&#39;s
      cache: test scope slf4j-simple
      cache server: never send appended archive revision
      cache: remove tree storage
      cache: fix compression with encryption
      cache: split loading archive files from archive loading
      injector: skip over dups when recursively copying array index instructions
      deobfuscator: remove apache commons dependency

Devin (5):
      Add ImagePanelComponent overlay component
      Add getTeam method for Player
      Add setter for background color of overlay components
      Fix padding for bottom right overlays
      Add team capes plugin

Runelite auto updater (1):
      [maven-release-plugin] prepare for next development iteration

SomeoneWithAnInternetConnection (2):
      Fix IllegalArgumentExceptions from XPGlobes&#39; tooltips for level 1 stats
      Fix example plugin to use the new overlay API

Tomas Slusny (16):
      Add hide items under value to GroundItems plugin
      Make native notifications lightweight
      Add clan ranks to clan chat
      Improve item caching
      Add chat message recolouring API
      Show item price when examining item
      Show full price for stackable items when examined
      runelite-client: add plugin changed event
      runelite-client: Make overlay UI reuseable and look native
      Cleanup overlay logic after native-ui changes
      Fix displaying of examine price without GE value
      Add support for examining bank and eq items price
      Fix overlay renderer cache
      Isolate graphics for each overlay (#267)
      Remove unused app property from RSStub
      runelite-client: Add app name to RuneliteProperties

Toocanzs (3):
      Move common game state and interface checks to overlay
      Change game tick hook to npc update
      Dispose of BufferedImage graphics in overlay util

Tyler Hardy (4):
      Add Karambwan fishing to animation and idle plugin
      Add crazy arch to aoe plugin
      Remove FPS plugin (deprecated by base osrs ::displayfps)
      Fix default config for dynamic plugins


UniquePassive (1):
      Make special attack orb look a little nicer

Vagrant User (1):
      Add support for native notifications

XrioBtw (1):
      Fix tooltips rendering behind the game

rbbi (1):
      Guice : RuneliteProperties inj (#212)
</code></pre>
            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
    <entry>
        <id>https://runelite.net/blog/show/2017-12-13-New-Site</id>
        <link href="https://runelite.net/blog/show/2017-12-13-New-Site"/>
        <title>New Site</title>
        <summary>We created new website for RuneLite replacing old one generated by GitHub pages</summary>
        <updated>2017-12-13T00:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <author>
            <name>Tomas</name>
        </author>
        <content type="xhtml">
            <div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
                <p>So, I am happy to present you the new site. This site replaces the old one, what
was generated by GitHub pages.</p>
<p>This new site is using latest web development technologies, focusing on
performance, user-friendliness and responsivity. It is still new, so if you will
have any problems with the site, feel free to submit issue on it&#39;s
<a href="https://github.com/runelite/runelite.net/issues">GitHub repository</a>.</p>
<p>Also, if you want to contribute, it has never been easier, as the individual
blog posts are rendered from Markdown, so all you need to do to create new blog
post is to submit Pull Request to the repository with new Markdown file in
format <code>YYYY-DD-MM-My-Post-Title.md</code> in the <code>src/_posts</code> directory.</p>
<p>Well, all I can say now is, enjoy!</p>
<p>~ Tomas</p>

            </div>
        </content>
    </entry>
    
</feed>
